We were crossing yet another desert when
Kari got sick and collapsed.
Tai kind of freaked out
because it seems that when they
were younger, she almost
died, and Tai blames himself.
We soon discovered a deserted city,
and while Sora and TK watched over Kari,
Tai and I went in search of medicine.
Machindramon and his goons were tracking
our every move, and on our way back from
the hospital, we just barely escaped
annihilation.
When we finally rejoined
the others, Machindramon
showed up and imploded
the building we were hiding in.
Could things get any worse?
Probably.
How long do humans usually sleep when
they're sick, TK?
It's tough to say for sure, Gatoman,
but I'd guess anywhere between eight hours
and eight years, give or take a minute or
so.
Wow, then considering how high her fever
is, we'd better get comfortable.
I wish one of the older kids were here.
I bet they'd know how to wake her up.
You'll think of something, TK.
See?
I knew you'd think of something.
I'm still not sure that woke her.
Huh?
I could be wrong.
Hi, Kari.
Hit the snooze button.
Hmm, one more time.
Please.
You've slept enough.
How do you feel?
I think my fever's gone.
So, how long was I asleep for?
Let's just say that
when you fell asleep, I
had nine lives, and now
I'm down to only three.
Where is everybody?
Hmm.
Hey!
I hear Patamon!
I wonder if he's found anyone.
Oh.
Who's that with Patamon?
It's Biamon!
And Sora!
Kari, you're awake.
You look so much better.
Have you seen Ty and the others?
Mm-mm.
I looked everywhere, but couldn't find
them.
Ty!
Help me, Ty!
Kari!
My guess is that when we all fell,
Ty and Izzy landed somewhere else.
I hope they're all right.
Don't worry, Kari.
Oh, I almost forgot.
Look what Biamon found.
I'm sure it's the medicine Ty went to find
for you.
Why don't you keep it in case your fever
comes back?
You can use it as a reminder of how much
Ty loves you.
This place has a lot of twists and turns
to it.
I'm sure if we all look together,
we'll have no problem finding the others.
Right!
We'll work as a team!
Yeah.
I'll try to be strong enough to help,
too.
After all, Ty would do the same for me.
This place is like a museum of the famous
sewer systems of the world.
I'll pass on Yoder Exhibit.
Heh!
Too late for that!
Stop!
Huh?
Listen, do you guys hear something?
Yeah, I can hear it now, too.
What do you think it could be?
I don't know, but it sounds like it's
coming from over there.
Let's take a look.
Work!
Keep working or else!
I said work, you lazy Noomomond!
Golly!
You slimy Noomomond make me sick!
If you didn't have such a weakness to
sunlight, we wouldn't have to keep you
working underground to power Machinderbond
City on Spiral Mountain!
You deserve to live in the sewers!
Now get back to work before I really get
mad!
Isn't that Monzeemon?
What happened to him?
He used to be so cuddly!
That's not Monzeemon, TK!
That's Waru Monzeemon!
Monzeemon was sweet and cute, but Waru
Monzeemon is about as cuddly as a porcupine!
His bear paw will give you heartburn,
along with his heartbreak attack!
Big meanie!
He's torturing those poor Noomomon down
there!
How can one kind of Puppet Digimon be so
nice while another can be so evil?
I've been too hard on you guys!
You need a break!
Okay, break's over!
If we had more power...
Sorry!
What happened?
Did she get sick again?
What's going on here?
Get back to work!
Huh?
The Digi-Destined?
He knows we're here!
Somebody's been sleeping in my bed!
Run!
And here they are now!
Gatomon, please leave me here.
I need to free the Noomomon from their
chains.
Do you understand?
I guess so.
Catch us if you can, you big throw-run!
I'll get you!
Noomomon Digivolve 2!
Hey!
I'm on Digivolve 2!
Wait a second, I'm still me!
You guys must be low on energy!
What do we do now, Sora?
Running comes to mind!
Wait!
We'll wait for Digi-Destined!
Sora, something wonderful is happening to
me!
I've never been able to fly this fast
before!
Me too!
Watch me go!
Faster!
Fast!
Attack!
I don't care what you're
faster than, as long as
you're faster than a
gigantic rolling teddy bear!
Queen Kari!
The Noomomon think you're...their queen!
I'm back!
Han, what are you doing out here?
Isn't it time for your flogging?
Don't just sit there, staring!
Get back to work!
Hey!
Who cut your chains off?
I did.
Got a problem?
Kari, no!
You're through!
Get off of me, you green blobs of sludge!
I'll beat the scuffing out of you!
No, Maman.
Kari!
You really think you have a chance against
me?
Come on!
Give it your best shot!
This is easier than swatting Digi-Fly!
Heartbreak attack!
No!
Where's that light coming from?
Kari!
What's happening?
I'm surging with energy!
Quick, get me a scratching post!
Boys and girls!
Oh, gang-ing up, huh?
I'll put you to work, too!
What do you think of that?
Meteor, away!
And a fake!
Hey!
Ugh!
No more chains, new Maman.
They're cute when they're not so slimy!
I love you, Queen Kari!
You're sweet!
That light again!
Look at it!
My light will guide us towards the others.
Hm?
Don't look at me, but I
think it's like this night light
I used to have that guided
me towards the bathroom!
Oh!
Well, Kari, I hope your light doesn't run
out of batteries!
Hm...
I'll lead the way.
Follow me!
Well, you see, Lord Machine German,
it's actually a pretty funny story!
Stop stalling and tell me what happened,
Waru Manziman.
That is, while you are still able to talk.
Yes, your middle-ness!
You see, I found the Digi Destin!
They were in your area!
Yes, and I was going to capture them for
you too, but this one little girl was
really strong, and then the new one were
biting me and it was really bad!
Enough!
If you thought that puny little girl was
tough, wait till I get through with you.
Why didn't you alert me, you stupid
carnival prize?
I wanted to tell you sooner, but they
wounded me!
Look at my owies and boo-boos!
I'm sorry, I should be more sympathetic
after your grueling battle.
Let me reward you for helping me locate
the Digi Destined.
Hey!
He shot my paw!
Cory!
Agamon, what are you doing laying down at
a time like this?
Sorry, Ty.
I'll try to keep up.
You know, Ty, that's the fifth time he's
collapsed.
Call me crazy, but I think maybe we should
rest for a little while.
Hmm.
Cory!
That's right.
Just let our Digimon die.
Huh?
Oh, sorry guys.
It's just a figure of speech.
I'm pretty tired too, Ty.
Why don't we rest?
Then we can commence our search again.
Please don't provoke him, Izzy!
Don't you understand?
Kari's sick.
We have to find her.
I know that, Ty, but she's not here right
now.
That's my point!
We have to find her now!
Calm down, Ty.
I'm warning you, Ty.
You better stop giving us orders or else.
Or else what?
I didn't plan anything after or else.
I just thought it sounded tough.
You want to see tough?
Here's tough!
Izzy, did you hear that?
Huh?
Just listen.
Getting closer.
Footsteps.
All I hear is my head pounding.
Someone's here.
You think he's been following us?
Maybe.
Let's pretend to keep fighting and we'll
hide behind that gate.
Okay, but just make sure your next
punch... is pretend too.
Better stop calling me names!
I will not!
You're a bully and a... a ruffian!
That's the best you could come up with?
Yes, on such short notice.
Take that!
Do you think it could be one of
Machinedramund's guys?
It's possible.
Should we?
Digivolve?
Yes.
Not a bad idea.
Systemon!
Digivolve 2!
Kaboom!
Never mind!
Abumon!
Digivolve 2!
Robot!
Abumon,
your Digivolve was a digi-dud.
Your energy levels are too low.
Izzy, I'm sorry.
It's okay, Ty.
I know your original intention wasn't to
punch me.
You were worried about Kari, that's all.
What's fair is fair.
I want you to hit me right now.
That's ridiculous!
I won't resort to that.
Nothing can be settled with violence.
I'm not gonna hit you, Ty.
Can I hit you then?
I wouldn't mind to swipe myself.
Okay.
I get it.
Here he comes!
Andromon!
I remember now!
We met Andromon on Fire Island.
He was the android Digimon who had a black
gear stuck in his mechanism, but we
removed it and freed him of its evil
spell.
I wasn't sure if it was you or not.
Well, it's nice to see a friendly face.
Even if it is made of metal.
What are you doing down here anyway,
Andromon?
And why are you sneaking up on people?
I'm trying to put together a resistance
army against Machinedramon.
I've heard rumors that Digimon are hiding
in the sewers.
They fled here when Machinedramon burned
the cities.
I've come to the sewers to organize them.
And while I'm here, I'm going to fix that
drip.
I thought you were spies sent here by
Machinedramon to destroy my plans.
How insulting!
I'm sorry.
Kari?
We're looking for my little sister named
Kari.
She's sick.
Have you seen her?
Sora, Biomon, TK, and Panamon are probably
with her too.
You mean... Queen Kari is your sister?
Queen?
Wait just a moment!
They're coming!
Kari and the others are coming here?
When?
Now!
Really?
Prodigis, Andromon!
Oh good.
Just what I was looking for.
Victims.
Machinedramon!
Hello, Andromon.
Babysitting?
I'll destroy you first while the others
watch.
I'll hold him off.
You hide!
Careful!
Andromon!
What is it, Kari?
They're coming.
You mean die?
When?
Now!
Machinedramon!
Sora, TK!
Kari!
She made it!
Was that Andromon I saw fighting with
Machinedramon?
That's him all right.
He's sacrificing himself to protect us.
Oh!
He's raising an army against
Machinedramon!
Dragonfire!
Are you all right, Andromon?
Yes, thank you.
We'll take you to safety.
No!
Let's fight Machinedramon together!
Meteor away!
The Celestial Arrow!
End of fate!
Machinedramon's a megadigimon!
They can't win!
Gigacannon!
They weren't even worth my time.
You're next!
Who wants to be the first victim?
Kari!
How brave you are to volunteer.
I'll try to make this as painful as I can.
What do you think you are doing,
Noomomon?
Do you slightly digimon call this
fighting?
Noomomon!
Gigacannon!
Oh, Noomomon!
Uh!
Oh!
I feel the power!
Gigimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
What?
Dwarf!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Wargreymon!
Digimon, digital monsters, Digimon.
Wake up!
We'll
finish you once and for all.
I don't think so.
You missed what I did as Wargreymon.
I sliced you like an onion.
Without Mashidramon, this area has become
unstable.
It's beginning to fall apart.
Nothing can happen to us that we can't
handle together.
Right.
I think it's becoming a little too
dangerous.
We better get out of here.
You're right.
Let's go.
Mashidramon City is dissolving.
My work here is finished.
Farewell, Andramon.
Thank you.
When we get down, can I build one of those
memorials to my friend, the Numomon?
Sure.
We'll all help build it.
Right, guys?
Yeah.
You're next, Piedmon.
Will the Digidestined be able to defeat
the most powerful Dark Master of all?
Find out their fate on the next Digimon
Digital Monsters.