DemiDevimon tricked Izzy and made him fall
into Vedamon's universe.
Convincing Izzy to
give up his curiosity,
Vedamon turned him
into a total-like zombie.
To make things worse, that Brainhead got
hold of his tag and crest.
Tentomon got so bummed out that he
de-digivolved to Pabumon.
Thankfully, Izzy finally
snapped out of it, and
with Pabumon's help,
got back the tag and crest.
Pabumon digivolved to Mega Kabuterimon and
sent Vedamon clear into another dimension.
Ha!
Later, Brainhead!
Digimon!
Digital monsters, Digimon are the
champions!
Change into digital champions to save the
digital world!
Digimon!
Digital monsters, Digimon are the
champions!
Digimon!
Digital monsters, Digimon are the
champions!
Digimon!
Digital monsters, Digimon are the
champions!
Digimon!
Digital monsters, Digimon!
Hey, what's wrong, you guys?
Can't you make this bucket go any faster?
What are you doing to help?
Watching for icebergs?
We'd gladly trade places with you,
but...
Unfortunately, our little legs won't reach
the pedals.
Hey, we could go faster if we threw you
off.
You wouldn't.
It's tempting.
Better not.
Wow, that palace is huge.
And way up there, as if my legs weren't
tired already.
But there's no doubt about it.
That is Mimi.
So up we go.
How do they get their mail?
All right, you know the drill.
What are you talking about?
Get out of my way!
Is this a palace?
Or some kind of a loony bin?
Seems like it's both.
Unless she's getting angry!
Oh, these are Geckomon?
I've heard of them.
They really love music.
Not surprising since they're born with
those horns.
Hurry!
Before she blows her tongue!
And I've heard of the other Digimon.
They're called Otamomon!
Hurry!
Can you help us?
We're looking for someone.
What time you got here?
Where's the triple hot fight sundae we
ordered for delivery to the princess?
That's not us!
Then you must be
delivering her bacon chili
cheeseburger with fries
and a super-sized milkshake!
That's not us either!
Of course not!
They're delivering the garden fresh salad
with little fat dressing without dessert!
We'd like to ask a question if you don't
mind.
Her highness asked for a fight sundae!
No!
She wants a bacon chili cheeseburger!
Excuse me!
She said she wanted a green salad!
Hey, excuse me!
Have you seen a girl in a hat?
We're ordering lunch here!
Well, then I'll have a burger!
All the princess really cares about is
that polka dot party dress she ordered!
Old news!
Now she wants pink leather pants with
matching boots and accessories!
No one told me that!
Oh, get with the program!
That's not my problem!
You're making it my problem!
It sounds to me like this princess of
theirs is extremely picky.
She sounds kind of spoiled if you ask me.
I wonder what happens if they don't do
what she says!
No!
Here she comes!
Presenting!
Her highness!
The princess!
Cool!
We're gonna get to meet the princess!
Huh?
It's Mimi!
Oh, bummer!
Huh?
What a surprise!
You're telling me!
What are you doing up there?
What do you think?
I'm being a princess, of course!
So you're the spoiled princess we've been
hearing about!
We should've known it was Mimi!
Don't call me Mimi anymore!
That's princess now!
Don't you worry, almighty wickedness!
This time we cannot fail!
We?
You'd better not fail!
It's in the bag!
Piece of cake!
Is the plan at the palace working?
Couldn't be better!
The Gekkomon are spoiling her rotten and
she's eating it up!
If she keeps this up much longer, her crest
of sincerity's gonna be useless, master!
Do you know what will happen if you
disappoint me again, Demidevamon?
I got a big idea!
Good.
Then see that you don't.
Well, the important thing is that you're
alright.
Yeah, that's for sure.
Well, come on.
Let's get a move on.
No way!
Right.
You want to change first.
We'll wait.
For what?
I'm keeping this dress on.
And it's beautiful, but it's not the best
thing to wear to walk long distances.
Walking?
I have no intention of walking anywhere.
Are you expecting us to carry you out of
here, your majesty?
No, I'm not going.
Huh?
Why would I leave?
I am a princess here.
Besides, who knows if we'll ever find our
way home.
So I might as well live large and in
charge.
You must be kidding.
No way!
Take a look around.
I've got a nice bed, pretty clothes,
food.
It's like having a birthday every day.
I am a princess.
And you want me to give this up?
I don't think so.
Is something wrong?
Another servant?
No, it's Palma.
And finally, a voice of reason.
Palma, come talk some sense into Mimi.
As in princess?
Oh no!
Not you too!
Uh-huh.
Okay, that's enough.
This is no time for playing games.
Both of you change out of those dumb
clothes and let's get out of here.
I am not playing a game, Ty.
I'm staying.
You can go any time.
Why don't you guys go look for the others?
Be gone from my palace!
Wait, Mimi.
Don't be mean.
They're our friends.
If you want to go, be my guest.
You are coming with us.
Get down off that high horse of yours and
shift your rear into high gear.
Yeah, come on.
Why do you think we almost killed
ourselves trying to find you?
Cause you were part of the team.
That's very nice, but I am not going.
That's it, Mimi.
Like it or not, Joe's right.
We've got to stick together.
So I'm not budging from this spot until
you come to your senses and leave with us.
Yeah!
Right!
Really?
You all keep forgetting who's in charge
around here.
Your Highness, what is it that you desire?
I desire these rude and bothersome peasants
to be removed from my boudoir at once.
Yes, Princess!
Hey!
Stop pushing!
I can't get your little frog hands off of
me!
Look out!
Oh, Mimi.
I won't dissect frogs in biology,
Kay!
If that's the way you treat your guests,
we're never coming back.
Now what are we going to do?
She's totally into this digi fairy tale.
I wonder what she could have done to get
them to wait on her hand and foot like this.
You really want to know?
Huh?
Uh, sure.
You're not taking us to an evil Digimon,
are you?
What if Mimi catches us?
She won't!
Here's our master, Lord Shogun-man!
Whoa!
Somebody's had a few too many donuts!
Is it a statue or what?
No, it's not a statue.
He's very much alive.
Huh?
He may be alive, but he's not lively,
is he?
He's sleeping!
He's been this way for over 300 years!
You see, Lord Shogun-man was proud of his
voice and ended his singing contest, but.
..
He lost!
He felt so bad, he fell into a deep sleep
from which he's never recovered!
It said only a voice as beautiful as the
one that beat him can wake him!
For centuries we've tried, but every
song's failed!
We Gekko-man love music,
but unfortunately not one
of us has a voice that would
be considered beautiful!
Then we got a break!
A strange little Digimon spoke of a girl
with a pretty voice.
He told us where to find her and we did!
I want to sing a song!
A song that'll wake you up!
And when you hear my voice, you'll call me
a sweet buttercup!
Whoa!
Just give me a listen!
Wow!
You mean all this is for me?
Maybe this will help you remember the
words.
I want to sing a song!
A song that will wake you up!
When you hear my voice, you'll call me!
Hmm... About we get a disco
ball and some spotlights, huh?
And of course, we'll need hair,
makeup, and costumes!
Oh, I'm tired!
Let's pick it up tomorrow!
And that's the way it's been!
One excuse after another!
We've done all she's wanted!
We've even redecorated the entire palace
for her!
I used to like Pink, but now I can't stand
to look at it!
And if any one of us
complains to her... Whoa!
Be careful!
You wouldn't want me to lose my voice now,
would you?
So we're in a terrible position,
you see?
We're totally helpless!
Unfortunately, you've given Mimi the life
she's been accustomed to, and then some!
Well, that you're friends of hers!
Could you please reason with her,
please?
We'd be so eternally grateful!
I don't think she knows what reason is!
Just leave it to me, guys!
I've got it!
Huh?
I knew it!
I knew you'd come through!
Yay!
What are you thinking, Ty?
Well, who says you need Mimi to wake up
Jumbo?
Crank it up and let me take a shot!
You?
What you laughing at?
I'm gonna sing a song!
A song that will wake you up!
I'm gonna belt it out!
Sugar and Ma, it's time to get out!
Hey, wake up!
I'm
attaching to sing a song!
A song that will waken you and aid all the
Gecko mom!
That are loyal to your world view,
and the idea of you being in charge!
I'm attaching to sing a song!
A song that will wake you and aid all the
Gecko mom!
I Mario this song to you!
A tune from now until June!
When you hear us sing, you'll call us
singing baboons!
Boons!
We just want to wake ya!
So don't close your ears!
Or you can sleep for years!
It's no use.
After that, he might not wake up for
another 300 years.
Hey guys!
Palma, why did you all disappear like
that?
It's like you weren't even happy to see
us.
What are you talking about?
In case you hadn't noticed, Mimi's gone
nuts.
Yeah?
Hmm.
Now that I think of it, she has kind of
gone off the deep end.
I mean, even for her.
Oh, you noticed?
You're so observant.
So, she'll be performing and won't even
know it.
Yeah, and we'll get the whole thing on
tape.
Watch it!
What's this?
It's a karaoke set.
Yes, I can see that.
But what's it doing in my royal chambers?
I just love hearing you sing!
I thought you might give us a private
concert!
Here!
Hmm... Thanks!
You're the greatest!
Now, feel the music!
Feel the music!
Ty, is she falling for it?
Huh?
What's that chord for?
I see...
So, you thought you could put a fast one
on Princess Mimi, did you?
That's Princess Mimi!
Yeah!
Who do you think you are, anyway?
Don't you remember we're your friends?
I remember you tried to trick me.
We tried to trick you because we're trying
to save you.
Have you completely forgotten about the
Crest of Sincerity?
Have you completely forgotten it's not
nice to lock people up in your dungeon?
Where's your manners?
Wait!
Uh... Before you go, I have
something I want to tell you.
Nobody likes you more than I do.
It hurts me deeply to have to say
this, but... You're a spoiled brat!
Oh!
Is that a fact?
Hmph!
What can I do?
Oh!
Sorry!
Big deal!
You didn't sing even when we did what you
wanted!
You're on your own!
Wait!
Don't leave me!
I'll sing for you!
I promise!
Help me, please!
Sorry, but we only help our friends!
What's wrong, Mimi?
Well, what's the matter?
I thought you were ahead of the time of
your life.
Helmon!
I've gotta go now, Mimi!
Goodbye!
Oh!
Won't anybody help me?
Please!
Helmon!
Don't leave me!
Hey!
Hey, Mimi!
Where am I?
What?
Do you have any idea what that horrible
dream was trying to tell you, Mimi?
I'm sorry!
Oh, I really am!
Well, then you know what you have to do to
make things right.
Yes.
That a girl!
I knew you'd find yourself again!
Zora?
What now?
The princess wants you!
Is she gonna chop off our heads?
Don't even joke.
What's going on?
What's she up to?
First of all, there's something I have to
say to everyone here.
Ty and Joe, Agamon and Gomamon,
Palmon, all of you have been so nice.
I'm so sorry.
What does he say?
I've been such a little idiot.
If you could find it in your hearts to
forgive me, and I don't know why you
would, but if you can, then I'd be honored
to sing for you one more time.
We forgive you.
Of course we do sing, your highness!
Yay!
Yes!
Thank you!
Hit the lights and cue the music!
I
wanna sing a song A song to bring
Shogunmon around When he hears my voice I
hope he likes the sound He has to listen
Listen to my sincere heart I've learned
that friends are friends
Even when they're apart My
friends do forgive me from
the bottom of my heart Yes!
If it's my choice, his eyes will open
We'll be cheering Cheering
with pride Don't panic!
It's our lord and master Shogunmon Finally
restored to us after so many centuries I
was having such a nice sleep Which one of
you clowns woke me up?
Or should I just squish all of you?
Women and Yakuman first!
And I thought I was
cranky when I first wake
up Give me the main
meaning back any day!
Whose idea was this?
Remind me never to listen to them again!
You wanna hear some singing?
The ground will shake When you hear the
noise I make Because I'm glad to be awake
Yeah!
Whoa And you are You
know where is your arms you?
That old Mimi's back.
Really?
You mean it?
Then let's take care of this out-of-tune
goon.
Hey, you!
How about some gratitude?
I saved you out of your 300-year nap,
you wannabe crooner!
Oh, that racket?
It was you?
Uh-oh.
Oh, have you come to play?
Loverplay!
Hartpool Torpedo!
Now it's zoo time!
Now why'd you try that?
Cause I'll knock you flat!
And now you're gonna feel it!
Did you see that?
Yeah, he gives new meaning to the term
flat note.
Watch out below!
Do it!
What is it?
He deserved to hear that last flat note,
don't you think?
Well, ready to go, Mimi?
Yeah, do you think I can take some of my
princess clothes with me?
Mimi!
Well, it just seems such a waste,
the jewels at least.
Didn't you say you knew it would happen if
you failed?
Well, when I said I
knew, I didn't really
mean that I knew knew,
you know what I mean?
But now that I do know
if it's not to my trouble,
sir, can I bother you
for a glass of water?
Yeah.