TK and I were looking for
Patamon in the city when we ran
into two of Myotismon's henchmen,
Pumpkinmon and Gatsumon.
They were supposed to be
searching for the Eighth Child,
but all they wanted to do
was act silly and cause trouble.
Myotismon showed up and didn't like their
attitude.
He blasted them back to the Digi-World,
then turned on us.
Where Garurumon put up a good fight,
but it wasn't enough.
Luckily, Patamon found us and Digivolved
into Anjimon.
Batforbrains took off, but I'm sure he'll
return soon, and he won't be happy.
Of course, he's never happy.
Digimon, Digimon monsters, Digimon are the
champions.
Digimon, Digimon guns.
Change into digital champions to save the
digital world.
Digimon, Digimon monsters.
Home!
Ty, you're late.
I'll get it.
Hello?
Kamiya residence?
Yeah, Joe.
So did you find the Eighth Digi-Destined
Kid yet?
No.
I didn't have any luck.
There weren't any other students who moved
from Heightened View Terrace.
But that can't be right.
There must be someone else.
Well, whoever it is, they weren't in my
address book.
Check your own book before you start
yelling at me.
Oh, that's right.
What did I do with my book anyway?
Uh... You still
haven't found it?
Oh, great.
It's only the future of the world
depending on you.
I'll find it.
What are you doing?
I'm trying to find my address book.
Miko, Ty's room is messier than your
litter box.
If Kari really is the Eighth Digi-Destined
Child, then I have to destroy her.
But every time I see her, I get this
strange sensation.
I still don't understand why I wasn't able
to attack her when I have a chance.
Come here.
Are you going already?
What happened?
I could have stopped
the Digi-Destined once
and for all, but something
was pulling me away.
Look at that little pet cat over there.
She's got it so easy.
She gets fed gourmet food out of a can.
Then she gets to chase a sock all day.
Talk about a perfect life.
Nobody was nice to me like that when I was
growing up.
Nobody was nice, period.
Back when I was Salomon, I was a slave to
the evil Myotismon.
Every time you look at me with those eyes,
I'll have to hurt you.
I couldn't understand it.
I guess he just didn't like my eyes.
This is one of the scars that Myotismon
gave me just because I have these eyes.
It's not my fault.
I wish I could remember where I was born.
I have no idea what I did before I met
Myotismon.
My past is a blur.
Thinking about the good old days?
I'm not gonna tell you again, Wizardmon.
Don't read my thoughts without my
permission.
I'm sorry, Gatomon.
Please forgive me.
And shouldn't you be out looking for the
Eighth Digidestined Human?
Yes, I'll get right on it.
Still, no reaction from the crest.
It's reacting.
I wonder what's causing it.
The Digivice Thunderbomb!
Hey, Wizardmon!
Whatcha doin' over there?
Uh, nothing.
It's hard to believe you came all the way
out here to do nothing.
Come on, tell me what you found!
All right, but if I show you, you have to
promise not to tell anyone.
Come on, show me!
All right, it's a bottle of green chili
sauce.
It's great on tacos.
What are you doing eating on the job when
there's work to be done?
You should be looking for the Eighth
Digidestined Child like the others!
Please don't tell Lord Myotismon.
Why don't you get rid of this for me?
All right, boy, you know what I hope?
I hope that the all-night drag-through is
still open!
There's no way I'm handing this over to
Demi Devimon.
He'll take all the credit for himself.
But wait, if the Digivice is here,
where is the Eighth Child hiding there?
Both horses were reported to be in stable
condition.
Now back to our top story.
Several more strange
monsters have been sighted
earlier today in and
around the Tokyo area.
In the same community, there
have been more reports of young
girls being struck down by
what doctors call sudden anemia.
Investigators say these incidents may be
related.
Now on to the weather.
Sudden anemia?
Ty!
I'll get it!
Hello?
Ty?
Oh, hi, Matt.
Did you just see the news?
I didn't have to see it, because I was
there.
We just got back from the city.
You did?
So that report on television
about the monsters was... Right!
It was Myotismon.
And was he on the warpath?
He even got rid of two of his own flunks!
What?
Ty, we don't know how much time we've got
left.
I'm telling you, we've got to hurry up and
find the Eighth Child.
Myotismon will mangle him.
I mean, if he finds him before we do.
Wizardmon, what is it now?
Go away before I use you as my scratching
post.
Sorry to disturb you again,
Godamon, but... But what?
The Digivice!
Where'd you get it?
I found it in a crow's nest in the Iraqi
woods.
Then the Eighth Digidustin must be
somewhere near there.
No, the Eighth Child
is... Tell me right now!
Well, you see, Godamon... What?
I wonder if the location of the child is
in somewhere inside your own heart.
What are you saying?
I believe that long ago, you buried away
an important part of yourself.
And somewhere deep
inside your heart lies the key
to the identity of the
Eighth Digidustin child.
Try to remember.
Hmm... What's holding you back?
Could it be you're afraid of what you
might find?
You can get your lost memories back,
Godamon.
You could remember your past without fear.
End your long nightmare and try to
remember.
Just leave me alone!
Who sent you here, Myotismon?
Myotismon has nothing to do with this.
I fight by your side, not his.
I tell you these things now, because you
are my friend.
Before I met you, I was always alone.
I was constantly traveling, never stopping
to make any friends.
Then one day, I fell from the sky and
crashed.
But no one stopped to help me.
I thought I was a Godamon until you came.
Here, drink this.
Looks like he passed out.
Ah, you're awake.
Huh?
Did you save me?
I didn't do that much.
I just couldn't leave you lying there.
Well, thanks.
I guess I'll be going now.
Don't be silly.
You're not strong enough to go.
I know you helped me, but I don't have
anything for you.
I don't want anything, but you must be
very lonely to say that.
What do you mean?
When you've been alone for a long time,
your heart becomes very hard.
It happens to everyone, you know.
Even me.
I don't remember any of that.
Well, that's how it happened.
I thought you saved me because you wanted
something in return.
I couldn't understand
the concept of compassion
because loneliness
had hardened my heart.
But you taught me that all creatures have
good inside of them.
That's when you told me your secret.
My whole life, I just keep waiting and
searching, but I never find her.
Find who?
Who are you waiting and searching for?
I can't remember.
It was too long ago.
All I know is I'm waiting for someone.
Waiting?
Me?
That's what you told me.
Why can't I remember who I was waiting
for?
Who could it possibly be?
Huh?
Miko!
Where do you think you're going?
You can't come out here at this hour.
Go back inside.
Good kitty.
Hmm.
I think perhaps your search is finally
over.
Huh?
Who are you?
Wizard Ma.
How are you able to fly like that?
Oh, well... Huh?
Oh, it's you.
Hello again.
You're Agumon's friend, aren't you?
How come you ran away last time I saw you?
What's that thing?
Can I see it?
Wizard Ma, tell me, is this girl the 8th
Digi Destined?
Yes!
Well, then who is her Digimon?
I think you know.
You were waiting for someone.
Try to remember.
Hold on, my memory is starting to come
back.
Yes, I was definitely waiting for someone.
Ever since I was Niarramon, I was so
lonely.
Every day I just kept waiting and waiting.
The seasons changed
and the years rolled by
and still I kept waiting,
but no one ever came.
Then when I became Salomon, I started
searching.
I went on a journey,
but what I finally found
was not the someone
I had been waiting for.
Instead, I found evil and darkness.
My Otis Man.
Then those days of torture and despair
began and I started to forget.
Forget that I was waiting for someone,
searching for someone.
Well, what are you guys talking about?
What does any of this have to do with me?
Someone's out there talking to Kari.
Huh?
Kari, get away!
What's the matter, Ty?
What do you Digimon want?
Wait, listen to what I have to say.
Kari, you get over here.
Those two are evil Digimon.
No, they're not evil.
Gatomon has been searching for me.
For me and the eighth Digi-destined child.
Watch out!
Kari, are you okay?
Oh no, Gatomon!
Gatomon!
You alright?
I'm fine.
This is nothing compared to what I've been
through.
Did you see that?
Gatomon saved Kari.
Now that you remember, do you understand?
Yes.
I was waiting for the Digi-destined human
I belonged with.
That's you, Kari.
You're the eighth Digi-destined.
You were waiting just for me?
I've been searching forever and ever for
you.
You could have just called.
Guess what, Ty?
Gatomon's my Digimon.
Now I've got one, too.
Don't be silly, Kari.
That doesn't make sense.
It makes perfect sense, considering she's
the eighth Digi-destined.
That's right, and I'm her Digimon.
No matter what happens, I'll always
protect her.
Well, then why are you a part of
Myotismon's army?
And just who is this guy?
He's called Wizardmon.
He put himself in great danger to bring me
this Digivice.
He's my friend.
But how do I know if I can trust him or
not?
Frankly, I don't care whether
you trust me or not, but
I'm going to follow Gatomon
as long as she needs me.
Here, you take the device.
Why give it to Ty?
It belongs to Kari.
She can't be seen with it.
If Myotismon finds out she's the eighth
child, and Gatomon is her Digimon,
then he'll destroy Gatomon, and he won't
rest until he finds Kari.
If you have the Digivice, then their
secret will be safe.
Okay, I'll take it, but you better not be
double-crossing us.
What's next?
Your sister needs her crest.
The real one.
The real one?
This crest is just a copy that was created
to find the Digivice.
Myotismon is the only one with access to
the real crest.
We've got to get it back.
Leave everything to us.
Wait!
Where's Myotismon's hideout?
We'll come with you, and we can help you.
No, it's too dangerous.
Be careful, Gatomon!
Can we trust them?
We have to.
We have no choice.
Myotismon has to be keeping Kari's crest
somewhere in the hideout.
I think we have to search his room.
Stop!
Myotismon is feeding upon the night.
He said no one may enter until he returns
at dawn.
Ah, forget about it.
As a matter of fact, Thunderbolt!
Go!
I can't remember a thing.
What were we talking about?
We were leaving you of guard duty.
Go home and get some sleep.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
See ya.
Hold it.
Don't forget to leave us the key.
Huh?
Oh, the key.
Here.
Thank you.
What a nice guy.
Let's go.
Hurry up, Wizardmon.
Let's find the crest and cruise on out of
here.
This place gives me the creeps.
Relax.
We've got plenty of time before the sun
comes up.
Myotismon won't be back for hours.
Maybe he keeps it in the coffin.
Great.
Now let's just get out of here.
Huh?
Uh-oh.
What are you doing in here?
Nothing.
If you're looking for something,
maybe I can assist you.
Another copy.
Do you think I'd just leave the original
lying around for thieves like you?
Wizardmon.
I'm all right.
Those eyes.
From the first time you looked at me with
those eyes, I knew you'd turn against me.
And that's why I had to teach you by
punishing you.
I would have hurt you even more when you
became a good servant.
But I promise you I will not be so easy on
you this time.
And do you think your betrayal will go
unpunished, Wizardmon?
How could I betray you when I was never on
your side to begin with?
You little fool.
Grizzly wing!
We really have to stay together.
Those who play together lose together.
I'm not afraid.
You soon will be, you pathetic little
traitor.
Magical game!
Grizzly wing!
Look there!
Up in the sky!
Wizardmon and Gatomon are in a fight!
Oh no.
I hope they're not being hurt.
Whoa!
Let's go!
What?
Wait up!
I wanna go too!
I can't risk you getting hurt.
Wait here!
I hope
you realize there's no safe place to hide
during this lightning storm!
Ha!
Magical game!
Crimson lightning!
I'll do away with you first, Wizardmon!
Hey!
Why don't you pick on somebody one-tenth
your size?
There are those eyes again.
And this time, not
only are they filled with
rebellion, but I can also
see a glimmer of hope.
The hope that one day your dreams will
come true.
That's right!
I believe in my dreams, and that's how
I've made it this far!
And just what have you really achieved?
You believe in your worthless friends.
And you believe that your dreams can come
true.
Dreams do not exist for the stupid!
If you believe in yourself, then dreams
are real.
And to make my dreams come true,
I only have to do one thing.
Defeat you!
What?
My dream is for me to return to my true
identity, the one I had before I met you.
What do you mean, true identity?
Could it be that...
Are you the eighth Digimon?
This changes everything!
Before I crush you, I'll
give you the pleasure
of watching me destroy
your wizard friend first!
Fizzly Weed!
Whoa!
No!
My friend!
We've come to help you, Gatoman!
Kai!
Quick, get out of the way!
Nova Black!
When will you digi-destined ever learn?
Crimson Lightning!
Greymon Digivolve!
Tell Greymon!
Boys and girls, hey Digimon, hey Digimon!
Giga Blaster!
You impudent fool!
Did you really think you could beat me
with those pathetic little toys of yours?
Agumon!
Oh, I wonder what's taking them so long.
Come back, Gatoman.
I couldn't stand it if anything happened
to you.
But I'm sure Tai and Agumon will take good
care of you.
Nice try, buddy!
If the Digi-destined are
coming to defend Gatoman,
then they really must think
she is the eighth Digimon!
Hey, what they think is no business of
yours.
Go blow smoke somewhere else!
You will pay for your impudence!
Just what do you mean?
Huh?
I hope you like fishing, Gatoman!
Because you're going to be the perfect bait
to lure out the eighth Digi-destined child!
Now I don't need the crest to find that
cowardly, puny human!
That's not fair, Myotismon!
I don't play fair!
Stop!
Gatoman!
Tai, help me!
Will Tai rescue Gatoman before Myotismon
finds Kari?
Tune in to the next Digimon Digital
Monsters!