Determined to find the Eighth
Chosen One, Gatomon went
through the gate to the real
world just as it slammed shut.
Jedi appeared and led us
to his house inside the lake,
where he gave us these
awesome Digimon key cards.
Only he didn't tell us how to use the
things.
Back at the castle, just as the whole
place was totally blowing up around us,
Izzy figured out how to open the gate.
We got through right before Dokukuman
would have made us into lunch meat.
Now we're back home again, only this time
we've got a serious mission.
Find the Eighth Child and save him from
Gatomon, or else!
We're back at camp where we started!
We've got to get to
Heightenview Terrace and stop
Myotismon before he finds
the Eighth Digi-destined.
I wonder how much of a head start he has
on us.
Not even a minute has
passed between the time
Myotismon left for Japan
and when we arrived.
Time flows at a different pace in the
Digi-world.
I'll say we've been gone
for months in the Digi-world,
and yet here in the real
world it's the same day we left.
But that's impossible!
You mean all those adventures took less
time than it does to say, get a haircut?
Please, Joe, don't exaggerate!
Imagine getting your hair done in such a
short amount of time!
I'm going to go take a look at the camp.
I want to see for myself how much time has
really passed.
One of you come with me, the rest of you
stay there.
Who volunteers?
Hmm?
One volunteer, not thirteen.
I thought I'd keep you company.
And we're going to keep Mimi company.
I guess we're all pretty curious to find
out what happened while we were gone.
But how will we explain it if somebody
sees our Digimon?
Oh, kids!
Huh?
It's... our teacher!
Our kids!
Huh?
It's our teacher!
We are back in the real world!
Mr. Fujiyama!
Watch out!
What are all of you kids
doing playing around here
when you haven't even
packed up your gear yet?
Well, sir, I can explain!
Well, I'm Ty's Digimon!
Didn't you kids hear that we're closing up
camp early because of the snow?
Everyone else is all ready to go home.
Sure, of course we heard.
Look at those dirty little toys you're
carrying.
Where'd you get them?
Uh, toys?
Who's he calling a dirty little toy?
That's not... You can't let
anyone know you can talk.
Pretend they'd be stuffed animals.
Oh, these toys!
Well, you see, they're stuffed.
Yes, Ty.
I can see that.
Oh, we found them here.
Yeah, that's right.
You see, we were hiking up
an uncharted trail when we came
across these stuffed toys
that someone had thrown away.
Makes perfect sense if you ask me.
Who in their right mind
would hike up an uncharted
trail just to throw away
seven stuffed animals?
Exactly our point.
And that's why we think that littering is
crazy.
Right, gang?
Right!
But being the good citizens that we are,
we cleaned up the mess and now I'm giving
the toys to my little sister Kari as a
present.
She wasn't able to come to camp,
remember?
Oh, yeah.
She caught a cold, didn't she?
Yes, but she's feeling much better now
because I went home and made her an omelette.
When did you do that?
When I... When?
That's a good question.
Right before I left for camp.
It's nice that you're thinking of your
sister, Ty.
But don't overdo it.
Those toys are filthy and belong in the
garbage.
Right, kids?
Right.
I'll meet you at the bus.
Yay!
I'd like to get his gear together and
throw him in the garbage can.
Well, you won't be littering at least.
The human world is so cluttered.
All these creatures crammed on top of each
other.
The ape that diddesken lives nearby.
What's next, Myotismon?
Unfortunately, until the sun goes down,
I must remain hidden in the shadows.
Begin the search without me.
Here.
I won't let you down, Lord Myotismon.
I need to be alone.
I'll come with you.
Remember, don't talk in front of anyone
else, okay?
Don't worry.
We can just pretend to be adorable stuffed
animals.
Ah.
Wow, look at all the kids.
Didn't we just say not to talk out loud?
Yeah, but look at all the human children.
We never knew there were more human
children than you.
This is nothing.
Why, just in the city alone, there must be
tens of thousands of kids just like us.
And when you add the rest of the kids in
the world, there must be millions.
Huh?
You mean there are millions of soras?
There's only one of me.
She just means there
are more kids our age, but
there are tons of different
people in the world.
Wow.
Hey, it's Michelle.
I've missed you so much.
You missed me.
You just saw me ten minutes ago.
What's going on?
Mimi's weird.
Hey!
She's bleeding out.
Too much caffeine.
Oh, Mimi.
She'll give us away.
I told her no time has passed since we
went to the Digi-World.
Forget Mimi.
We have to find some form of
transportation to heighten View Terrace.
I've got an idea.
Mr. Fujiyama.
Hmm?
Can you have the bus drop us off
somewhere?
Have the bus drop you off?
No can do.
The rules say I have to take you straight
to your homes.
Please, Mr. Fujiyama, I'm begging you,
sir.
Could you just let us off somewhere near
heighten View Terrace?
Heighten View Terrace?
Why do you want to go there?
Well, we used to live
there and we were feeling
nostalgic so we thought
we'd visit our old hangout.
Hmm?
We'd appreciate it, sir.
But it's against the rules.
You know, I think we drive pretty close to
heighten View Terrace.
Let's see.
First, we take the freeway to the parkway
to the throughway and...
Oh, that's the wrong way.
Oh, yeah.
Here at the roadway, heighten View Terrace
is within walking distance.
Mm-hmm.
Great.
Then that's where you can let us off,
mister.
Hold on.
I didn't give the bus driver permission
yet.
Please, Mr. Fujiyama.
You'll break D.K.'s heart if you don't let
us go.
It was the last place we all lived together
as a family before my parents got divorced.
D.K.
Oh, brother.
Mr. Fujiyama, please let us off at
heighten View Terrace.
As an upperclassman, I'll take
responsibility for getting them home.
Well, I guess if a reliable kid like you
is going, Joe, then it's okay.
However, call your parents and tell them
where you are.
Deal.
Thanks, Mr. Fujiyama.
You're the greatest teacher ever.
Yeah, yeah.
Yahoo!
Hey, how long are you gonna keep that act
up?
Hey, if we didn't come
up with something sappy
like that, he never
would have let us go.
You mean that sad story was just an act?
I was crying my eyes out so much for you
guys that my glasses started to fog up.
Joe, calm down before you have an asthma
attack.
I missed all of you so much.
I hope she's not gonna act this way with
every kid that she meets.
Hey!
Excellent.
My laptop is in perfect working condition
here in the real world.
Great.
Looks like the digivice is working too.
Cool.
What's that?
Is that the latest toy all you kids are
into?
No, it's just one of the old ones that we
all hate.
Let me take a look at it.
Uh, it's broken.
Maybe I can fix it.
Here, give it to me.
I'm pretty good with electronics.
Yes, sir.
Thank you, Sara.
Unlike other children, you really listen
to your teachers.
No.
There's no harm in just letting him take a
look at it, Tai.
For about a second there, I thought Mr.
Fujiyama was an evil Digimon.
I think you've spent way too much time in
the Digi-world.
Think about it.
If he were an evil Digimon, every time you
failed a test, he'd scream out his attack,
Homework Blaster!
Actually, it's more like Tickle Blaster.
It's this way, guys.
You can't turn over a rock without finding
a kid under it.
I haven't found it in
this world, and yet I
still haven't found the
Eighth Digi-Destined.
What do you mean you couldn't find the
Eighth Digi-Destined?
You have failed me.
Please don't hurt me, your evil ship.
I swear he's not here.
Silence, Katomaj!
I have made several copies of the Eighth
Digi-Destined's Tag and Crest.
The one that you have is a copy,
too.
So, I'm a copycat?
The original's with me.
Even though they're
only copies, they will still
become activated when
the Eighth Child is nearby.
This time, make no mistakes.
You must find that child.
Gotcha!
And when you do find him, then he must
die!
They were nice to drop us off here.
Yeah!
There's the Heighten View Terrace Tower!
The tallest apartment building in Japan!
Terrific!
I'm afraid of heights.
That place isn't so hot!
That's true.
The heat never worked.
I used to live there.
Wow, Sora!
You lived in that big castle?
Yep.
I live near here, too.
A block away in another building.
Sora and I went to Westside Elementary
together.
Hey, I went to Westside Elementary!
You're kidding!
You mean that you guys
were telling the truth when
you said you used to live
in Heighten View Terrace?
Yeah, we really did live here before my
parents broke up.
That was a long time ago when I was a
little kid.
Strange coincidence, because I used to
live here, too.
I lived here, too, before we moved.
Huh?
Me, too.
Just for a little while.
It's a long story.
So at some point, we all lived at Heighten
View Terrace at the same exact time.
This can't just be a coincidence.
There's got to be some meaning here.
Huh?
My Otismon's army!
Run for it!
They can run, but they can't hide from
Mammothmon.
A new motorcycle!
Hey!
Respect other people's property,
you big walking shack carpet!
But you know there's a leash law around
here!
Oh, look, honey, how cute.
A wild elephant on the rampage.
They must be filming a movie or something.
What's that big-eared freak trying to do?
Destroy the Digi-Destined with everything
else, too?
We never should have brought that type of
Digimon along for this.
It's got an awful lot of trunk space!
My phone's dead!
Say, do any of you remember this place?
I bought candy here.
It was my favorite store.
Oh, sure, mine too.
You probably don't remember this place,
TK, because you were too little.
But Mom and Dad used to take us here all
the time.
Maybe some candy will help me to remember.
You're awfully quiet, Izzy.
Didn't you like living in Heightenview
Terrace?
I don't remember.
How long did you live there?
Just for a little while.
About six months.
Wow, why did your parents move away?
I don't know.
You're kidding.
Well, if you don't know, then maybe I
should tell you why.
What do you mean, Joe?
Yeah, Joe, how could you know why Izzy's
parents moved away from here?
Did you know them or something?
No, I didn't know Izzy back then,
but I did see what happened.
His whole family packed
up and left Heightenview
Terrace because of
a terrorist bombing.
Bombing?
Did you say terrorist?
Maybe you don't
remember it, but about four
years ago, this story
was in all the papers.
It was one of the worst terrorist attacks
of all time.
They never found the group responsible for
the bombings, so a lot of families got
scared thinking it could happen again and
moved out.
My parents figured it had just become too
dangerous to live here anymore,
so we moved out to Odaiba.
Now that you mention it, I do remember.
A lot of my friends moved away after that.
Now I remember.
My parents acted scared that whole time.
What's going on?
Where there's trouble, there's my Otismon!
A monster Digimon!
He's called Mammothmon.
He's a fully digivolved Digimon with the
strength of a woolly mammoth.
He shoots missiles he
calls Tusk Crusher and
has a chilling attack
called freezing breath.
Get out of here, kids!
This is Headquarters!
Can anyone there hear me?
Come in!
Emergency!
My radio's dead!
Wait a minute, I think he sees us!
Get out of here now!
And he's heading his way!
Huh?
That monster's fully digivolved,
you can't fight him!
Just leave everything to me!
Viumon!
Digimon!
Digimon are the champions!
Viumon!
Digibov 2!
Digimon are the champions!
Viumon!
There were two!
There were two monsters!
What are you talking about, TK?
Oh man, now I remember.
A long time ago, TK
was insisting that he saw
two monsters and my
mom was upset at him for it.
But I really did see monsters,
Mommy.
TK, there's no such thing as monsters.
You were just imagining it or maybe it was
a dream.
But Mommy, I saw them.
Now that's enough.
I don't want to hear any more of these
crazy stories.
I just assumed he imagined the entire
thing.
So when did all this take place?
It was right after the terrorist bombing.
This is where it happened.
Right on this footbridge.
Dust Crusher!
This is really strange.
Does anyone besides me feel like they can
remember the night of the bombing?
Sure do.
I feel like I was there, but somehow I
forgot.
Gee, that sounds like repressed memory.
We gotta get off this bridge!
I'm having deja vu all over again!
Meteor away!
This is just how it happened!
Back then, a giant ball of fire destroyed
the bridge!
Something is definitely different.
I remember the fire-breathing monster
didn't fly.
There had to be another one.
You're right.
There were two monsters fighting,
but they were different than these two.
NO BREATH!
Sora?
Digimon!
Dust Crusher!
The fire breathing monster I saw...
Greymon!
It was Greymon and another Digimon...
Zora!
It was Greymon!
Right!
Peace to the boys and girls!
It was the day Coromon came to my house
and Digi-volved into Greymon.
He was fighting with a bird-like Digimon.
After the fight, they disappeared.
Win play!
After the fight that day, Greymon and the
other Digimon disappeared.
And the police called the fight a
terrorist bombing.
Exactly.
Somehow the Digimon were involved all
along.
That's why my little sister already knew
Coromon.
Kari met him back on that day.
You met her?
It must have been a different Coromon.
But I did have a strange
feeling when I first
met Ty that we had
met somewhere before.
Listen, it's the cops.
They'll ask a ton of questions.
They'll blame us for all this.
I'm too young to go to the big house.
Stop running!
You know, I always thought it was kind of
strange that out of all the kids at camp,
we were the only ones chosen to go to the
Digi-world.
And I knew it couldn't just be
coincidence.
Somehow we were all connected by some
common event.
Today I discovered what that event was.
We all took French in school?
No.
Four years ago, we were all living at
Heightened View Terrace at the same time.
And all of us saw those two Digimon fight.
Then the Eighth Digidestin saw the Digimon
too.
Right, so the person who's the Eighth
Digidestin had to have been there as well.
What if Myotismon has found the kid
already?
I mean, he's been searching the city all
day.
And if the child lived here four years
ago, maybe it's still here.
I don't think so.
Mammothmon wouldn't be
making all this commotion if
they'd already found the
Eighth Digidestin child.
Myotismon is still searching.
I say the child is still out there.
Or maybe he moved like you guys.
We'll find him before Myotismon,
the Eighth Digidestin.
He might be someone we know.