Continuing on our quest, we had yet
another run in with Kawagapai.
Fortunately, the day was saved by a most
diminutive Digimon named Piximon,
a wise trainer.
His training methods at
first appeared a bit odd, but
later we found out it was
a form of self-discipline.
Matt and I went off to
find our own crests, and
we found them in a
most unexpected location.
Our nemesis, Edumon, must
have the entire area under
surveillance, because he
sent Taranumon to deal with us.
Hagumon took care of that dino with no
problem.
How prodigious!
Digital Monsters, Digimon are the
champions!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters, Digimon are the
champions!
Change into Digital Champions to save the
digital world!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters, Digimon are the
champions!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters, Digimon are the
champions!
What is it, Izzy?
Some kind of power generator?
Even better, Edimons
has hardwired the entire
desert, creating an
extensive computer network.
My guess, this is one of his remote data
access terminals.
Great, let's crash it.
It could be a booby trap.
If it is, Edimons, I say we cross the
wires and mess it up good.
What are you going to do with that?
I wonder.
It's entirely possible that our computer
have compatible systems.
And if they do, I can tap into Edimons'
network.
Hey, you have mail.
Oh, that was quick.
Who even knows I've logged on?
Oh, no, it's Edimons.
Open it, it's probably just spam.
Right.
Help me.
S-O-S.
Mayday.
I'm being held prisoner.
Help me escape and I'll guide you to the
quest you seek.
Whoa.
Do you think he's for real?
I mean, who could it be?
What do you mean the system's down?
I don't want to hear any excuses.
I want those stinking kids located now.
Yes, a mighty Edimons, sir.
Most majestic royal one.
The problem is, we've got a glitch at the
pyramid host computer.
Datamon.
Get me there in a hurry, you plop of your
little freaks.
Let's roll.
Oh, I don't like this.
I don't like it one little bit.
I don't like the look of it.
I don't like the smell of it.
I don't like the... You don't
have a brain cramp, Joe.
You're turning green around the edges.
Yeah, somebody asked for our help.
We've got to at least check it out,
right?
According to my laptop, we should be
getting close.
Hey, look!
It's glowing.
Oh!
Huh?
TK, come over here.
Look what I found.
Look!
Another crest!
Watch it!
Awesome!
My own crest!
Congratulations!
Now, TK, don't think this means you get to
stay up any later.
Sora's crest is the only one left to find.
Maybe if we rescue this guy, he can lead
us to it.
Well, what are we waiting for?
To the rescue!
Da-da-da-da-da-da!
What's that?
Huh?
See these hieroglyphs?
Look familiar.
This is definitely the same writing we've
come across before.
Wait a second.
This is a new one.
Oh!
Prodigious!
This is amazing!
Do you know what I'm thinking?
I've got a feeling you're going to tell
us.
Well, you see, it's quite
possible that these hieroglyphs
are not a form of writing
at all, but rather code.
Computer code.
If you change a piece of the code,
then you change the program.
Ah!
Like that, for example.
Wait.
Back up.
Are you telling us that this
whole place is some kind of
giant computer game and
that none of it is really real?
Oh, it's real, all right.
Huh?
You know, I'm thinking that everything we
see and everybody we meet in this place
are actually pieces of data or programming
given physical form.
Now, wait a second.
If you're writing this whole thing's one
big computer, then how did we get here?
Did we squeeze in through the floppy
drive?
No, we're just kilobytes of data,
too.
I mean, the versions of us that are in
here.
If I'm just data, why do I still feel like
I'm flesh and blood?
And I still have to go to the little
girl's room.
You don't really.
You just think you have to.
Oh, well, I hope you're right,
because... Where's the real us?
Our flesh and blood bodies?
I don't know.
I suppose we're back at the campground
still.
Oh!
Yeah, we're alive back there.
We exist simultaneously with our other
selves.
We're in a parallel digital universe like
the Digimon.
Does that mean I don't have to worry about
brushing my teeth anymore?
We've got bigger things to worry about
now, TK.
Although, do us all a favor and don't stop
brushing.
Yeah, please.
Hey!
Wait a second.
I've got an idea.
Let me see.
If I can just correct this program...
Uh-oh!
He's in computer dark mode.
This could take a while.
Whoa!
I've called up a holographic map of the
Digi-World.
You can see how physically similar it is
to the planet Earth.
In fact, there are a lot of parallels with
our world.
That's terrific, Izzy.
Great time for a geography lesson.
Pay attention and you might learn
something.
Yeah?
If I enter the email address
of the person who contacted
us, I can find his location
in the Digi-World here.
Now, look.
That email address is from a web domain in
our world.
I've logged on to it a thousand times.
Is there a point to this somewhere?
Is the person who sent the message in our
world or the Digi-World?
That's just the thingies in both.
Look.
The Digi-World's on the left.
The world we know is on the right.
And if I overlay them like so...
The white lines match up perfectly.
What does it mean?
Reminds me of the balls of Bjorn my kitty
used to play with.
That's the world's digital network.
Through those lines, every computer on
Earth is connected to every other computer.
The Digi-World is a physical embodiment of
the data passing through them.
Guys, we're seeing something nobody else
has ever seen that nobody even knows about.
The digital shadow world that exists
alongside our own.
And they're not just parallel,
they're physically linked.
So anything we do here will have effects
on the other.
For real?
Intense.
Yeah.
And here's the coolest part.
Wherever this person is in the Digi-World,
I think I can take us there just by
entering his email address and clicking on
it.
Like accessing a webpage.
Hey, all this techno-talk's making my head
spinning.
Computer guys can never just do something,
TK.
That'd be too easy.
They gotta spend all day telling you how
they'll do it.
This is depressing.
Even when on computer data I have
allergies.
Look on the bright side, Joe.
If you weren't here, you never would've
met me.
Sara, does this mean that we don't exist?
That we're really not friends?
Of course not.
This may be a make-believe world, but that
doesn't mean our friendship isn't real.
Truthfully, I don't get it, but it sounds
right.
Oh, well.
Wherever we are, we're here.
So let's figure out what we're gonna do
next.
Come on, Brainiac.
What are you waiting for?
Okay, okay.
All I have to do is click on the guy's
email address and then bingo.
I hate bingo.
It's so confusing with all those different
letters and numbers.
Hey, look, a door.
All right, last one through is a rotten
egg.
Our electronic pen pal is right out there.
Or it could be a trap.
No way.
We're just bits of data, so I uploaded us
as file attacks.
Hey, I believe you.
Whoa, check this out.
Heads up, Edamon at 9 o'clock.
That's it.
It's a dumpster for you, Edamon,
you old pile of junk.
Uh, I think I left the water running back
at the Sphinx.
Okay, Ty, you're relieved.
It's our turn to stand watch.
Finally.
It's not much fun watching a bunch of
rocks.
Uh, goodnight.
I thought being in a computer cartoon
adventure would be more fun than this.
About tomorrow.
What?
I'm worried.
That Edamon is bad news.
Is it really worth it just to find my
crest?
Sure.
Don't worry, Sora.
Piece of cake.
I'm looking forward to spinning that ugly
monkey around by his tail.
Hey, come on.
Snap out of it.
Huh?
Look, if it was my crest or TK's or anyone
else's we were going after...
You know you wouldn't hesitate for a
second.
Oh.
Maybe you're right.
It's just, after what
Izzy said... What?
You mean all that stuff
about us being nothing but
little kilobytes in the great
computer program of life?
It just makes us seem so small and
insignificant.
Like nothing we do really matters.
Of course it matters.
We can't take the chance that it doesn't.
Remember, there's one thing that's
important to keep in mind.
This is more than a parallel universe.
It's a shadow world physically linked to
our own.
Anything that happens
here in the Digi-World can
have a direct effect on
the things in the other.
Then, the same thing goes for us,
right?
We're shadow versions of our other selves.
Right.
Exact computer copies.
So whatever happens,
we have to be just as
careful as if we were
still our physical selves.
Hey, sometime this year.
Man, you guys talk more than my mom's book
club.
Can we go?
Alright.
I got into the program and found the most
direct route to the center of the pyramid.
Okay now, let's get this straight.
We're only going in there to find this guy
and get Sora her crest, right?
Right, right.
That means no fights or adventures or
dangerous stuff.
You whimper more than my puppy.
Matt, Mimi, TK, stay here and stand guard.
Let's go in.
If you really don't think you need me,
I miss you guys already.
We'll be back in time to eat.
Or get eaten.
See you guys!
Come back as soon as you can!
Okay, keep together.
There's a hidden back door to the program
we could use to get in.
It should be somewhere right up ahead.
That's funny.
It should be right here.
Where's my fried banana sandwich?
You know I like to eat after my nap.
Ty, what is it?
It's Edamon.
Who's there?
What do we do now?
Quiet, Biomon.
Great, now I'm hearing things.
Yoo-hoo!
Huh?
You know, I'm gonna have to have this
place completely exterminated.
Because...
Something's starting to bug me.
We've got him talking to himself.
Really funny, Ty.
Are you crazy?
What if you'd gotten us caught?
But we weren't, were we?
Well, now that we're in, what do we do?
I guess next we try to find a way through
these walls.
The trick is... finding the weak points.
Hey, I found one!
Oh!
As I was saying, Agumon, the trick is
finding the weak points.
Let's use heads, not hands.
Hey, check it out.
You can see right through this wall.
Yeah, here it is.
It's another breach in the system's
security.
Look!
Gaffimon!
Be still.
Ow!
Hey, what's a big idea?
What do you mean?
Don't give me that.
Just because the boss likes me.
Have you gone nuts?
Nuts to you!
No!
I...
You could have gotten us all captured back
there, Ty.
You're so immature.
Could you yell a little quieter,
huh?
Gee, Sora, relax, kid.
Get a grip.
Who elected you the queen of the fun
police?
Yeah, this is tons of fun, and getting
caught will be a blast.
Couldn't you just pass notes?
It's much quieter.
This looks nasty.
We don't have to go through here,
do we?
This firewall's the
system's last line of defense,
but there appears to be
only one safe way through it.
And if we pick the wrong way, they'll
scoop us up with a spatula.
You're not scared, are you, Joe?
Maybe I am a little.
Relax, it's not like we're human or
anything.
We're just bunches of kilobytes,
remember?
The weak point should be...
here.
Cool.
Are you coming in, or are you just going
to stand there all day?
This is the host computer.
Yowza.
Do you think it comes with a CD-ROM drive,
or is that optional?
And what do you suppose that thing is?
I've heard of him.
His name's Datamon, a super-intelligent
robotic Digimon.
He disappeared without a trace some time
ago.
Nobody ever knew what happened to him.
Maybe that's the thing that sent us the
email.
It kind of looks like he's a prisoner.
Of course it was.
Who else?
Today is your lucky day.
And mine.
I get it.
He's communicating with us through the
infrared board on my laptop.
Oh, a hardware fan.
Well, listen, we haven't much time.
Long, long ago, I bought Etamon,
and lost.
One of my rare miscalculations.
Anyway, I was severely damaged,
and he imprisoned me here, and forced me
to act as his webmaster, administering his
network.
Without Etamon knowing, however,
I was able to slowly repair myself,
restoring my capabilities bit by bit over
the years.
Eventually, I gained control over Etamon's
network.
Not total control, but enough to bring
some misery to that blubbering baboon.
At last, I'm ready to free myself, but I
need your help to break the cyberlock.
What about my crest?
You said in your message that you could
lead us to it.
Um, yes, whatever you want.
Just please, help me out of here.
Can we trust this talking can opener?
Etamon is your enemy as well as mine.
That makes us allies.
Please, you're my only hope.
Okay, you're on.
What do you need from us?
I am transmitting instructions for
disengaging the cyberlock.
Hey, push that lever for me, would you,
Ty?
Got it.
Right three, left five.
Quickly, quickly, before Etamon returns!
Then push the button.
Okay, Ty, pull the lever back to its
original position.
That should be the last step in the
process.
Hold it.
Etamon!
I've been watching you on surveillance
cameras and you're an annoying little brat.
You know that?
Fucking troublemaker.
Hey, it's been my pleasure.
Great.
Why don't you just call him ugly,
too?
All this time, I thought it
was his snot-nosed kids
who were causing my
network to go on the fritz.
But it was you, wasn't it, you digital
dumpster?
Well, in a word, yes.
You rat!
Digibomb!
Help out!
Ogilmon, digivolve
to... Rayman-on!
Tentermon, digivolve to...
Kabu-Kerry-mond!
Vealmon, digivolve
to... Verdramon!
Golemon, Digiball, too!
Digimon!
Digimon?
Huh?
I'm free!
Now let's see how you like it!
Huh?
Wee!
Ha-ha-ha!
Oh, Seelmon!
Hey, we set you free!
And I do appreciate that, you chumps!
Dumb kids!
You'll think by now they'll learn to trust
no one!
Trust me!
This will hurt!
Dark fat worm!
Beomond, over here!
Uh-oh!
Back!
Huh?
Well, so much for no fighting!
Beomond!
Tough luck!
Looks like I won again!
It's not over yet!
Mucky breath!
Just wait!
With their powers harnessed to my own,
I'll be more than a match for you!
Ha!
Come back here,
you bratty little... Sora!
Hi!
They've gone back out through the
firewall.
Okay.
The weak point was here, right?
Wait a minute!
Let me get back online so I can find it!
We don't have time for that, Izzy!
What can happen?
This isn't the real me, right?
Don't test theories now!
Pain still hurts, Ty!
Hey!
Joe!
What are you thinking, Ty?
We're in a video game?
Nothing can happen to us because these
aren't our real selves here?
Yeah, something like that!
Well, think again!
Our digital selves are directly linked
with our other selves back home.
You need to be a lot more careful.
No telling what may happen.
You mean if I... If something
happens here... It... happens there?
I can't... move.
The weak point is one meter to your right!
No way!
Just one false move and it's over!
Hey, Ty!
It's safe, Ty!
We came through it all right on the way
in!
Yeah, but then I didn't know... that...
Go on!
It's okay!
Come on, Ty!
We're wasting time!
Sora needs us!
What's wrong with you?
Ty?
Sorry!
We held them!
As long as we could!
Now to finish off you kids and put an end
to your annoying interference!
What?
Would you care for some needle spray?
Howling blaster!
Come on, let's move!
Ty?
What's wrong with you?
Come on!
No, not again!
They didn't get away again!
I'm having an extremely bad day,
baby!
I don't get it!
When the creep grabbed
Sora and Biomon, why
didn't you go through
the firewall after them?
I couldn't... I couldn't move!
It's not your fault!
We're all in this together, Ty!
We'll find a way to get them back!
It's all my fault!
Sora!
No!