So everyone was finally reunited,
except Sora.
She was still upset
because Demi-Devi-Mon told
her that her crest of
love would never glow.
Demi-Devi-Mon and Myotismon unleashed a
vicious attack and really hurt Bi-O-Mon.
The rest of the Digimon tried to help,
but Myotismon was too powerful.
Bi-O-Mon wanted to fight, but Sora
protected her.
That's when she realized
she was acting just
like a mom, protecting
someone she loved.
Her crest then began to
glow, helping Berger-Mon
digivolve to Garuda-Mon and
stopping Myotismon's attack.
Digimon, digital monsters, Digimon are the
champions!
Change into digital champions to save the
digital world!
Digimon, digital monsters, Digimon are the
champions!
Digimon, digital monsters, Digimon!
Hey, check it out, Mimi!
How about this for an instant bath?
I'm glad I took these bags from the
restaurant.
Gee, now you'll be able
to go soak your head
the next time you
have an allergy attack.
Right.
That was so funny I forgot to laugh.
Now that Myotismon's
chasing us, we're gonna have to
keep running like a bunch of
crazed shoppers at the mall.
No, he's just a big creep if you ask me.
I'd have to agree with you on that.
Yeah, he's small potatoes for us.
My wish is to never see him again,
period!
Mine too!
Gather round, everyone!
I hope lunch is ready because I'm
starving!
Chennai's back!
He wants to speak to us!
Hope he's found a way to get us out of
here.
Don't keep us in suspense!
What's this all about anyway?
Well, I brought you some good news and
some bad news.
Which would you like to hear first?
Save the good news for last.
I hate being depressed.
He's a basket case anyway.
Let's start with the good news.
Actually, you all look like you could use
some cheering up.
I've been told another child will be
joining your group.
Another child?
Who tells you these things anyway?
Well, this is someone you shall want as a
friend.
This someone is a digi-destined.
Really?
Is there another one?
Oh, I hope this new one will have a
digi-mon that will be able to help us.
You and me both.
The important thing to remember is that
all eight of you must be together.
As long as you are separated, the worlds
will not be in harmony with each other.
Everything will go wacko, so we must find
that other child as soon as possible.
How do we do that?
Hmm.
I hope it's someone my size.
I hope she's my size so we can swap
clothes.
Tell us something about this kid.
Like, what's his or her name?
Uh, the name?
Yeah.
It's... I forgot.
And I... Calm down.
I do know the location of the child.
It's Japan.
Huh?
Japan?
Where is Japan?
Japan's a big island in the Far East.
Agumon and Tai were transported there when
our two worlds converged.
Mm-hmm.
If they ever converge again, maybe we'll
all get to go home.
Yeah.
Remember, that was the good news.
Can't wait to hear the bad.
My Otis-mon has heard of the Eighth Child
and will be going to Japan soon.
He's gathering his forces as we speak.
If he gets to the child first,
both of our worlds will be doomed.
Doomed?
We need some spies on the inside.
Ah!
The noodle-brainer team!
Don't worry.
I'll whip them all into shape.
These dweebs will be unbeatable when I get
through with them.
Nanamon is an invader Digimon.
I'd tell him what I
really think about his
sunglasses, but his power
punch would flatten me.
Okay, big boy.
We know you can talk the talk, but
now it's time for you to do your stuff.
Just watch.
I don't wanna.
Can I help you two?
Yep.
We're a couple of renegade soldiers
looking for a battle to fight.
We may look silly, but underneath our cool
exterior we're fighting machines.
That's so!
Who are ya?
I'm Pankagumon!
I'm Reggepalmon!
Yeah!
What a couple of weirdos!
You're perfect!
I'll take ya!
Yeah!
Cool!
Come in.
My Otismon, I have some good news to
report.
The soldiers are assembled and we're ready
to move out!
Are they worthy of me?
Yes, my master!
They're a bunch of helpless sea slugs if
you want my opinion.
Who are you?
Greetings, little blue one.
Gah!
I've got time on him.
Have you done what I've asked of you?
Yes!
Per your instructions, I
searched everywhere and
found the most ferocious
Digimon I could find.
You'll be very pleased.
I knew I could trust you, Gatoman.
I look forward to meeting them.
Thanks!
What is it?
We've prepared the room and it's ready for
your inspection.
Fine, the two of you are dismissed.
Right!
You
don't mind my asking, sir, what is this
room for?
Legends tell of this hollowed gate.
It is the passageway that will take us
forward to the other world.
When we pass through this porthole, we'll
be free to infiltrate the human realm.
According to my information,
the gate to the other
world should be
somewhere inside this castle.
My theory is that Myotismon
sent Demi Devamon to
distract us while he stayed
behind to prepare the gate.
Truly an ingenious plan on his part.
A good theory indeed.
Agumon and Palmon have certainly been gone
a long time.
It's not that I'm worried, it's just
that...
Well, I hope they're looking for the
location of the gate.
I'm wilting!
I want to get out of here now!
Now hop like Bunnymon!
Come on!
Get the jelly out of your legs!
I want you grunts to be tough!
This battle's gonna be big, so get with
it, you worthless warts!
You gotta try like you never tried before!
We've tried we never tried before!
Oh, why should we start now?
Listen up!
Everybody that mouths off will go without
dinner tonight!
You do understand me, don't you?
Oh, well...
But it's the only reason we joined the
Storky Army in the first place!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
I'd like to soak in a hot tub for about
two months!
I've got blisters on my blisters!
I think we have to stop this guy,
and I know how to do it!
Yeah?
I was a soldier with him before,
he likes to drink soda, but the bubbles go
right to his head and make him as dipsy as
a Toodlemon!
He gets real kooky and he'll do anything
he want!
Even let us escape?
I must be exhausted!
Why?
I thought I saw a little pink thing pop up
and talk to us!
His stomach will fill with bubbles!
Yeah, he's sure to explode!
But if it explodes, won't he make us hang
around and clean it up?
You're nutsy!
Forget the mess, we can all escape!
One of us should go and get some soda,
he won't miss one of us!
That might work!
After that slob wouldn't
let us have dinner, I'll
open the bottles and pour
them down his throat myself!
Next up, contact sports!
How about wrestling?
You're the ball!
Yeah!
I wonder where... There it is!
Oh!
This is what he gets for not feeding us!
You guys are so pathetic, don't tell me
you're all tired!
You're a worthless pack of goons!
What?
What in the world?
Oh, boy!
Me likes orange!
Oh!
Delicious!
Have some more!
Oh!
Hey, anybody wanna go dancing?
I'm wide on my feet!
Oh!
Go!
Yeah!
Oh!
I love that soda!
It worked!
Yeah!
Let's get out of here!
Before he wakes up!
Yeah!
Bubble Fizz won't last forever!
I'm worried!
Just be patient!
Hey, Luke!
They're back!
Sorry!
We had a big bruiser on our hands!
Let's go!
My signal is useless inside the castle,
so you are on your own!
I'm counting on you!
We got it covered!
I hope so!
You must stop Myotismon from carrying out
his plans and protect your friend in Japan!
We better move him!
I must find the secret to the gate!
Once I understand the meaning of these
cards, the key will open the lock!
Then I will be able to enter the path to
the human world!
You digi-destined think
you're so smart, but
in reality I am always
one step ahead of you!
I've got
a real funny feeling about this,
you guys!
Think something's wrong?
Something just doesn't feel right!
Oh!
Making any progress, Joe?
No.
This lock's ancient, but I still can't
break it.
Maybe if we had the key it would open.
Yeah, and maybe if we had a cannon we
could blast our way in.
It's no use!
Maybe there's another way in!
Let's check!
Joe, let's go!
How come I never get to be the hero?
Hmm... Something's
totally weird here.
What?
We've passed this way before!
Is that you, Ty?
Yeah, I'm up here!
Have you found anything unusual down
there, Izzy?
Well, you could say that, Ty!
The truth is, you're way down there and
we're up here!
I think you guys may need glasses!
We're way up here above you!
But there's no way!
That's scientifically impossible!
I'm ready to proceed!
Go now and tell our forces that no sacrifice
is too great in this moment of glory!
Right!
There's certainly no need to tell them
that they won't be sharing in the rewards!
I hold all the cards, and they are no
longer a mystery now!
All I need is to find that digi-destined
eighth child!
My theory is my Otisman
has set up these optical
illusions to deter us
from finding the gate!
Well, I'd say he succeeded!
We're still as lost as we were before we
started!
All we've done so far is go round and round
in circles and we don't know up from down!
It's making me dizzy!
Huh?
What's up?
Someone's coming!
You sure?
You doubt me?
Huh?
I'm itching to bite!
Why?
Cause you're not pleased?
They seem to know where they're going!
Maybe we should try to follow them!
They'll lead us to the right place!
I shall now be embarking on a journey to
another world!
There are forces which must be neutralized
before our victory here can be complete!
But never fear!
I shall return in triumph!
It's time to stand back and watch me work
my magic!
Open the gate to my destiny!
You're not going anywhere!
Not as long as we can help it!
What is your name?
Do you work for me?
Can't you see I'm busy at the moment?
Yeah!
Right!
Demi-devi-mon, would you please take care
of this annoying gang of hoodlums?
I have better things to do!
Of course, sir!
Anything you want!
I'm at your service!
I'm not letting you get past this gate!
Bad chance, you little twerp!
I brought reinforcements!
It's all yours, Nanamon!
Right!
Don't even think about passing by me!
You got it?
Farewell, Digi-doomed!
Okay!
Let's fight!
Yeah!
We don't want to fight, you guys,
but the future is at stake!
You'll have to forgive us!
Digimon!
Abumon!
Digibob to...
Raymon!
Kabumon!
Digibob to... Wongumon!
Kantumon!
Digibob to...
Kabuterimon!
Gobamon, Digivolve too?
Ikakumon!
Back in your ranks!
Come on, I'll buy you dinner!
Too late now, we're going for some fast
food!
Y-y-you're big!
Anybody need a wrestling coach?
You can't resign!
You want to bet, Pipsqueak,
when it comes down
to having my fanny
kicked, I'm out of here.
And if you don't believe me, you might
check the fine print of my contract.
We're coming through!
Don't let me stand in your way!
You might as well give up!
I'm outnumbered!
Could help us so hard to find!
Just admit you picked the wrong side and
give it a rest already!
If you're trying to frighten me,
it won't work!
You haven't dealt with me!
That was two!
To the gate, everyone!
We've got to get
through, Digimon!
He's one nasty dragon guarding the gate.
Debbie doesn't like losing.
If you want a real surprise, look into his
eyes.
He'll be hypnotized!
Nova Brun!
Howling Luster!
It'll be a joke!
Farpoon Torpedo!
Had enough Needlespring!
I'm starting to feel really weird.
What's happening?
Come
on!
What's happening?
C'mon, we have to make a run for it while
we have the chance.
Ready, get set, go!
Go through it!
Digimon!
Digimon monsters!
Digimon are the Junkers!
Braymo!
Digimon tools!
A little Braymo!
It's a dreamer!
Champions of this is over her!
He did it!
It's clear sailing from here!
C'mon, everybody!
Let's get through that gate!
Get ready to jump!
Hurry!
The gates are closing!
Goodbye!
It can't be!