I thought if I gave myself up to
Myotismon, he would stop his attacks.
What I didn't know is that his plan was to
destroy both me and Gatomon.
The others tried to rescue
him, but all of the Digimon
powers together still weren't
enough to defeat Myotismon.
He released a big blast at me and my
little Gatomon.
Wizardmon wanted to save us, so he jumped
in and took the full force of the blow.
Gatomon digivolved to
Anjurumon and struck Myotismon
with her celestial arrow
and he was finally beaten.
Except, for some reason, his mysterious
fog hasn't lifted yet.
Digimon, digital monsters, Digimon are the
champions!
Change into digital champions to save the
digital world!
Digimon, digital monsters, Digimon are the
champions!
Digimon, digital home
monsters, Digimon.
Aw, give me a break.
That lousy fog barrier's still up.
So beating my Otismon didn't solve
anything.
Hang on.
We've got mail from Jedi.
Wonderful news, my friends.
I may have found the way to defeat him
once and for all.
Although this looks like
a graham cracker, it's
actually an ancient text
which I've translated.
The sky will be darkened by the wings of
many bats.
The fallen people will invoke the name of
the undead Digimon King, and when the
clock strikes the hour of
the beast, the undead king
will reveal himself in his
true form as the beast.
Then angels will shoot arrows of hope and
light at the loved ones of those they've
been sent to protect, and a miracle will
happen.
Please always recycle.
That last part seems weird, but good luck.
Well, that was about as clear as mud.
Can you make heads or tails of it?
Oh, well... Listen, Ty, maybe we
should try and find Mom and Dad.
You're right.
I wouldn't mind checking out my place
either.
And I'd like to change my pajamas,
or at least get a matching robe.
Yeah, let's go.
No reason to stay here.
All right.
Can someone explain what's going on?
It's a pretty long story, but I'll try.
Hey, everybody, wait for me.
Sorry I'm late.
Huh?
Aren't we missing somebody?
We're waiting for Joe.
He's still upstairs.
Mom?
Dad?
There's no sign of anyone.
Do you think they've been captured with
all the rest?
That would be sad.
Don't do that!
Relax.
It's only your brother, who's totally
freaked.
Jim, what are you doing hiding in there?
Well, I'm not playing hide and seek.
Those creepy things tore the place apart.
They are creepy, aren't they?
Frankly, I wouldn't talk if I were you.
Hey, don't worry about this little guy,
Jim.
He's a friend of mine.
And I've got more good news.
My Otismon's been destroyed.
Just who is my Otismon?
For once in your
life, Joe, you actually
sound like you know
what you're talking about.
Mm-hmm.
There's a first time for everything.
Find out what's happening at the
convention center.
And we'll try to find a way through the
fog barrier.
Right, TK?
Hmm.
So tell me, Joe, are you still planning on
being a doctor?
Joe is smart.
He could be a doctor.
There's a lot more to it than that.
Joe could be whatever he wants.
It's what my dad wants me to be.
Poor dad.
He doesn't know.
No.
Are you implying Joe's not smart enough
for something?
Listen, I don't care if you are his
brother.
You've got no right.
Now calm down.
I'm not saying he's not smart enough.
I'm just saying it'll be
kind of hard for him to be
a doctor when he passes
out at the sight of blood.
Yep.
That's my pal Joe.
Look, I think your friends are coming.
Huh?
We'll talk about this later, Joe.
There's one of them now!
Let's go!
Tentamon!
Teperent!
Roo pulled shakuhay!
Marching fishes!
Nipis and I.
Pyrroquister!
Excellent!
Good work, you guys.
Mom, wake up.
Daddy?
What's happened to them?
They're all so totally still.
Are they?
No, their pulses are normal.
That's good.
Joe, listen to me.
It's your life.
You've got to live it your way,
not Dad's way.
I guess.
After I become a
doctor, I'm going to South
America, Africa, someplace
I can really be of help.
Dad's already told me he doesn't approve.
I can imagine.
Anyway, right now we've got to see to all
these people.
What can we do?
If only we could get help from the
outside.
It's hopeless.
There's no way to get through this fog.
Hello, anybody!
Come out!
Wherever you are!
No, like this!
If you save us, we'll give you anything
you want, including candy!
Nice try.
This just isn't working.
Maybe we should go back to shore.
This is all our fault, Gatomon.
Mm-hmm.
Don't worry, this spell
or whatever it is will wear
off, and then everyone
will just wake up again.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Isn't that right, Mom?
New buster!
Ooh, bubbles!
We were better off lost in the fog!
Let's go!
If you insist!
Come on, guys!
Hey, what happened to them?
Over there!
The sky will be darkened by the wings of
many bats!
Now things start to get interesting!
You wanted to talk to me?
Yes, son.
When you went off and
left us there in hiding, your
mother and I thought we
might never see you again.
So we talked, and decided,
the time had come to
tell you that we're not
your real parents, Izzy.
I already know.
I heard you talking once.
I pretended to myself I hadn't heard
anything.
Then I made believe I had misunderstood.
Then I tried to wipe it
from my mind and just
act like everything
was the same as before.
But it wasn't, and I
didn't mean to, but I just
started drifting away from
you a little more each day.
That's why you buried yourself in that
computer.
That's right.
It's not surprising.
It's who you are.
You see, in so many ways, you're the
living image of your real father.
What was my real father like?
He was a fine man and a brilliant
mathematician.
In fact, he was a lecturer at the
university.
He and I were distant cousins.
I was his only living relative.
And your mother had no family of her own,
so when it happened...
Late one night, there was a terrible car
accident.
Neither of them survived.
We had lost a little boy of our own,
you see, just before.
So, when we were asked if we might want to
take care of you...
Well, it seemed like, I don't know,
some kind of sign.
We said yes.
So you made me your son.
We always planned to tell you the truth.
We were just waiting for you to grow up a
little bit more.
But now, you seem to have found out on
your own.
We waited too long.
I'm sorry, son.
No.
No, Dad.
There's no need for you to be sorry.
It couldn't have been easy for you to tell
me all this.
And, um, well, um, glad you did.
We just want you to know we love you,
Izzy.
You see, as far as we're concerned,
you are our real son.
Nothing can ever change that.
Gee, it's times like this, I wish I had a
Digi-Mommy.
Ah!
Lord Myotismon.
Lord and Master.
Mom, what is it?
Are you alright?
Mom!
Hey there, Master!
Good to see you back on your feet!
More energy!
I need more!
You got it!
Come
on, this is gonna be bigger and better
than ever!
Myotismon.
Lord and Master.
Stop it, Dad!
Snap out of it!
Mom, it's me!
Dad, Master!
What's going on?
Very odd.
Physically, they're still asleep.
It's like they're all having the same
dream.
Hey, wait a minute!
Do you guys remember that prophecy?
Yeah, it fits.
It says the fallen people will invoke the
name of the Undead King.
Well, the first part about the bats came
true.
Huh?
When was that?
What did the third part of the prophecy
say?
Before the recycle part, it was,
when the clock strikes the Hour of the
Beast, the Undead King will reveal himself
in his true form.
Terrific!
But what's the Hour of the Beast?
Six, six, six.
Six seconds and six minutes past six o
'clock.
Sounds like triple six is our unlucky
number.
It's almost time!
Quick, get in the van!
We're never gonna make it!
Showtime!
Is that my Otis mod?
He's been taking steroids.
It's his true form, the Beast.
Hey, come on!
Fight!
Stitcher bombs!
Where are my manners?
Allow me to introduce you to the new and
improved Venom Myotismod!
Venom Myotismod?
That's right, the King of the Undead!
He's the un and you're the dead!
More energy!
I'm hungry!
No problem, boss!
There's all those people just laying there
waiting for ya!
Myotismod, Lord and Master!
Remember to start your day with a good
breakfast!
I'll begin with a little snack!
Hey, hang on!
What are you doing?
Wow!
He's going after everyone at the
convention center!
Pump it up, you guys!
Digivolve!
You heard them!
Let's do it!
Yo!
Digivolve!
No!
Aruma!
Digivolve!
To...
Vettel Gremont!
We
flip a coin to see who goes first!
Allow me!
Gigablaster!
Move claw!
It didn't even phase it!
Did it work?
More energy!
I must be!
That answer your question?
Matt!
Go to the convention center and warn the
others!
Don't worry about us!
We'll take care of this clown!
Alright, but just watch yourself!
Let's go!
Pizza tank!
I am hungry!
Now!
Huh?
I don't know how long they can hold them
off!
Even if we had time, we couldn't move all
these people!
You don't understand!
You can never outrun him!
We have to destroy him!
You can count on me!
Yeah!
And that's two!
Me three!
Hey!
Make that four!
Uh-uh-uh!
Patamon's the only Digimon I need to come
with me!
The rest of you stay here!
Huh?
Nothing personal!
I just want all of you to save up your
strength!
If my plan doesn't work, you'll all be
needed!
Let's do what she says!
She knows these bad Digimon better than
anyone!
Excuse me, I don't mean to be a downer or
anything!
But how can any of us hope to stand up
against that guy?
He's bigger than most buildings!
I've got a plan, like I said!
Come on, Patamon!
Let's fly!
Uh-huh!
We're right behind you, Patamon!
Let's go, son!
We're in this together, right?
Right!
Patamon!
Angels?
What's going on?
It's kind of complicated.
They digivolved, Mom.
Anjumon is the fully evolved version of
Patamon.
And Anjuwoman is the same for Patamon.
You see?
Well, trust me on this, huh?
It's nice to have outside interests, but I
hope your schoolwork hasn't suffered.
Dad, this is the fate
of the planet we're
dealing with, the survival
of the human race.
Don't worry, I can take a makeup test for
anything I missed.
I sure wish I'd brought the camcorder.
Uh-oh!
Looks like trouble!
What happened to him?
He must have drained them of their energy.
Goodbye, small fry!
Let's go, arrow!
And the bait!
This won't be easy.
Nobody ever said it would be, Anjumon.
I shall enjoy devouring you.
Angel food is one of my favorites!
I'm so sorry, Matt.
We tried.
He was too much for us.
Why is that monster so much bigger than
the other Digimon?
Search me?
Hmm, I thought he was fully evolved.
But he found some way of digivolving into
an even higher level.
Some kind of mega ultimate level.
Hey, that's not fair.
It's like changing the rules in the middle
of a game.
Stop it, you're tickling me!
Now it's my turn!
You can do it, Anjumon!
Go, Anjumon!
Wait a minute, the prophecy, that's it!
Quick, Izzy, what did it say in there
about angels?
I begin to grow born with you!
What does the prophecy say?
Angels will shoot arrows
of hope and light at the
loved ones of those they
have been sent to protect.
And a miracle will happen.
Okay, if Anjumon and Anjawoman are the
angels in the prophecy...
So then who are the ones they've been sent
to protect?
That must mean TK and Kari.
The angels will shoot arrows at their
loved ones.
It's simple.
Allow me to explain.
Say I'm kind of like a guardian angel.
Whose guardian angel am I?
Yours.
And who do you love the most?
I was getting to that.
My mom and dad, obviously.
Exactly.
But TK and Kari not only have moms
and dads, they have something else, too.
They have brothers.
In a word, bingo!
Why would you want them shooting arrows at
your loved ones?
Sounds dangerous to me.
They're angels, Izzy.
Maybe they're like Cupid.
He was sort of an angel.
When he shot arrows, they were arrows of
love.
Mom, isn't that a little corny?
It may be corny, but I buy it.
All we've got to do is get
Anjumon and Anjuwaman
to hit you guys with
their arrows of love.
Hey, let's not be too hasty here.
What do you think?
It's worth a shot.
Kari!
TK!
You sure you wanna?
Let's see these arrows of hope and light.
You two have got to get them to shoot at
us.
They'll only do it if you tell them to.
You really want them to shoot you?
What if you get like dead or something?
Never happen.
Right?
Right.
Okay.
Anjumon!
Listen up!
I know this maybe sounds crazy.
But shoot Matt and Ty with your arrows!
You too, Anjumon!
He's right.
Sounds crazy.
But... Wait, you
sure about this?
What if that prophecy's all wrong?
You guys want a miracle to happen or not?
Yeah, miracles require a little faith.
Scared, Ty?
No, not at all.
How about you, Matt?
Course not.
Piece of cake.
But maybe I'll just... hang on to you to
make sure you don't chicken out or anything.
Yeah, right.
I'll do the same for you, buddy.
One miracle!
Coming up!
Agamon!
What did you ball?
Two!
For Greymon!
Will the Digi-Destined win the battle for
Earth and defeat Venom Myotismon?
Don't miss the next Digimon Digital
Monsters.