After we climbed Infinity
Mountain, we found
ourselves right between
Leomon and Ogre-mon.
They were being controlled by Devamon,
a most heinous character.
Devamon thinks that we were brought to the
Digi-world to defeat him.
I think he's slightly confused.
We escaped with the help of a well-timed
Digivolve and discovered a mansion where
we ate, cleaned up, and tried to get some
sleep.
Unfortunately, it was all an illusion
created by Devamon.
He destroyed the whole island and split
all us kids up.
Uh, I think we're in trouble.
Digimon are the champions!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Digimon!
Thanks to that Creek Devamon, File Island
broke up and all us kids got separated.
Now he's up there in his
castle on Infinity Mountain, and
I hate to think what horrible
things he's planning next.
Barone, those little intruders will meet
their doom.
Nothing can stand in my way.
The Digidestined don't have a chance.
Now fly, my Black Gears.
Fly!
Ty, it's cold, I'm hungry, and I wish we
were on solid ground.
It looks like you're
about to get your wish,
but next time, be careful
of what you wish for.
You just might get it!
Okay, so Mom was right, I should've worn a
sweater.
Take it easy, Agumon, I'll pull you out.
Hey, look, I found my clothes.
Except they're even too cold for me now.
Don't worry, I can give you the latest hot
look.
Fly!
Hey, Agumon, that's smokin'.
Now can you hook up my pants?
Fly!
Oops, nuked him a little too long.
But look on the bright side, Ty.
What bright side?
You won't be cold anymore.
What?
Mailboxes?
Agumon, maybe people really lived here at
one time.
I wish we could mail ourselves home,
but it looks like the only way we'll ever
leave Friesland is to take a real long
cold swim back to Infinity Mountain.
And I have a feeling that if the mountain
is drifting farther and farther away,
then our friends are too.
They must all be out there on those other
islands.
Where will we end up if we just keep on
drifting around like this, Ty?
Why would I know that?
Because you're from another world,
Ty.
I've never left File Island.
But Agumon, I've never left my world
either.
Well, I guess it could be worse.
There could be evil Digimon attacking us.
It's too quiet here.
Ah!
Frigimon!
It's Frigimon!
Frigimon is a food-friendly snowman.
But don't worry, Ty.
He's a good Digimon.
Oh no, my belly's freezing!
It's a black ear!
The black ear's controlling him!
Sub-Zero Ice Punch!
Hey, did you see that?
Did I?
His punch froze that mailbox solid.
I guess I better heat things up.
Pepper Brad!
Ha!
Frigimon!
I really hope you have a back-up plan.
Sub-Zero Ice Punch!
Yeah, wrong!
If he touches us, we're gonna be Ice Cube!
You're right!
And I'm so hungry, I don't have the
strength to Digivolve!
Whoa!
Ah!
Come back here and fight Frigimon!
Huh?
Uh-oh!
Whoo!
Going somewhere!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
We're trapped like ice mice.
There's nowhere else to run!
Ah!
Frigimon!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
I've got an idea, Ty.
Pick me up and throw me at him.
If I can land right on his back, I can
vaporize that black ear with my pepper breath.
I don't know if this is gonna work,
dude.
I can barely lift you, much less throw
you, tubby-mon.
It has to work, Ty.
It's our only chance.
Ha!
Sub-Zero Ice Punch!
He really likes to bury himself in his
work.
Alright, now's our shot.
Roll up into a ball.
You mean like this?
Yeah, now I'll show you why I'm my soccer
team's best striker.
uh,
what am I doing laying here?
What happened?
A black gear was on you and you almost
turned us into ice sculptures!
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I just hate when I do that, but thank you
for destroying the gear.
I'm glad you're both alright!
Have you seen anyone else here,
some more kids like me... hmm.
Come to think of it, I did see another boy
like you.
He was with a Gabumon.
They fell onto that other island over
there.
You saw Gabumon?
And Matt.
Perfect.
Matt would land that far away.
It's too cold to swim and we're drifting
at 100 miles a year.
You're a weird kid.
But since you got that
black gear out of my
aching back, I'll help
you get across the water.
Sub-Zero Ice Punch!
Hey, it's an ice bridge.
Now we can walk to the island.
I hope your punches don't, uh,
you know, freeze up.
Don't worry, as long as it's cold,
I'm full of punch.
Yeah, baby.
What if the ice breaks while we're out
there?
We could be Seedramon bait.
Alright, alright, we get it.
Quit shaking up the whole island.
Man, does everybody in the digital world
always have to be so noisy?
Come on guys, let's start walking.
TK!
TK, can you hear me?
Where are you, TK?
Matt, you must save your strength.
Wait!
Look, Matt, there's a cave right over
there.
Let's go in and get warm until the storm's
over.
A cave!
Of course, that's where TK is!
Yes!
TK!
I'm sorry, Matt.
Don't give up hope.
I was so sure he'd be in here.
But then again, TK never liked caves that
much.
There now, come and sit by the fire.
You can't help TK nor anyone for that
matter if you get sick.
You must rest to stay strong.
No, I gotta go back out there and find
him.
I feel fine.
Sit down.
You're not leaving this cave.
I'll go look for TK.
Huh?
Hey, come on, Matt.
I'm your Digimon, remember?
I'm here to help you through thick and
thin, whether it's hot or cold.
Besides, I've got a built-in warm fur
coat, which you haven't.
Come on.
Just sit right here and get warm.
I mean it.
I'll be back in two shakes of a Digi-tail.
Oh.
Poor little TK.
It's just not right.
He's my little brother.
I should be the one out there looking for
him.
TK!
Hey, Dad, are we there yet?
Huh?
Sorry, I just had to say that.
Sub-Zero Ice Punch!
Man, that island's just as far away as
ever.
Let's take five, you guys, and then we'll
keep on going.
The island's still moving.
If we stop, we may not be able to catch up
with it.
Agumon, if you could fly like Bergermon,
we'd be there already.
Well, I can't.
Bergermon probably can't fly in the cold
anyway.
No one toasts my clothes like you.
Come on, laugh!
No way.
Oh, I hate to see friends fight.
I'll carry you both across.
Like this.
There.
Nice and comfy?
Yeah, comfy as a mackerel on ice.
But at least we'll still be nice and fresh
when we get there.
Hey, did I ever tell you about the party I
went to that the Numomon crashed?
Now that's a party no one will forget.
Well, no sign of TK out here anywhere.
Poor Matt will be so disappointed.
Matt!
What are you doing out?
I told you not to leave.
Can you hear me?
Matt!
He's frozen.
I have got to warm him up or else... or
else he will never make it.
But how?
All I have is my own fur and... Hey,
that's it!
Why not?
No one's here to see me.
There.
Here you go, my friend.
You'll feel better in no time.
Good thing we're alone here.
This one Numomon kept following my sister,
but I handled it.
A little Sub-Zero Ice Punch show and tell.
Hey, you two, wake up!
We're here!
Hooray!
I wonder where Gabumon and Matt landed.
Hmm.
Right in the middle, I think.
So they must be up there somewhere,
in that forest.
Sure.
Let's go for a hike.
Then after that we'll hike.
Then we can hike some more.
Sheesh.
Hey!
There's a bed!
Matt must be around here somewhere!
Matt!
Can you hear me, Matt?
Oh, Gabumon!
Matt!
I'm here!
Gabumon!
Matt!
Are you out there?
Huh?
Gabumon!
You took off your fur for... Well,
thanks.
Yeah!
Uh, it's good to see you're
up and feeling... Achoo!
Achoo!
Better!
Hey!
You kept me all warm and now you have my
cold.
Bet you look pretty funny with no fur on,
Gabumon.
Thanks.
It's okay!
Matt!
Gabumon!
Hey!
It's Tai and Agumon!
They're here!
Matt!
Hey!
Tai!
I thought we'd never find you guys!
It sure is lucky that we met up with
Frigimon!
Frosty the Snowmon here?
Yup, this is him.
He happened to see you two fall on this
island, and then he got us here in no time.
Sub-Zero Ice Punch, you know?
Did you see anyone else?
No, when it rains kids, I usually notice.
You were the only two who fell here.
If there are more of you, they must be on
the other islands.
Poor TK.
Hey, don't worry.
We'll find him.
Hey!
Watch it, dude!
Sorry about that.
I am not used to having a cold.
A cold, huh?
I have an idea.
Don't go, Frigimon!
You can't catch his cold.
You already are!
How'd you get sick?
You're the one with the fur around here.
Stop making fun of him!
Leave him alone, Tai!
Hey, why don't you chill out, Matt?
I was only trying to see how we could help
him.
Let's go!
Gabumon, I think you ought to go take a
rest for a little while.
I think you're right.
We have to figure out what we're going to
do next.
Well, isn't it obvious?
We have to go search for all the others.
Yeah, right.
But how are we supposed to do that?
You heard what Frigimon said.
Everyone landed on different islands.
Unless you've got an airplane stashed
around here someplace, I think we're stuck.
Huh.
So I guess we'll ask Frigimon for help.
Weren't you listening to me?
He said they're scattered all over the
place.
He only has two arms.
He's not an octopus.
Then I'll have to make a raft out of some
of these trees, okay?
Matt, calm down.
Wow, what's eating you, dude?
I'm on your side.
I'll help you get off this island if we
have to build surfboards, okay?
Look, the others will be fine without us
for now.
We've got to focus on the real deal.
Real deal?
What?
I've got to spell it out for you?
We've got to know if this island's moving
toward that place Devimon talked about.
That's not the real deal!
You dupus!
There's nothing more real than our
friends, and finding them, and getting us
all back home safe, and don't you ever
forget it!
You want to ditch your friends to go look
for some far away land?
Go ahead, but I'm not coming!
I'll find TK!
I'll find all of them!
By myself!
But Matt!
Hey, come on!
Don't freak out on me!
You're not getting away that easy!
Nobody runs away when I'm still talking.
Now listen!
Maybe there's something across the ocean
to help us find the others!
Why do you have to get so bent out of
shape?
I know how you feel, Matt.
Ah!
Oh!
You haven't got a clue how I feel,
Ty.
You're acting like such a jerk!
Who are you calling the jerk, jerk?
Ty!
Stop that!
You have to work together, guys!
Stop fighting!
Matt!
Ty!
Quit it!
What do we do?
We have to stop them some way!
It's TK!
He's out there, on some strange island,
and he's all alone!
That's it!
Wow!
Matt!
Ty!
Get away from that cliff!
Don't give up, guys!
Hold on!
Ah, it's hopeless!
I'm so tired and hungry now, I don't have
any strength left at all!
We'd be okay if I could just digivolve
into Garurumon!
Ah!
I think it's Mojomon!
That's him, but he has a black gear inside
him!
Mojomon is a peaceful mountain Digimon
that doesn't like fighting!
You'd better tell him that!
He doesn't look very peaceful right now!
Ice Cloud!
It's raining kids and Digimon again!
I'm gonna have to start carrying an
umbrella!
Thank you, Frigimon!
Good timing!
Without you, we'd be flat as pancakes!
Well, next time, try not to land on my
head!
Here, I brought some food!
Excellent!
Let's eat!
And it's good and tasty, just the way I
like it!
An old cold remedy!
Ah!
I'll take your Omojomon!
Frigimon!
Sub-Zero Ice Punch!
Ah!
Boomerang Bone!
Whoa!
Nice trick, Mojomon!
Now watch ours!
Omojomon!
Digivolve 2!
Accommon!
Cremon!
Kabumon!
Digivolve 2!
Garururumon!
That's it, Garururumon!
Gah!
Now, Graymon, aim for the black gear!
Right!
Nova Blast!
Phew!
Now that's more like it!
Back down to standard Mojomon size!
Garururumon, what are you looking at?
Hurrah!
Just look at all those black gears!
There's a mountain of them!
Whoa!
I feel like I was just run over by a
monochromon!
A black gear was controlling you,
Mojomon!
That's right!
The fight wasn't your fault!
Whoa!
The same thing happened to me!
It's okay, though.
No one got hurt.
This doesn't change anything, Ty.
We still have to go find the others.
Huh?
Look!
The gears have fixed themselves!
It must be Devimon!
And the island's moving again!
We're moving all right!
The other way!
Back toward Infinity Mountain!
And Devimon!
If that's true, then this is no time for
us to be fighting!
Mhm.
No stinking gears are gonna stop us!
Yeah!
Together we're gonna be all right!
And now I know my little brother will be
all right!
Cause he has Patamon to take care of him
when I can't be there!
And I think as long as we can
all trust each other, Together
it's a sure bet that we'll be
able to fight and beat Devimon!
Yeah!
Yeah, that's I mean... Yeah!
You're too far as I wasrrr.