After Devimon destroyed
Vile Island, Matt and
I were stranded in a
freezing environment.
On another island, Tai and Agumon encountered
Frigimon, a victim of the Black Gears.
They got Frigimon back
to his kind self, and in
gratitude, he created
a bridge to our island.
When we found each other, things went
badly between Matt and Tai.
They got even worse when Mojomon attacked.
Agumon and I digivolved and defeated
Mojomon.
I do hope we find all the others soon.
Digimon!
Digital monsters!
Digimon are the Drunkons!
Change into Digital Champions 2.
Save the Digital World!
Digimon, digital monsters.
Digimon are the champions.
Digimon, I
would say we're traveling
at a very high speed,
plummeting toward
an unidentified island.
Panda, crash landing is imminent.
Try to think of it as if we're just
hitting the beach.
Now that should be good for some frequent
flyer miles.
Are you all right, Mimi?
Oh no, humidity.
Yes, some kind of tropical rainforest,
but not one I'm familiar with.
It all happened so fast.
Where are we?
Have you any idea what humidity does to my
hair?
Hmm?
It goes like, oh, poodily.
Not a pretty sight.
Uh, perhaps we ought to look around and
see if we can find any of the others.
Yeah, let's go.
Maybe we can at least find some air
conditioning or something.
Well, here we are, Izzy.
Hardly the light and breezy island-style
lodgings I was expecting to find.
Oh.
Uh, yes.
Very interesting, Izzy.
But don't you think we should keep
searching for the others?
I mean, now really isn't the time.
I know, but just look at this place.
It's prodigious.
I gotta check it out, Digimon,
just for a minute.
All right, but just for a minute.
Yum!
Bananas!
Banana?
Can you reach high enough?
Mm-hmm.
Shh!
I was really starved.
Now we can pretend we're having banana
splits, huh, Palmon?
Huh?
Hey, what's the big idea?
They certainly do look delicious.
Hot!
I can't believe it!
This place is seriously getting on my
nerves!
Hmm?
Hmm.
Is that hair, Moose?
Yeah!
Huh?
Uh, goodbye.
Meet the Nisha.
He means hello!
Nice to meet ya!
Huh?
Uh, yeah, what he said.
He means I'm right!
Palmon, who's the talking dessert?
It's Sukumon and Shumon, also known as the
Digi Losers.
Hey, thanks!
Sukumon and his mouse
buddy are always together
because they share the
same teeny tiny brain.
Whoa!
Wait!
All right, that's enough!
Leave us alone!
But you're okay, but first you gotta pay a
what do you call it?
Pay a toll!
Huh?
What do you mean a toll?
Does she think she can use our woods for
free?
She's gotta pay.
Like that, uh, purse there, for instance.
I like the hat.
No!
Huh?
What part of no don't you understand,
you wackazoids?
Now get out of here!
I think she insulted us!
Bingo, Einstein!
She did!
Go ahead!
Let her have it!
Ah!
Do it again!
That's it!
I give up!
I want to see the camp therapist!
Ooh, pretty!
Oh, wow!
That's better than two and ten foils!
I feel all dingly and refreshed like a
whole new person!
Yeah, we're a whole new person!
Is this one as much of a pain as the last
one?
No, really, we'll be nice from now on,
really!
So you'll leave us alone?
Wait, first tell us if you've seen any
other humans around here.
Any what?
Creatures that look like this one!
Uh... Well, as a matter
of fact... Oh yeah, I forgot!
Tell me!
Uh, well, it wasn't nearly as pretty as
you are, of course.
But we saw something fall into the old
ruins with the Tentamon!
So when were you planning on telling us?
Next week?
They must have seen Izzy, too,
Belmond!
Listen, you two, can you take us there?
It's important that we find him!
Sure, okie dokie!
No funny business!
Cross our heart!
And hope to die!
Well, of all the absolutely ridiculous
things to say... Right over there!
Huh?
Oh!
How are we supposed to get over there?
You're the one with the big hat!
You think of something!
A gorgeous girl like you must have a big
brain!
Thanks a lot, really.
Before you go, maybe you give us a big
thank you kiss, huh?
Mwah!
Oh, please tell me they're kidding!
Climb aboard, quickly!
Oh, maybe we jump the gun.
Ugh!
Just the thought of that kiss is making me
queasy!
That's ok!
We'll wait till you come back!
Don't hold your breath!
Ok, Izzy, I highly suggest putting an end
to this architectural tour.
As I mentioned before, I'm gathering
information.
I'm sure this place is crawling with
clues.
Look!
It's one of Devamon's black gears!
So it is!
You know what I think?
If we keep this gear from turning,
we'll completely jam that creep up!
Or even better, we could not do that!
Wouldn't that be fun?
And then we can go look for the others,
like we should have done in the first place!
Wait a minute, this is the same writing we
saw the last time!
Remember?
It made me realize that in DigiWorld,
basic data is a living, viable substance.
All that data is stored on my hard drive.
Only there was a power source here!
Get a power source, stop the gear,
is find our friends on that list!
Hmm.
Those lights are getting power from
somewhere.
Hey, an outlet!
Check it out!
It works!
Oh, goody!
Now, let's see if I can decipher this.
Here are the old ruins.
Let's just hope that giant kissy-faced
lemon custard was telling the truth.
One way to find out!
Yes!
Wow!
It's them!
Mimi?
Tentermon!
And Izzy!
Hey!
Hi, Mimi.
Finally, a friendly face!
Where's the rest of the gang?
I've no idea!
But, uh, shouldn't we, like, look for them
or something?
What are you doing, anyway?
Right now, I'm trying to decipher these
hieroglyphs.
Well, can't that wait, if you don't mind
my asking.
That's what I keep telling him.
Let's go and look for the others,
I say.
But does he listen to me?
No!
All right!
Get up, Izzy!
I'm sure the key to figuring everything
out is in here.
The question is, does each glyph represent
a letter, a word, or a phrase?
Hmm.
I'll have to cross-reference the
characteristics.
Hmm.
Izzy, any idea how long this is going to
take?
I mean, can we go sometime before winter
sets in?
Izzy?
Izzy, your friend is asking you a
question.
Yeah, her rear end's getting cold sitting
on the stone floor doing nothing.
Oh, wait.
Wait!
Yeah, yeah!
That might work!
Uh-oh!
Izzy!
Are you ignoring me, you computer geek
pipsqueak?
Okay, so if I make the variable constant
and search for bottle patterns... Hey!
Here's something!
Prodigous!
These ruins are a gigantic maze!
I'm leaving!
Right now!
Huh?
Oh, don't try, Mimi!
Oh no, not you too!
Izzy, do something!
Do what?
My laptop can't do everything!
I don't know!
Tell her you're sorry!
Sorry for what?
I can't take it anymore!
I haven't had anything to eat and my feet
are killing me in a giant limit custard
trying to kiss me and all I want to do is
get out of here!
We just want to leave!
Is that so wrong?
Honestly, Izzy, how can you be so
insensitive?
Insensitive?
What do you mean?
You ignore us while you poke away at your
computer!
I'm not ignoring you!
I'm doing something ultra important!
Like maybe saving this world!
If I can just decipher these hieroglyphs
then maybe we could...
You escape your stupid hieroglyphics!
Mimi, wait!
Oh dear!
You just like playing on your computer,
that's all!
You think I'm just playing around here?
I almost think you like computers more
than people!
Don't look now, but Mimi and Tentamon are
gone!
Now what do we do?
Hmm?
I hate this place!
I'll never recommend this resort to
anyone!
Mimi, wait!
Oh dear!
Mimi!
Mimi, are you alright?
I'm not a bad person.
So why is all this happening to me?
Mimi!
Mimi, we've got to be careful!
One wrong turn and we can get lost in
here!
All I want to do is get back home!
That's all!
Please wait!
I really think we ought to find our way
back!
I want my own bed!
My own baby brother!
Please!
Stop running off!
I don't see them anywhere!
Where could they have gone?
They didn't go deeper into the maze,
did they?
That'd be my guess!
These deciphered hieroglyphs tell me the
inside of these ruins is a giant labyrinth.
So if that is the case... They
could be lost in there forever!
Forever?!
Hey, uh, Tentamon?
Yes?
You get the feeling we're sort of going
around in circles?
See this sooty smudge on the wall?
I remember passing it a long time ago!
You're right!
Could it be that we're lost?
I realize this is probably a bad time
to say I told you so, but... Oh, quiet!
Oh, I can't bear it!
I'm going in!
And get lost too?
No, Palmon!
We have got to use our heads first!
But we can't just leave them!
We won't!
But this is one super complicated maze!
I've got to try to get a handle on it!
Then maybe I can help get them out!
Well, being lost isn't so bad!
Great!
Oh dear!
Are you hurt?
No, I'm fine!
I'm getting used to it by now!
If I'd just gotten to cheerleading camp,
none of this would have happened!
Let's try a systematic approach to this.
Maybe if we just keep turning to the left
or something like that...
Why should I listen to you?
It's your friend Izzy that got me into
this mess in the first place!
Wait!
Don't be too hard on him!
Yes, he gets a little wrapped
up in his work and doesn't
always interact well with
others, but he's a good boy!
There they are!
That's Mimi, that blinking light?
Precisely!
Oh, that's my girl!
I've honed in on the signal from her
digivice!
We can hear her!
Let's hope she can hear us!
Izzy to Mimi, do you read me?
Repeat, do you read me?
Izzy, is that you?
Oh right, it's working!
Okay, Mimi, I'm gonna navigate for you,
so walk exactly where I tell you to!
Don't worry, it'll be okay!
He knows what he's doing!
Is that you, Palmon?
Just do what Izzy tells you and you'll be
out of there before you know it!
See, I told you Izzy was a good boy!
Okay, now take the first doorway on the
right.
When you get to the end, turn left.
But be careful of the
next room because
there's a big hole in
the middle of the floor.
There should be a narrow ledge you can use
to get across!
Uh, Izzy, did we have to take the scenic
route?
Uh-oh, what do you mean uh-oh?
Okay, I'm ready, which way should we go?
Something has happened.
I was hoping it was just a glitch.
But there's definitely something in that
maze with them and it's moving closer.
Now I am starting to worry.
Izzy, what's with the silent treatment?
Did you hear that?
It sounded evil.
Tantamon, it's been such a long time.
Oh no!
St. Taramon!
Half man, half horse!
You really don't want to get on either of
his bad sides!
Come on, Nini, run!
I like a good chase.
Take a wrap!
Izzy, we are quite anxiously awaiting your
directions.
Are you there?
Another lap!
Through the doorway!
This way, Nini!
Great job, Izzy!
It's a dead end!
Where do we go now, Izzy?
Izzy, hello!
We seem to have lost contact with him.
Oh, really?
He's back!
Solar Ray!
Fire!
Your bravery is noted, but that alone will
not gain you any mercy.
What are you waiting for?
Make yourself bigger!
If you mean you want me to digivolve,
I'm afraid that's impossible.
What do you mean, impossible?
I'll tell you what he means.
He cannot protect you, so you have to hold
your ground, and that's truly impossible.
Stop talking!
Get going!
Oh, how I'd like to, but if I'm separated
from Izzy, I can!
Ah!
Stop that!
Can't you see I'm in the middle of saying
something?
What's that practice?
Izzy!
Get out of there!
Hurry!
Come on!
You don't have to tell me twice!
Watch out, Izzy!
I don't want this, Izzy!
I'm ready if I'm
ready for a break.
I won't take your hand for this.후!
Oh... And come
on, Digivolve to...
Kabu Terrimon!
Oh!
I forgot, when you get bigger,
you get a lot bigger, don't you?
Watch for your step!
Oh, uh, sorry.
Yeah, but this is no time for us to start
taking it easy.
Look who's here!
Yeah, I see him!
Leave them alone!
Electro Shocker!
I think it's time for a needle spray!
That felt interesting.
One of those black ears fell out of his
body.
Where am I?
Are you a good Digimon now?
Hm?
What?
That device on your bag.
This?
I have seen it before.
It is the mystical symbol of the Digivice.
These ruins are its temple.
And I am its guardian.
Well, that certainly looks familiar.
The Digivice is a preserver of the light.
A last line of defense against the
darkness that threatens existence.
Really?
I didn't get that.
But I'm starting to think they're more
than just a cool accessory.
Liomon!
Why are you here?
To destroy them.
The children.
What?
I warn you, Sentaruman.
Do not interfere with me.
No, Liomon!
I can't look.
It's too scary.
Well, maybe a peep.
Whoa.
Time's standing still here.
I said no, Liomon.
The children possess the Digivice.
As the guardian of its temple,
I must protect them as well.
Protect them from me?
Good luck.
Fist of the Beast King!
Solar Ray!
Now let's stop this madness before one of
us is hurt.
Liomon?
The children must be... destroyed!
Your Digivice!
It stopped him in his tracks!
Bad Kitty!
Out!
Go on!
Well, that got rid of him.
These things really are kind of amazing.
A preserver of light against the darkness.
Can you order a pizza with it?
I'm still starving.
Sentaruman, maybe with your help,
we could stop this black ear.
No, I'm afraid I have
neither the strength nor the
knowledge to oppose Devimon
and the powers of darkness.
Are you still going on about that?
When could we start looking for something
to eat?
Guess I'll just have to keep deciphering
and analyzing these two sets of pyroglyphs.
I'm sure all the answers are in here
somewhere.
Excuse me, isn't this where I came in?
You're not seriously starting all that
again?
Not right now!
Just a nano.
This black gear!
Who cares about that dumb old thing?
All I want is lunch!
Look,
the process has reversed itself.
Amazing!
Excellent work, Mimi.
It just goes to show you that sometimes
the simplest solution is actually the best.
That's not much of a compliment.
Well, are you?
I knew you couldn't keep away.
Huh?
So are we gonna go on a date or what?
Come on, what's your phone number?
Man, he is persistent.
At least blow us a kiss!
Okay!
Oh, come on!
Do it like you mean it!
You know you like us, you know you do,
please!
I love you!