We figured the eighth child had to be
somewhere in the Shibara section of town.
So the rest of us spread
out while Joe made phone
calls to every school kid
we knew four years ago.
Maybe one of those kids is the
Digi-Destined.
Meanwhile, that flea-bitten
menace Gatomon was still
on the prowl, causing
who-knows-what kind of trouble.
Meany and Sora stumbled onto this
fire-breathing bozo called Skull Meromon.
And things looked pretty
gnarly till MetalGreymon
joined the fight and
was able to cool him off.
Well, sort of.
Let me drive.
You're going the wrong way.
How do you know which way to go?
You've never been to the real world
before.
What's the difference?
I've never driven a car before either.
Well, it's my first time too.
Whoa, check him out!
Ew!
So these are city people in the real
world.
They don't look like much fun.
Well, Pumpkinmon, you're the right guy to
teach them what fun really is.
You are without a doubt the most rockin'
creature to ever have a pumpkin for a head.
Remember, Cheeks dig evil Digimon.
At least that's what I keep telling myself
anyway.
Gatsumon, you are the mon.
We're going to have such a blast here in
the real world.
They might even name a building after you.
The Gatsumonument, where they keep all the
party supplies.
Three, two, one... Yeah!
How much longer, Matt?
Relax, TK.
You're almost home.
Matt and TK's mom and dad aren't together
anymore, Padaman.
So even though they're brothers,
they don't live together.
So TK lives with their mom and Matt lives
with their dad.
That explains why they try so hard to stay
together all the time.
Sure late.
Yeah?
So?
The next stop's good enough.
No.
I'm gonna take you all the way home,
little brother.
You don't have to.
I know I don't have to, but I'm going to,
okay?
I've got my reasons.
What reasons?
You're my brother.
Thanks, Matt.
Ah, nothing like sweet brotherly love.
That's a digi mouthful.
We like when you guys get pushy.
Hey, quit it!
Easy, TK.
You don't have to be mean about it.
I thought what you guys said was not your
own beeswax.
Why are you listening to our conversation
anyway?
Fine.
You don't want me around, I'll leave.
Padaman?
I know what I'm not wanting!
Padaman, don't... Huh?
Padaman got off the train, TK.
Don't you want to go after him?
Who cares about him?
I think you care about him.
Don't you?
TK?
Better decide, TK.
The door's closing.
Where'd he go?
Where are we?
It seems like we've been walking around
for hours.
Yeah, I'm tired.
And I don't even have any feet or legs.
You shouldn't have yelled at him like
that, TK.
Hey, it's not my fault.
Well, actually, it is.
Oh, I'm really sorry.
I understand, TK.
I know you didn't mean to hurt his
feelings.
Well, I thought he was making fun of us.
No way, dude.
You know Padaman better than that.
Hey, why don't we try looking over there?
Another winner!
So will you give me a few?
What, again?
I'll pay you back, I promise!
You'll pay me back with what?
With what I'm about to win!
But you never win!
I'm hot tonight!
Hey, you two!
You kids just don't get the message!
Get out and stay!
If you have to try sneaking in here
dressed as cartoon characters,
at least get a decent costume!
Boy, it's a good thing we were just about
to leave!
We teach you some manners!
What did you just say?
Uh-oh, oh boy!
And I told her, don't get the fuchsia lip
gloss whatever you do!
It's so bad!
Whoa!
I think you knocked over a monster!
Even worse, I think I knocked over a
teenager!
I've heard about these strange looking
creatures.
Hey, it takes one to know one!
Excuse me!
Do you know what time it is?
Time for new clothes!
Get lost, you creeps!
And what's with the costumes?
Aren't you guys a little late for
Halloween?
What's Halloween?
I don't think I like these teenage things!
Me either.
Maybe I can reprogram her if I pull out
her safety mechanism.
Come back here, you little mutants!
This teenage thing is gonna teach you some
manners!
Huh?
Uh-huh!
Hold it right there!
Why are you two in such a hurry?
Do you know these guys?
I sure do!
They work for Myotismon!
Uh-huh!
You're right!
But right now we're being chased by
something even scarier than Myotismon!
Huh?
There's a really mad teenage human after
us!
Come to think of it, you'd better hide
too!
Come on!
Ugh!
You can run, but you can't hide dressed in
those stupid costumes!
Where are they?
Uh, they went that way.
Thanks!
I think I know why you two troublemakers
are in the real world.
Did Myotismon happen to send you here to
find someone?
Yeah!
That 8th DigiDestined kid!
Huh!
Then you're our enemy!
No, we're not!
We just want to cruise around the city and
have some fun!
Well, we thought you two were Evil
Digimon!
Evil shmeevil!
We love it here!
In fact, next stop, Hollywood!
Ah!
They're not ready for TV.
Typical.
Everybody wants to be in show business.
Lights, cameras, and action!
Ugh!
Hey!
There's some light!
Yeah!
Whoa!
What are they doing up there?
Hey!
Get down!
Stop!
That's enough!
That's not funny!
It's me!
Sirens!
Get down or the police will arrest you!
We better get out of here, guys!
Let's run!
Did he just say let's run?
Sure!
Wait for us!
Hey!
Where are Pumpkinmon and Gatsumon?
They were right behind us!
They must have gotten lost or something!
Those two!
Even when they're found, they're lost!
Oh!
Sweetie!
Ta-da!
Man oh man!
I think this one makes me look fat,
but what do you think?
Well then, let's switch!
You guys need to change your attitude!
You need to change your clothes!
Oh wow!
This look says you're not afraid to think
big!
Here's a sporty look!
Of course, I haven't figured out what
sport it is yet!
And finally, something nice and a little
teddy!
Well, what do you think?
Oh!
Hey!
Patamon!
Patamon, come back!
So should we follow those guys?
And why not?
Do you see him anywhere, Matt?
No.
Looks like we lost him again, TK.
Patamon doesn't usually hold a grudge,
but he was mad as a bull with a black gear!
Hey now, don't look so bummed out!
Yeah, I'm sure you'll find your little
flying pig friend somewhere!
Maybe some ice cream will cheer you all
up, huh?
What?
You guys don't have any money,
so how did you get ice cream?
We stole it!
I can't believe you two!
Everywhere you guys go, there's trouble!
The next time you two get someone angry,
make sure they can't run very fast!
So, want some ice cream?
Not me.
You stole it!
Gabamon won't take it either, right?
Ice cream... yeah... Gabamon!
Gabamon!
My otis man!
Losers.
Failures.
No, no.
Don't say that!
Instead of causing pain and suffering,
I find you here, eating ice cream.
Well, it is stolen!
I don't care about ice cream!
Have you found the eighth Diggie Destined
child yet?
Well, we were about to find him.
Redeem yourselves by stealing the crests
from these children or else.
No problem, boss.
That's just what we were about to do.
Can you believe those truths turning on
us?
And I thought Pumpkinmon and Gatsummon
only wanted to have fun, not fight.
I suppose they'd rather fight us than
fight Myotismon.
I just can't stay mad at TK anymore.
Besides, I really miss him.
So I told Rebecca and Sarah to just find
us at the park later.
That'll work.
It's like, it's so easy to find somebody
at the park.
Yeah, it's totally easy to find somebody
there.
Oh, in the park.
Whoa!
Hey, how'd you do that?
Aren't I amazing?
Well, you might make a nice pie.
Come on, let's turn around.
Whoa!
Huh?
I don't think so.
We're surrounded.
Sorry we have to do this to you guys.
But orders are orders.
You understand.
All right, if it's a fight you want,
let's do it.
Uh, I quit.
Ah, me too.
Huh?
Why should we fight?
Somebody always gets hurt.
Besides, it's way more fun just hanging
out and cruising around the city.
That's for sure.
Hey, why don't you guys hang out with us?
Huh?
Whoa!
My Otisman's coming.
You should all hide.
Quiet.
Where are the Digi destined?
Uh, they were here just a second ago.
They must have got away.
Yeah!
You can't believe how fast they are,
but we almost had them, boss.
Yes.
I can imagine.
You had your chance.
Now I'm condemning you to my dungeon in
the Digi-World.
Grizzly wings!
Pumpkinmon power!
Pumpkinmon!
Gatsumon!
Don't watch!
Well, that wasn't very difficult.
Now it's your turn.
Those two, they were really trying to save
us.
You're right.
Oh, and you just condemned them for no
reason at all!
Digimon!
He should pay for what he did to those
two!
Crimson Lightning!
Wait a minute.
Those guys just wanted to be our friends.
Garuruma!
One!
Diddy ball!
Two!
We're Garuruma!
Go and get him!
Those girls said the park was the place to
find someone, but where's TK?
They're up there!
Oh no, look out!
Crimson lightning!
We're Garuruma!
We're Garuruma's in big trouble,
and it's all my fault!
If I hadn't been so mean,
Patamon would still be with
us, and we would have never
met Punkimon and Gatsumon!
And if those poor guys
had never met up with
us, they wouldn't be
stuck where they are now!
Oh...
Digimon!
It's mine!
Angemon!
Digimon!
Digimon!幹 couple monsters!
Ah!
Mon,
are you all right, we're Gururuman?
Yes, thanks to you I am.
Anjumon rules!
Well, I guess we don't have to look for
Patamon anymore.
Hmm, Anjumon, they must be desperate if
they sent you.
Anjumon, shall we take him?
Let's go.
Hey, Digimon, hey, Digimon.
Monster friends to the boys and girls.
Champions of the digital world.
It's time I take my lead.
We will fight again.
Hey, Digimon, hey, Digimon.
Champions of the digital world.
I hope they're all right.
Me too.
Gabumon?
Huh?!
Oh, oh!
Padamon?
Are you okay?
Yes.
I'm all right now, TK.
I'm sorry, Padamon.
I'm sorry I got mad.
Don't cry, TK.
It's all right.
Hey, look at that window!
That's were those crazy Digimon tried on
all the clothes, remember?
Look out!
We're going Hollywood!
Ta-da!
Come on, have some ice cream, guys.
Yeah, it was a steal!
They were funny.
I know what you mean, TK.
I miss them, too.
I guess we shouldn't take our friends for
granted.
TK nearly lost Panamon's
friendship, and who knows
if we'll ever see Pumpkinmon
and Gatsumon again.
But one thing's for sure.
I know Myotismon isn't through with us
yet.
His henchmen are out there right now,
searching for the Eighth Digi-Destined.
You may be sweet, little Kari, but
next time I will get my claws into you.
Will Kari survive her
next encounter with
Gatoman, Iotismon,
Iotismon's most loyal servant?
Find out on the next Digimon Digital
Monsters.
That's okay with Edmonds.
That thing falls...