Calm down, Matt.
Don't get so bent out of shape.
The last thing we need right now is a hot
head with attitude.
We've got more important things to think
about.
Everyone's upset.
Look, all I know is that this stupid
bickering is giving me a gigantic headache.
Chill out.
Matt, have you forgotten that we have been
chosen to be the Digi-Destined?
Hmph.
And would you mind telling me who exactly
chose us for this dumb job anyway?
I, uh... Come on, I want some answers
and you can't seem to give them to me.
You have a point there.
But, uh... Don't
waste your time, Joe.
Matt's just being a big spoiled brat.
You're the brat?
Why don't you go mind your own business?
The problem with you is pretty easy to
figure out.
You're upset because you want to be the
boss.
Yeah, like I want to be boss of this sorry
group.
If any of you brainiacs want to take
charge, be my guest.
I say we should just take care of
ourselves.
Stop fighting, you two.
We've got to stick together.
Don't look at me.
Matt's the one who started it.
He's got a bug up his nose.
Hmph.
I don't have to listen to this.
Bug up the nose, that's a bad thing?
One moment.
Don't push me too far.
Oh, I'm scared.
You had better be scared.
I'm getting really mad.
Excuse me, but what are you going to do
about it?
So, those little twerps are about to
self-destruct.
I'll just sit back and enjoy the show.
Stay right there.
Get real, dude.
Watch it.
Stand back.
Digiball.
Oglebomb.
Orp.
Digiball.
Whoop.
Pilot jump jump.
Orp.
Digiball.
There is no need for us to fight.
I must.
What's the matter, you chicken?
That's it.
Matt, I'm going to tell Mom that you are
fighting.
Sorry, TK, but I have to do this.
Both of you stop it right now.
It's ridiculous.
You two are just making things worse.
He's got to be taught a lesson and fast.
Here, take this.
I'm only doing this to honor the memory of
all the brave Digimon that have helped us.
They trusted us and believed in our
commitment.
We can't let them down.
What if we made a mistake?
This is awful.
We have to stop.
And there's nothing any of us can do about
it.
Best thing is for them to duke it out.
I just hate fighting and we can't let our
friends destroy themselves.
It's a dog-eat-dog world, isn't it?
They're not dogs.
The deal is this.
We just sit and watch them take care of
business.
Oh, yeah?
I don't have to like it.
Goomomon, get a grip.
The last thing we need is any more
fighting around here.
Ah, I'm a genius.
They're all gonna have...
Terra Force!
I
have a good fight!
I've had...
Oh, like that's gonna help.
Metal... Well, maybe a little.
Oh... My name's Kari.
Please tell me who you are.
Do you wanna be friends with us?
What in the Digi World is she doing?
She appears to be conversing with herself.
She's losing it.
You seem to be nice enough.
Kari!
What's happening?
In this world, there is a balance of
darkness and light.
The light represents all that's good in
the world, and the darkness is the evil.
When the darkness becomes larger than the
light, it upsets the balance.
Whoa!
The balance seems to be really out of
whack.
So, somebody find a switch and put the
lights back on.
There's something over there!
I know this sounds incredible,
but could we be home again?
I've seen that Digimon before!
Why, of course!
That's Parrotmon!
He was the mysterious
Digimon that appeared in
Heightened View Terrace
approximately four years ago.
Now he's completely Digivolved!
He passed through the dimensional divide.
Some time ago, a digi-egg fell through a
hole from our world to yours.
Kari, what are you talking about?
I think Kari's had too much catnip.
My theory is that someone else is using
Kari's body to speak for them.
My wish is that there be peace and
happiness for everyone.
I don't understand.
Are you some kind of super being or
something?
No, nothing like that.
I am similar to the Digimon.
I was produced by data bytes taken from
the internet.
But there's a difference.
Unlike the Digimon, we're unable to take a
shake in the form of a physical body.
In order for me to communicate to you,
I had to temporarily borrow Kari.
Couldn't you have taken Joe instead?
Hey!
I had to take Kari.
She's the only one that I'm able to
communicate with.
To be honest, I wanted to contact you when
you arrived at File Island, but it was
completely impossible under the
circumstances.
Wow!
Wow, it's a blast from the past.
That's us four years ago.
Hey, that's me.
How typical.
I'm on the telephone.
I was so cute.
Hard to believe we were that little.
There's my brother and me.
That's definitely me.
But what's with the light?
Its purpose is to process all of your
vital information.
That's kind of freaky.
Why is it doing that?
Just follow me.
I'll explain it to you.
Here we go again!
Where are we now?
Whoever you are.
A rather bizarre place indeed.
Check this out!
Crests and digivices!
Okay, this is getting weird.
Oh, and floating in the sky is normal?
Okay, it's official.
This is definitely giving me the creeps.
What's the matter, fellas?
Can't you say hello?
These men are just computer images.
They are figments from the past who have
been digitally transmitted to your present.
I don't believe it!
This is from Myotismund's castle!
Here's Myotismund's secret passage!
Let me guess.
Those are the elves that make the shoes at
night.
They're monitoring the positive and negative
forces to preserve harmony in the world.
We took the information that we scanned
from all of you.
Then we created your digivices and crests.
You did that?
That must mean that you're the ones who
chose us.
Is that true?
Yes, it is.
Then tell me this.
What makes us so special?
You made it possible for Greymon to
survive and digivolve and it couldn't have
been accomplished without help from you
and Kari.
But he digivolved without me.
A digimon can't digivolve without you.
It doesn't work that way.
The very fact that you were both there
made him digivolve in order to protect you.
But how?
We were just goofy little kids and we
didn't even have a digivice.
A digivice is just a tool that was designed
to help in the digivolving process.
It assists you by making you
aware of your powers, but it's
the special qualities in each
of you that really makes it work.
The same thing with the crests.
Can you tell me what your personal crests
really represent?
Well, mine's courage.
And this one means love.
Sincerity.
Mine's knowledge.
Reliability.
I know what this crest means.
It's hope.
Well, mine is... Wasn't
it called friendship?
All of that's true, but there's more to it
than that.
Every one of you has strengths and
weaknesses.
We took each of your strongest qualities
that you possessed four years ago.
Then we made a crest for them.
Oh, I get it.
If that trait is lost, then a digimon
might become corrupted.
That happened.
When I tried to make Agumon digivolve by
throwing myself in front of his enemy.
But then something weird happened.
He digivolved into Skull Greymon.
And now I realize that was pretty foolish.
But the important thing is, is that you
learned from it.
All this time we've been
racking our brains trying to
figure out stuff about
ourselves that we already knew.
Huh?
That's a fine howdy-do.
Oh no!
Pro-digis!
I see why you chose Tai and Kari.
But the rest of us never made contact with
the digi-egg.
So why us?
When we examined all your
data, we came to the conclusion
that you had something in
common with Tai and Kari.
But we're not quite sure what it means.
All we know is that you've proven
yourselves to be very capable.
Who do these belong to, huh?
Isn't it obvious?
I have a feeling it's us!
Yes.
Wow!
Which one's me?
I think the answer's in the crests.
Look!
This is me!
And that's mine!
Yes, but I'm afraid I have bad news.
The Dark Masters got wind of our plan and
have worked very hard to defeat us.
Save your breath.
They're computer images.
What?
Just because those guys are computer
images, we have to sit back and do nothing?
His name is Gardramon.
He's a machine digimon, and his armor is
constructed of solid iron.
Absolutely nothing can penetrate that can
of beans.
Here comes some more of them!
This is no space age vacuum cleaner!
Meet Mecha-norimon!
His twin beam will annihilate anything!
Which makes housework a breeze.
Ah!
Piemon is here!
Don't come any closer!
Shoo!
Go away!
Relax, it's just an image.
Yeah, Savior's screaming for the real
thing.
He's going to steal the crests!
Oh, no!
Ah!
Piemon!
Hands off those crests!
Jedi!
That man's Jedi?
Follow him!
Don't let Jedi out of your sight!
Let's follow and see what happened in the
past.
That's my digi-egg!
So that's why I was brought up all alone.
That explains it.
Cheer up!
We're together now!
It's Fire Island!
After Jedi rescued the digi-eggs and crests,
many years passed by... until finally...
I was born!
Oh!
Matt!
For Sarah!
For Joe!
For Mimi!
For Dickie!
For Ezra!
We didn't think they would ever come!
Then suddenly, out of the blue,
they arrived with a bang!
The question is, what exactly are the Dark
Masters planning?
We are working day and night trying to
find out.
For now, all we can
do is guess, and try to
outwit them before
something terrible happens.
Whoa!
Well, if that's true, what should we do
now?
It's hard to say, but I believe you'll all
find an answer on your own.
Oh!
Hey!
Are you gonna be alright?
Oh, hi there!
What's wrong?
You've come back!
We missed you!
Did it hurt?
No.
What do you mean?
Don't you remember?
Well, that's alright.
Remember what, Tai?
Never mind, Kari.
Don't you worry about it.
Well, Matt, there's no doubt about how we
became the Digi-Destined.
We saw it happen.
We sure did.
So now the entire world is depending on
us.
And we all have to save it together.
How about it, Matt?
Are we still a team?
What's wrong?
Hey, let's put the path behind us.
I know, but you wouldn't understand.
Sure I would.
I say that you and I should let bygones be
bygones.
That's not the problem, Tai.
This thing is bigger than either of us.
It's not about right or wrong.
I have my path and you have yours.
And I'm not even sure
where this path is going to
lead me, but I know I
have to find it for myself.
But I still believe in all of us.
I mean, without any of you, where would I
be?
This is all just so confusing.
And I let it get to me.
That's why we fought.
It's important that you
guys can count on me,
but I'm going to do
this because I have to.
Soon Omon will be with me, so I'll be
alright.
Don't worry.
It'll be a lot better this way.
Matt, if you approach this logically,
I'm sure you'll reconsider your decision.
Your crest.
Its theme is to promote...
Friendship, I know.
But I haven't been too much of a friend,
in case you haven't noticed.
Maybe it's because I
don't know the true meaning
of the word, or maybe
I've just forgotten.
Here's a good idea.
Let's break up into two groups instead of
one big one.
I'm sorry, but I really need to do this
alone.
Oh.
Well, I believe in you, and I'm not going
to stand in your way.
What am I supposed to do without you,
Matt?
You're a big kid now.
You can take care of yourself,
TK.
Yeah, but... Don't worry.
We'll be here for you.
Besides, you know how big brothers are.
They need their own space.
Everything will be fine.
Hmm.
We'll see ya.
Goodbye, everyone.
We better move it, troops.
We've got the world to save.
So we're down one digi-destined.
That's no problem.
We can do it, right?
Hmm?
Mimi?
I'm sorry, Sora.
I'm not going.
Huh?
Why not?
Come on, what?
Well, I just don't want to see anybody
else fight or hurt themselves.
I hope you understand.
Then I'm staying too.
But why?
It's not safe for Mimi to be here all
alone.
I'll make sure she's okay, and then
hopefully later we can rejoin you guys.
Okay?
Okay.
Good luck, Joe.
Thanks.
Wait for me!
Gee, now we're all going to be split up
again.
Just when we were finally all together.
You may think we're separated,
but we're really not.
Huh?
The roads might be different, but the
place we end up in is the same.
I mean, think about it.
If they truly are the digi-destined,
they're destined to be together once again.
At least, that's the way I hope it works
out.
Is Gatomon right?
Or is this the end of the digi-destined?
Tune in to the next Digimon Digital
Monsters.