And you...
Anju-a-man!
Magnum Anju-mon!
Mega Garbuterian!
Pseudomon!
Come
on, footage mom, Phil!
Pseudomon!
Metal Garbu-man!
What?
You're dealing with the new and improved
DigiDestined!
That's impossible!
How can you DigiBall without your crests?
Nothing's impossible.
At least not when you've got your friends
helping you.
You said it, Madden.
Now, time to fight!
Yeah!
They're doomed!
So you wanna fight?
Deathclaw!
Malkan's Hammer!
All right!
Your hammer nailed it!
We can help out too, right, Lilliman?
Hang on!
Hang on for a while!
Flower unit!
Next time, Lilliman, can you use someone
else as a boomerang?
Sorry, but I wanted to make sure you came
back to me.
Malkan's Hammer!
Ty!
Now's your chance to go for his body!
All right!
Huh?
Joe!
Mimi, look out behind you!
Huh?
Gate of Destiny!
Celestial Arrow!
Tattoo!
We'll go for the other claws, too!
Thanks, Kari!
We owe you one!
Matt, this is better than any video game!
I'll say!
Deathclaw!
Flower Cannon!
Hey!
Why should you guys have all the fun?
Save some for me and Izzy!
We'll distract Apokalomon while Matt and
Ty concentrate on attacking!
Watch our backs!
Let's end this!
Virus Grenades!
Mega Cavalier Moth, protect Sara!
Got it!
Winged Bride!
Thanks, guys!
Giga Cannon!
Now it's my turn!
Horn Buster!
Attack!
Now!
Metal Wolf Blonde!
Terra Force!
Did it!
We destroyed all of his claws!
Still think you're so tough!
Is that your best shot?
You know you're beaten!
Face it like a mom!
You think so, huh?
Though I may be beaten, but I won't go
down that easily!
I'll take you and both worlds with me!
What?
You still haven't seen my ultimate attack!
Total Annihilation!
He's gonna destroy everything!
They should've made out my will!
I'm too good looking to go!
I want my mommy!
There must be a solution!
We won't give up!
We're stronger than he is!
We're a team!
It's destiny!
After all!
We're the Digi-Destins!
What was that?
I'm not sure!
What happened to the explosion?
It was completely contained by the power
of our Digi-Vices!
Then it's over!
We actually won!
Looks that way!
Excuse me while I throw up!
I guess we saved the world!
Mm-hmm!
Hey!
You did it!
You're amazing!
Remind me to call you the next time I have
trouble with my landlord!
It was nothing!
Thanks!
For everything!
Well, I did have some help, you know!
Great, bro!
I'm proud of you!
Sorry I'm late!
Forgot to set my alarm!
Is it over?
Yeah!
So what's gonna happen to the digital
world now?
See for yourselves!
Look down!
Huh?
It's Vile Island!
The ancient prophecy said
that after the great darkness
is over, the first thing to
be reborn will be the island.
And from that island will come the land
and the seas.
Yeah, but what does that mean?
It means that the Digi-World will start
over from the beginning.
What's happening down there?
The Digi-World is being reborn,
as are all the Digimon from the past.
We're gonna need a lot of diapers.
Huh?
All right, let's go!
Right!
It's the primary village!
And everything's back to normal!
Looks like it's starting to rain!
Ugh!
A Digi-Egg storm!
Wait, those eggs are my responsibility!
Are you gonna count them all?
Are you crazy?
You never count your Digi-Eggs before they
hatch!
What are you doing?
Helping these Digi-Eggs hatch!
Are you gonna hatch them all?
What do you suggest?
We make an omelet?
Of course we're going to hatch them all!
The future of the Digi-World depends on
it!
Yay!
You can help!
Just rub them gently!
This is fun!
We should be done in about 60 years!
This means Leomont will be reborn!
That's right!
And Pixiemon, Waymon, and Wizardmon too!
Yes, someday.
We should take a picture!
To commemorate this special occasion!
A picture?
Good idea!
Sure, let's do it!
Yeah, I'm in!
Great!
I'll go get TK and Kari then!
I'll shine my head!
Alright, we're ready!
Say cheese!
Huh?
What's wrong?
Oh!
What is it?
Look, it hatched!
It's so cute!
I'm out of here!
Huh?
What do you mean you're leaving?
It's time to hit the road!
Take a hike!
Make like a tree and leave!
But Ogremon, why not stay here with us?
Look, I'm a virus type Digimon.
You guys are data and vaccine types.
If I hang around here too long,
I'll get sick to my stomach!
Catch you later!
He vanished!
He just can't face the fact that he likes
us!
Hmm, I've never heard of a virus giving
someone a cold shoulder.
Don't say that.
Do you remember the day that Ogremon first
digivolved into Skullgreymon?
At the time, I said it was the wrong thing
to do.
But the truth is, when it comes to
digivolving, there's no right or wrong.
A Digimon's destiny cannot be changed.
That day was a real eye-opener for me.
Of course, I haven't been able to open
them since.
Well, if that's the
case, then next time I'll
just digivolve myself
into the next Dark Master!
No, no, no, no!
This sure brings back a lot of memories.
This is the exact spot where we spent our
first night here in the DigiWorld.
That's right!
This is where Gabumon first digivolved
into Garurumon and bought Sidramon.
Yeah, and this is the place where I
fainted for the first time.
Well, the first time in the DigiWorld,
anyway.
Boy, it sure is great strolling down
memory lane, isn't it?
Hey, do you think when we all get back,
we'll be some kind of heroes?
And win a whole bunch of awards,
like an Emmy or something?
Chill!
Sorry.
Oh, don't be me.
Open mouth, insert foot.
I mean, we can always come back,
right guys?
Right?
Chill!
Oh, I forgot.
Faux pas.
Time passes differently here than in our
world.
You guys will probably be long gone.
Whoops, there goes the other foot.
Hey!
You know, we've still got a lot of summer
left.
I was thinking, maybe we could stay here
until our vacation's over.
Yeah!
That's a great idea!
If Matt's staying, I'm staying too!
Me too!
Is that okay, Ty?
Sure!
I'm staying too!
Me too!
We might as well.
We've got plenty of time.
Since an entire day in the digital world
is equal to just one minute in the real
world, and we've still got four weeks left
of summer vacation...
Then we can stay here in the
digital world for up to... Let's see...
Carry the four, divide by
three... A really, really long time!
To be precise!
It's 40,320 days!
That's about 110 years!
Alright!
We're staying!
Yay!
Hey, look!
It's an eclipse!
Yes, it is!
And there's something very important you
should know about it, children!
I know!
You're not supposed to look directly into
it!
True!
That's not all!
This eclipse could cost you your lives!
You mean it's not an ordinary eclipse?
That shadow is the gate that connects your
world to the digital world!
I'm afraid the eclipse will only last for
two more hours!
That's not a problem!
We'll just wait until it opens up again!
Yeah!
After all, we still have over a hundred
years of summer vacation left!
Actually, when Apoclamon
appeared, the flow of
time here and in your
world became synchronized!
So, then we still have four weeks left,
right?
That's plenty of time to have fun!
Well, actually, you only have the two
hours, because once the portal is closed,
it's closed forever!
But... Sorry, it's
time to say goodbye!
Aww!
I'm sure gonna miss you, Sora!
Say hi to your mom for me when you get
back!
Sure!
I wanna thank you, Biomon!
Before I met you, I didn't get along with
my mom very well!
We argued!
She would never let me do anything!
But thanks to you, I understand her a lot
better!
You showed me how much my mom really loves
me!
You mean it?
Of course!
That makes me so happy to hear you say
that!
Sometimes I thought I was just bothering
you and getting in your way all the time!
Don't be silly!
You weren't a bother!
You're my best friend!
Oh, Biomon, I'm gonna miss you so much!
I know it's gonna be
hard to find a friend as
great as I am, Gomomon,
but you'll have to try!
Not a problem!
I took an ad out in the personals!
I've got five interviews lined up for next
week!
Hmm... What?
At least let's shake hands!
Okay, for luck!
Wow!
What?
For someone without a hand, you've got a
pretty strong grip!
Tentamon?
Yes, Izzy?
There's something I need to tell you
before we part ways.
Okay?
I love you!
Tentamon!
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine, but I was a little taken
aback by your sudden display of emotion.
You're right.
Sorry about that.
I don't usually get emotional,
but this was a unique occasion.
I understand.
You don't have to say it.
I know how much our friendship has meant
to us.
And in the name of our friendship,
I need to ask you one last favor.
Yeah, what is it?
Would you please turn off those windshield
wipers?
Sure thing, pal.
Anything for you.
Give me a hug.
You're choking me!
You're
crying, and neither one of us needs to be
crying.
Besides, I'm sure we're gonna see each
other again one day.
Yeah, just like we saw each other again
after that thing with Debbie Wong.
That's right, we did.
Let's make a pact.
We'll see each other again.
Promise?
Hmm.
That says it all.
I wouldn't mind hearing you play your
harmonica one last time.
Glad to.
Stupid madness harmonica.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
Yeah.
Sure.
Hey, come over here and look at this!
This is the spot where I first made my
pepper breath!
Remember?
How could I ever forget?
That's where you burned Sidramon's tail
and he attacked us!
And your aim hasn't gotten much better
since then either!
Hey!
You don't really believe that,
do you?
Hmm... Well, look
at the bright side.
Your aim hasn't gotten any worse.
Come on, Ty!
For me?
Uh-huh.
Here, let me put it on you.
It doubles as a flea collar.
Thanks, Kari.
It looks good on you.
Gee, thanks!
Oh well, I guess this is... goodbye.
Yeah.
Till next time.
Next time?
Yep, that's right!
Huh?
Palmon!
Where are you?
I want to say goodbye!
Huh?
Princess Mimi, what are you doing?
Palmon's disappeared.
Have you seen her?
Not recently.
Sorry.
I don't understand how she could leave at
a time like this.
There's only a few minutes left.
Palmon!
Where are you?
I'm leaving soon!
Mimi.
Have you all finished saying your
goodbyes?
You can take this cable car home on one
condition.
You have to promise to bring it back to
San Francisco where I borrowed it from.
Well, uh...
Can't we just have a little more time?
Please, Jen, I do something!
I'm sorry, Sora.
The gate won't wait any longer.
What's the problem?
Palmon seems to have disappeared!
Why would she run away?
Why?
Palmon, so that's where you're hiding!
Mimi's been looking for you!
Yes, I know.
But I don't want to see her.
I don't understand!
It's simple.
If I don't see her, then she can never say
goodbye to me!
Is that what you really want?
I'm afraid you'll regret it one day.
It's too painful to say goodbye.
I'm sorry, Mimi.
We can't wait for Palmon any longer.
It's time.
Get on the cable car, everyone.
Come on.
Come on, let's go.
Well, guys, this is it.
What can I say?
Try goodbye.
Don't let anyone push you around!
Make sure you dress up!
Make it easy!
Bye!
I'm sorry!
It's okay!
Don't worry about it!
Goodbye, Palmon!
And thanks for everything!
I love you!
Goodbye, Mimi!
Bye!
Monster friends to the boys and girls!
Hey, Digimon!
Ultimate friends to the boys and girls!
Champions of the Digital World!
Seven young kids go to camp for the summer
We'll wind up living in a digital land
Where everybody gets to meet his own
Digimonster A digital companion,
a digital friend A Digimon in training,
we'll digivop to rookie And Digivop to
champion and ultimate too Are gonna save
the digital world for me Are gonna save
the digital world for you Hey,
Digimon!
Hey, Digimon!
Monster friends to the boys and girls.
Champions of the digital world.
Hey, Digimon!
Ultimate friends to the boys and girls.
Champions of the digital world.
Our adventure in the
digital world might be over
for now, but that gate
won't stay closed forever.
I have a feeling that this won't be the
last time we see our pals the Digimon.
You wait and see.
One day that portal will open up again and
we'll return to the digital world.
I wonder if Agumon will remember me.
I know I'll never forget him or the rest
of the Digimon.
None of us will.