Genai really threw us for a
loop when he told us there
was an eighth child and
it was up to us to find him.
We were just about to pass through the
gate that would take us into the human
world when we were rudely interrupted by a
trouble-making Digimon called Gatomon.
Talk about your bad luck!
The door closed right in our faces!
Now that pestering feline
is off to find the missing
child and we're stuck here,
not knowing what to do.
Somehow we have to find a way to open that
gate, but how?
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Change into Digital Champions to save the
digital world!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Digimon, N2 champions!
Are the champions!
Digimon!
Digital monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Digimon!
Iota's man has shut the gate.
You can't follow him now.
Listen, Pops, you've got to help us get
through that gate.
The eighth kid is doomed if we don't.
And that isn't all.
If that rotten creep
goes on a rampage in the
real world, lots of innocent
people will get hurt.
There just has to be some way we can open
the gate up again!
Well, of course there is.
No kidding?
How then?
Any door can be opened with the right
keys.
Oh, don't be so mysterious, Jedi!
Follow me to my house and I will explain
everything.
Where's that?
Look above you!
What kind of directions are those?
Very good ones if you will just listen.
Huh?
Keep looking and you shall see it.
There!
A searchlight!
Sorry I ran out of maps.
Follow the light and you can't miss it.
Excellent!
Snack time for me.
Let's jet!
Looks like we're gonna be doing a little
swimming.
My hat!
My beautiful hat!
Either we got those directions really wrong
or Jedi's house is in the middle of a lake.
So that's why I've never found it.
Must be really tough to get pizza
delivered.
Hmm?
Hey, come on in!
The water's fine!
Oh no!
Huh?
Steps?
All right gang, we're in business!
There are stairs going right down into the
lake.
They must lead to Jedi's house.
Well, what are we waiting for?
I was kinda hoping we'd send a boat to
make us up.
Hey!
If anyone wants any sushi, now's your
chance!
I wish I had my boats!
Me too!
Quite a place, if you don't mind living in
Pink Bob.
No long, Domo.
I don't see a doorbell.
Hey, Mr. Jedi!
We're here!
Hey!
Who needs a doorbell with such noisy
visitors?
Huh?
It's the real Jedi!
Who did you expect?
Santa Claus?
We've just never seen the real you!
Yeah!
So tell us!
How come you're always hiding?
I'm not!
Well, you could've come in person,
but you always choose projections, right?
It's just a show to impress you.
What kind of a person are you,
anyway?
A human?
Or some kind of Digimon?
That is not important.
How come you call us the Digi-destined?
Easy, I'm old, but I'm not deaf.
You were chosen to save this world and
your own.
But just how were we chosen?
Why us?
Yeah, we only signed up for summer camp.
That is all you need to know for now.
Come inside.
The most important thing is to return to
your world and find the eighth child.
That, and maybe have a nice bowl of soup
with a tuna sandwich.
Look at the fish!
But those are halibut.
They're saltwater fish.
You are right.
So I have to feed them popcorn and salty
pretzels and tons of salted nuts.
Do you think he's pulling our legs?
I have no idea.
Now a look at the weather.
State, county, city.
Does anyone recognize this area?
Our hometown?
Mm-hmm.
And the red flashing circle indicates.
Myotismon's location.
Myotismon!
Wow, he's only a mile from where we all
live.
I'm afraid so.
I'll bet you that he goes downtown.
This is not good.
What'd you find?
Nothing.
The table's fine.
So what's causing all this interference?
Please tell us how to open the gate back
to our world.
You certainly are impatient.
Keep your goggles on, my young friend.
You'll need these.
Check them out!
Whoa!
Digimon key cards.
It's the spinning image.
All right, look at Gomamon.
I'm cuter in person.
There I am, too!
But what are they for?
Yeah, and how do they help us open the
gate?
Well, there are nine holes on the stone
wall of the gate.
Yeah, so... Oh, wait!
Do the cards go into the holes?
That's right.
However, take a closer look.
It's not quite as simple as that.
Do you see the problem?
You're giving us one too many cards.
That's right.
One of them is a fake.
Oh!
We'll try them all.
Till we get the right combination.
No, you will not, you silly boy.
That's absolutely the last thing you
should do.
There are many, many other worlds.
If you put the cards in the wrong holes,
it'll be a disaster.
You could end up in a different world with
no way to return.
Let me explain.
The wrong cards might
take you to a world where,
for example, people
in Digimon switch skins.
No!
Not that!
I like my skin!
Don't worry, don't worry!
You're not going to switch
your skin with anyone as
long as you learn how
to use the cards correctly.
But we don't have any idea what to do.
You must learn to use your power the way
Myotismon is using his.
Tomorrow I'll teach you the proper use of
the cards.
The digital world is like our world,
but different.
Why is that?
The same material is used in all worlds.
Molecules and atoms?
Exactly!
Everything here in the digital world,
plants, trees, buildings, even the Digimon
themselves came from computer data in your
world.
So if there are strange things here, they
are the result of broken or missing data.
What about you, Geni?
Are you just made up of computer data,
too?
Of course!
So in each of the worlds, I would appear
somewhat different.
But Geni, if you're not human,
how are you different from Digimon?
I have no attributes.
Attributes?
Just what does that mean?
You mean the different attacks Digimon
have?
Yes!
And the way a Digimon digivolves.
But attributes determine much more than
that.
They explain why some Digimon are good and
some are evil.
All Digimon can be classified as data,
virus or vaccine.
We're definitely familiar with the virus
kind.
By the way, have you used that Digimon
analyzer I gave you?
Yes, but there is something I wanted to
ask you about it.
What's that?
I'm only able to access information on
Digimon that I have seen.
Not on the ones that the other kids have
seen.
Hmm, you're right.
That is a problem.
Is it one that you can solve?
You just leave it to me, my young friend.
I should have it all taken care of by
morning.
But for now, you had better get some rest.
Okay.
Wow, Joe.
Why not just eat the bones, too?
Hey, I was hungry.
Huh?
Good morning, all.
Hi.
Izzy, I completed the modifications for
your computer.
When you insert someone's Digivice into
this adapter, the analyzer will show
information on any Digimon that person has
seen.
I also installed a new screensaver.
You know, the one with the colored fishes
swimming around?
I really like that one.
Great minds do think alike.
And now I have a request for all of you.
I don't want you to forget that you are
the Digi-destined.
I'll never forget this stomachache.
Joe, this is serious.
I have done all I can do.
I can no longer help you once you return
to my Otismon's castle.
Good luck.
Man, this place looks even scarier than it
did the first time.
How do we get past the DaVidramon?
Leave that to me.
I'll take him out while you go in.
Mm-hmm.
Digimon!
Mega Kabuterimon!
Let's go!
Now's our chance!
Hornbuster!
Oh, so much for a quiet entrance.
What happened, Issa?
Everything's turned all right side up
again.
You fix the warp in space.
Come on, let's get to the gate!
We've got to figure out the pattern in
these cards.
Hmm.
What?
A clue?
Good one?
Bad one?
Funky one?
Maybe... In-training,
rookie, and champion?
Or could it just be small one,
medium one, big one?
How can we be sure?
And we still don't have a clue which card
has the fake one.
Maybe it's where they live.
Water or land?
Maybe the key is in their names.
Like, Agamon starts with A.
That's letter number one.
Then... Oh, no.
It really doesn't make any sense.
Izzy, what are you looking at?
My Otismon used a spell to open the gate.
And I think this picture must have
something to do with it.
Some of these characters I know.
Sagittarius and Leo are signs of the
zodiac.
But there's nothing about a monkey in any
horoscope.
And what's the significance of this star
pattern?
What's that spell?
I don't know.
Well, maybe somebody should go take us.
I'll go find out.
Come on, guys.
We have to figure out the cards.
Yeah.
Let's go.
What's the point?
We'll never unlock the gate.
Don't even say that, Joe.
Even if we put the cards
in the holes so they look
right, we have no way of
knowing until it's too late.
We have to try, Joe.
Something tells me we don't have much
time.
Hey, everyone.
The walls and ceilings in the castle are
caving in.
The passages are all blocked.
That means we can't go back the way we
came in.
We're trapped.
Now we have to open the gate.
One of us has to choose nine cards and put
them in the holes, and that'll be that.
You, Ty.
Me?
Yeah, it's your call.
Mine?
Why is it up to me?
I'm not trying to put you on the spot or
anything like that.
I just think we all really believe in you.
Ty?
Me?
Joe's right.
In times like these, decisions need to be
made by the one in charge.
Hold on.
Have you guys all gone crazy?
Who made me a leader?
Do you remember when you were gone,
Ty?
We fell apart without you around.
And after all that,
weren't you the one who
managed to bring us
all back together again?
Uh, yeah, I guess.
Just do it, Ty!
Uh-huh.
Mimi?
I just want to get back to my home,
that's all!
Oh!
I'm sorry.
I was being selfish again.
I have to remember we're a team.
Come on, Ty.
Save the day!
Yeah, we have to believe in our friends.
Remember what Jenai said?
Yeah, he said to believe in our power.
You believe, don't you, Ty?
Maybe.
Come on.
We've gone through a lot of weird stuff
already.
If we hadn't stuck together, we never
would have beaten Sidramon.
Or smashed Tyrannomon.
Or escaped from Toy Town.
And I'd still be making french fries in
Vegemon's diner if you hadn't saved me.
You can do it, Ty.
You can do it, Ty!
All right.
So you're leaving it up to me to get this
gate open, huh?
And whatever I decide is the best way,
you're all willing to go along with it?
Uh-huh.
Well, I've decided I want Izzy to do it.
What?
You do?
Why me?
If that's what Ty thinks, I accept it.
Me too.
Don't worry, Izzy.
Ty believes in you and so do the rest of
us.
But what happens if I'm wrong?
No one will blame you.
We all know you're the right one for the
job, Izzy.
Go for it.
I still have no idea how this all fits
together.
Maybe you could use your computer to help
figure it out.
The computer?
Well, right now I'd rather
use it to log onto the
internet and book us
a flight out of this place.
Huh?
Wait a minute.
The horse, the lion, and then the monkey!
That's it!
Remember, all Digimon can be classified as
data, virus, or vaccine.
Could it be?
Who here has met up with Digitamamon and
Gekomon?
I have.
Give me your Digivice.
Bro-digis!
You figured it out?
I think I might have.
Come on, guys.
Check this out.
The first three, the lion, the archer,
and the monkey, would be Leomon,
Centaruman, and Edemon.
In addition, there's one of each
classification.
Data, virus, and vaccine.
The stars, starting at the top, represent
in-training, rookie, and champion.
So now we can put all the cards in the
right squares.
You did it, Izzy.
Good work.
We knew you'd figure it out.
Wait a minute.
Not so fast.
There are two cards here.
One of them is the fake, but I don't know
which one.
So that's it.
I'm sorry.
We still can't be certain where the gate
will open to.
But we made it this far.
That's great.
Yes, it is.
I can pick which one's fake.
If I can't, everyone gets an ice cream,
and I buy it.
Huh?
I'll tell you in just a minute.
It's Dogugumon, an evil Digimon with
computer virus parasites covering his body.
Intruders in the castle must be destroyed.
Don't get them!
Digimon, digital monsters.
Digimon are the champions.
Dogumon, Digiball too!
Ikakuma!
Kalamon, Digiball too!
Kalamon!
Digiball too!
Kaluruma!
Digimon!
Blue Blaster!
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
We're running!
Which one is the fake card?
Hurry up!
Choose!
If I choose wrong, we're toast!
Poison Thread!
The monsters too!
The champions!
Monster friends to the boys and girls!
Hey, Digimon, hey, Digimon!
Ty, you've got to make up your mind now!
We're out of time!
Okay!
It's this one!
Monster friends to the boys and girls!
Hey, Digimon, hey, Digimon!
It was real close, Zoonomon, but it looks
like we made it!
It looks like we made it!
Where are we?
I know this place!
This is the summer camp where we all met!
You did it, Ty!
We're home again!
We're back to where we were first sucked
into the digital world!
But where are our Digimon?
I wonder if we got the cards wrong after
all!
Then in this world, we could be without
them!
You can't get rid of a study, Ty!
Wake up!
Come on, sleepyheads!
We're up!
Where have you been?
We thought we ought to go look for a
little lunch!
Now that we're home, we don't have to eat
leaves anymore!
We can eat cheeseburgers!
That's right!
And pepperoni pizza!
And french fries!
And ice cream!
Yeah, and broccoli!
Broccoli?
How did you know that my card was the
fake, Ty?
I didn't!
I kept your card because you're my friend!
That's so nice!
Hey, everybody!
We've got to go and find the eighth child!
Yeah!
And we've got to get a move on since my
Otismond's there ahead of us!
I'm happy that we're finally headed back
to my hometown!
And we already know that's where we're
going to find the eighth child!
Let's go!