Last time, Matt lucked out and found Joe
in a restaurant where these two creeps,
Veggiemon and Digitammon,
were working him like a
dog to pay for a lunch
he'd had, like, weeks ago.
Pretty soon, Matt was slaving away,
too.
The whole thing was a scam by Demidevamon
to keep them both there forever.
Luckily, TK and I showed up just in time.
With WereGururumon and Matt's
crest of friendship glowing, we
beat the little bat and sent
him and his crew to the showers.
Now we had to find Mimi and the others,
so we all split up again.
Digimon.
Digital monsters.
Digimon are the champions.
changing to Digital Champions to save the
digital world.
This is extremely perplexing.
We've been trying to find Gen-I for over
two months.
Got any ideas, Ten-A-Mon?
We're walking in circles.
We could walk in squares, but that's not
likely to work either.
Let's take a breather and wait for him to
come to us.
I'd prefer to take a more scientific
approach to this problem.
Yes, but even scientists need to take a
break.
There's no time to rest, so stop asking.
Eww... I'm absolutely certain
that he's around here somewhere.
I hope so, for my feet's sake.
This better work!
I hate it when my Otis-Mon gets angry.
Demi-Devi-Mon!
Nice day, huh, boss?
I'm still waiting for you to steal the
crests from those kids.
I've got a sure-fire way to get them.
I've heard that one before.
With this cute little face tell a bit,
boss.
After all, you're my Otis-Mon.
I'd be out of my head to make you mad.
I'll give you one more chance.
But I won't be so benevolent the next
time.
Do you understand?
Loud and clear!
If I don't steal those crests,
he's gonna rake me over the coal!
Run!
Ah!
Uh-oh!
They're here!
I've gotta hit it!
Me!
I'm curious to know why Gen-Eye is so
secretive.
I want to discuss the merits of the crest
with him.
I like that about you, Izzy.
You have a never-ending thirst for
information.
It's amazing your brain doesn't explode
with all that knowledge.
There are a lot more things I can learn.
How much room do you have left in your
brain?
As much as I need.
I wonder where Gen-Eye could be.
With all my knowledge, I still can't find
him.
Hmm... Look, Izzy!
It's a sign!
You mean from above?
No, you're on the ground.
How bizarre.
It says, beware of falling sludge.
Uh-oh, this could get real ugly.
Huh?
Aaaaaaah!
Bleah!
Yuh, yuh, yuh, please tell me this was
just a dream.
I say we go anywhere but this way.
Yeah.
Oh no, there's another sign up ahead.
Bottomless sludge pit, not a very pleasant
experience.
Huh?
Whoa, I feel like I've been flushed.
I hope I never see another sign as long as
I live.
Me too.
Whoa!
Attack sludge impossible!
A humiliating attack by an attack sludge.
Hmm, there doesn't appear to be any other
place for us to go.
Huh?
We're surrounded by sludge.
I don't have a chance!
There's no bottom to this pit.
Well, that could work in our favor.
It's a lot easier on your head that way,
if you ask me.
Unfortunately, that's impossible.
If we fall any farther, we'll be
in... A very unpleasant place.
That's not good.
Whoa!
Does anybody need a lift?
Hey, what are these?
I have temporarily given you a life ride.
You see, all those that are greedy fall
into the pits.
I'm not sure I comprehend what you're
saying.
What are you accusing us of being greedy
for?
What did you know?
Too much, of course.
You're sticking your nose in where it
doesn't belong.
What could possibly be wrong with gaining
knowledge and information?
See?
You're doing it again.
You can't seem to stop yourself.
You're headed straight for the pit if you
don't learn to control yourself.
How come?
You don't even know that you're killing
it.
I don't?
It's like a disease with you.
Oh, well.
Nice knowing you.
Don't worry, Izzy.
I'll save you.
Give me your hand.
It's your decision.
Do you want it to fall in the pit?
No way.
Of course not.
That makes two of us.
Then give up your curiosity to me.
It appears I have no other choice.
But it's your curiosity that I admire.
What procedure should I utilize to keep us
from falling down this pit?
Stop asking questions.
I won't.
I don't want to know.
That's more like it.
Well, we finally made it out, but where
are we now?
Welcome to my universe.
I certainly hope you enjoy your stay here.
Izzy?
I'm Vedamon.
I personally designed this universe.
Pretty nice.
Don't you think?
Vedamon was living proof
you should always stay
away from Digimon with
unusually large heads.
That big brain of his was scrambled,
if you ask me.
Your curiosity is in this sack.
It's garbage.
You don't need it.
And I don't want it messing up my
universe.
I just hate having clutter.
If it's not needed, I save it.
Now that that's done, I want you to read
my latest book.
It's all you need to know.
All you need to know, whether you like it
or not.
It happens to be a bestseller.
In order to be one with the universe,
you must erase your thoughts.
But your thoughts make up who you are.
You mustn't erase them.
It is important to
breathe into your thoughts
until they disintegrate
and slowly turn into mush.
I've heard enough.
Keep away from me!
Huh?
The less you think about, the happier
you'll be.
Someone's trying to send us a
transmission.
Soon your mind will shut down and you will
have nothing left to worry about.
Izzy!
Look, it's time.
Where are you?
I'm home, but I got your message that
you're in danger.
I'm trying to find you!
Tell me about it.
I'm trying to find myself.
Don't bother coming back to the Digi
World, Ty.
You'll just clutter up the universe.
Izzy!
Ty is risking his life to save you,
Oh well.
Is your friend!
Indifference is the key to success.
Practice it.
The Izzy I knew is no more.
I've got a warehouse full of curiosities
and other castaway items.
And all of them are for sale.
There's always someone who wants to buy
junk.
And I know the salesman who can give them
a bargain.
Radamon, curiosity salesman
extraordinaire.
A penny for your thoughts and a nickel for
your fears.
Hmm.
Ha ha!
That was fast.
Just a minute, I'll be right with you.
Whoa!
Have I got a bargain for you?
I hope so.
I'm earning a sale right now.
Dreams and curiosities are at bottom line
prices.
I'm telling you, it's a steal!
Huh?
Did anyone in this picture happen to
tumble into your universe?
Why yes, they did.
Perfect!
You must be in the market for the
curiosities.
I'll fetch them for you.
Huh?
They're very fresh.
If you're looking for brain garbage,
this is the place.
I'm looking for something else.
Don't try to give me a hard time or I'll
get mad.
I want this.
Hmm.
The kid in the picture was carrying a tag
and a crust with him.
Well, that's not something I ordinarily
carry.
It's a very expensive item, huh?
Hmm.
How about I trade him for some of my
curiosity?
Hmm.
He must have a mountain of curious
thoughts.
So what do you say, Betamon?
Is it a deal or not?
It certainly is.
I can tell by looking at
you that you're a Digimon
with enough wacky thoughts
to make me a fortune.
Izzy, what are you doing?
I'm preparing my brainwaves
by focusing on some basic
fundamentals, so I would
rather you did not disturb me.
There's something that I forgot to mention
to you.
Oh yes?
What?
In order to fully improve
yourself, you must throw
away possessions that are
considered excess baggage.
Such as?
Just about everything except your clothes.
Of course.
Izzy, what are you doing?
This is expendable.
Have you gone bananas?
You can't throw those away!
Hmm, what a nice looking trinket.
Give back that tagging crust, you poor
excuse for a Digimon!
Back off, Bug!
Yaaaah!
Izzy!
Forget about him, now get back to your
training!
Yes.
O.
P. Q.
R.
T.
U.
V.
Double.
So sorry to make you wait!
Yeah!
Alright, come on, give me the guts!
Wait, don't you recall the deal that we
made?
I want a piece of your brain.
I'm going to crank out some of my
thoughts.
Duh?
Mmm, I'm trying but it's hard to get them
out of my head!
Come on, hurry up!
They're stuck!
I'll help!
Aaaaah!
E.
F.
G.
I've lost him!
H.
I.
J.
I... I have no energy... left!
Oh!
Huh?
Monkey Man!
Pabu!
Pabu-man?
What's the matter with you?
I told you not to bother me when I'm
meditating!
Pabu!
Have you forgotten who I am already,
Izzy?
Have you forgotten who you are?
Try to remember!
Try!
I just want to figure out what the Ditchy
World really is!
Can't remember...
Aaaaah!
Hold on, Izzy!
And don't let go of your curiosity!
It's your curiosity I admire!
This is merely scientific
speculation, but I believe I
stumbled onto something more
than just a simple computer game.
No!
Pabu!
Oh, sorry!
I didn't mean to make you D-Ditchy-Valve!
Pabu!
You lied!
What?
You are nothing but a weasel lie!
Don't get Ben all out of shape!
I always take shape when I'm mad!
Give me a break!
I'm gonna get in big trouble!
It's not my concern, you pesky pipsqueak!
I'll beat it, pal!
Oh, please!
My otis man will pull my feathers out if I
don't bring him that tagging crust!
You got yourself into this, now you can
get yourself out!
Please, I'm begging you!
He's a big brute!
Buckle!
I'm mixed up because my curiosity's gone.
But I believe somehow I've been tricked,
so I must implement a plan to get it back!
Pabu!
Unfortunately, all I'm coming up with is a
big zero!
Pabu!
There's gotta be some
way I can get my curiosity
out of there, but I
can't figure out how!
Pabu!
Pafetamon!
Get out!
Forget it!
It's mine!
No, it's not!
You wanna bet?
Hand it over, you old coot!
Now you've really got me mad!
Hey, wait a second!
He's stolen the tagging crust!
Let's get out!
A fat hair!
Where'd he come from anywhere?
Pabu-mon over here!
Thoray!
My trick, though it's too late!
AAAAHHHHH!
That's good work, Pabu-mon!
You've got the crust!
Uh, you want me to follow you?
Uh... UGH!
Oldchild ơimt!
Partner Kramer, privil!
Armeame for lunch!
Can, let's make a deal!
Whoa!
Digus!
You've found my curiosity!
It was a mistake to give it up!
I'm sorry, I just tossed it away.
Hey, curiosity is essential.
Ba-boo-ba-boo.
I'm going to have to concentrate.
I hope it transfers.
Come back in my heart.
Ha!
Now you're going...
It's time for you to digibow!
Multimon!
Izzy, be careful!
Digi-doll monsters, Digimon are the
champions.
Dental-mon, Digi-doll
two... Kabu-terrimon!
What
I need is some pest control to...
Sorry, but I've never been very partial to
vermin, Digimon.
Ah-ha-ha-ha!
Get up, you got a Digi-bow!
Dental-mon
are the champions.
Digimon!
Dental-mon are the champions, Digimon are
the...
Digi-bow-two!
Mega-Kabu-terrimon!
Digi-bow-terrimon was successful.
He digi-bowed to Ultimate
Mega-Kabu-terrimon.
Let's see if you can take him on,
Digimon!
I have a surprise for him, too!
Yeah!
Run!
Go, Mega-Kabu-terrimon!
Nothing like a speeding planet to give
them the ultimate headache!
HARD BUSTER!
Whoa!
Alright!
Thanks for the proper start, I'm on!
EZ, wake up!
Are you alright?
I was so worried.
I'm fine.
I'm so tired I can barely stand up.
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault.
You didn't know.
EZ!
Awesome!
You made it back!
That's right, we're back.
Yeah, we're back.
How's it going?
Better now.
Tell us what happened.
Yeah, how did you get here?
We thought you were a digi-gunner.
EZ was taking a self-improvement class.
I improved so much I flunked right out.
Hello, kids.
It's been a while.
It's Jedi!
The connection between the worlds is still
damaged.
You'll have to stay long there.
I've collected some information about the
digital world that you'll be able to use.
Make sure you take a look at the Digimon
file.
It'll tell you all you need to know.
I wonder if there's anyone we know in
here.
I've just downloaded my favorite,
Mega Kabutarimon.
Yeah, I'm a cool dude.
A funny thing happened to me on the way to
Betamon.
Prepare to face the consequences.
I hate this part.
Quiet!
You had your chance.
Don't make me sit in this tree all night!
AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!