It's sad to think that someone can be so
depressed it takes over their entire life.
For Matt, these feelings of
dread took the form of a deep
black cave, and he was
about to be lost in it forever.
Gabamon finally opened Matt's eyes,
and proved that he was really loved.
Sora had a similar problem,
but Matt and Joe were
able to pull her out of
her own cave of darkness.
Tai and Ward Raymon had
been holding off Piedmon all
on their own, and they
were completely exhausted.
With the power from Matt's crest of
friendship, they became re-energized,
and should be able to take care of that
laughing fool once and for all.
a diesem Celia reallyプroject to die.
Now that we have two Mega Digimon,
let's destroy Piedmon once and for all.
Go get him, Metal-Gururumon.
Come on, War-Greymon, take care of this
clown!
So... I'm a clown.
Then I'll act like one clown trick!
I'll get him!
Try jumping through this hoop!
Are you okay?
Why don't you join us?
We're having a ball.
Oh, sorry if I call to a balance.
Round and round he goes.
Where he lands, nobody knows.
He thinks this is just a big game.
Well, I'm tired of playing around.
Let's not be hasty.
He wants us to make a mistake.
What's the matter?
Don't want to play with Uncle Piedmon
anymore?
No!
Trumpsword!
Be careful of the swords!
Hey, wait!
Some of those swords aren't real!
War-Greymon, I'm picking up the real
swords on my sensors!
Over to your right!
Cover me!
That's old wolf's snout!
Looks like the joke's on you, Piedmon!
Terra Force!
All right!
Nice shot!
Izzy, have everyone digivolve and attack!
You heard him, guys!
Now it's our turn!
I'm in!
Me too!
Caution!
A white flag?
Maybe he's trying to surrender to us.
I don't trust him.
I think he's got another trick up his
sleeve.
Hey, why don't you make yourself
disappear?
Playtime is over!
But I'm just getting started!
War-Greymon!
Metal-Gururumon!
What happened?
I don't know!
Ta-da!
Thanks for coming next shows at 7.30!
You've been a great crowd!
Good night!
He made them all disappear!
Well, at least he didn't saw them in half.
What did you do to tie and met,
Piedmon?
I hold the keys to their existence.
And I need a place to put them,
so I made a couple of keychains.
I think I'll hang these two on my
backpack.
What kind of sicko turns people into
keychains?
I'm not a sicko.
I'm a collector and these new items have
such sentimental value to me.
Now, who wants to be next?
Look at all this fire!
This is terrible!
I didn't bring a single marshmallow.
Sentaruman, I came as fast as I could.
Oh, Jedi!
I'm glad you made it!
Is this it?
Yes, this is the mystical wall of fire the
ancient prophecy on File Island describes.
Really?
What do you say we barbecue?
Incredible!
Is it really true that he had to make it
across these flames?
I know it sounds crazy, Jedi, but that's
what the prophecy says!
Unbelievable!
Oh!
Andromon!
We've got to get out of here, Sora!
Andromon's buying us more time!
It
looks like a giant circus tent.
Whatever it is, I don't like it.
Hey, there's a way out across this canyon!
My only question is, how do we get to it?
The only way is to use these swings like a
trapeze artist, but don't let down,
there's no net!
Kari, hold me tight and don't let go!
Not so easy to fly, is it?
What are you carrying in that backpack?
Bricks?
Ow!
Gatomon, you've got to trim your claws!
Away you go!
Don't you want to take your friend along?
Andromon!
Go, Izzy!
Joe!
Don't worry, Izzy!
I'll save you!
Now you see them, and now you don't!
They're dropping like flies!
Really?
That's strange!
I feel fresh as a daisy!
Mimi, get up here!
It looks like the battle's started!
Thanks!
Oh, it's just my luck!
I finally bring all the reinforcements and
all they want to do is hang around!
Hello, my name is Izzy and I'm very smart!
Although I didn't know how to stop me and
my friends from being made into kitchens!
I love a good puppet show!
Ah,
so you want to play hide and go seek,
hmm?
Okay!
I love a good game!
Now, let's see, if I were a little pest,
where would I hide, hmm?
Maybe you're in this room, over here!
I think we're out of danger for now!
Ah!
Kick-a-boo!
Run for it!
On the
on-the-on-the-on-the-on-the-on-the-in!
Celestial Arrow!
Run, Cory!
Hurry, Sora!
It's Anjumumon!
Garudumon!
We're back!
TK, come here.
What is it?
I want you to take Kari and get out of
here.
Well, what about you?
Listen to me.
There isn't much time.
Paimon has the rest of our friends,
and if he gets us, we're doomed.
TK, please.
You're the only one who can protect Kari.
You have to be brave.
Now get going.
I won't leave you.
Don't worry about me.
I'll be fine.
All right.
No matter what happens, just keep running.
Okay, Sora.
I promise I'll do whatever I can to
protect Kari.
Right.
Hurry, go!
Come on, Kari.
Let's go.
Sora, I want to stay and fight with you.
Don't be ridiculous.
You can't even Digiball without Joe.
So go before Paimon gets here.
But, Sora!
Go, Momon.
Joe risked his neck to protect us.
And if Paimon turns you into a doll,
his sacrifice will mean nothing.
Now, please help TK and Kari.
There's not much time.
Ow.
Now go!
Look, I only need five
more keychains for my
collection, and then
I'll have the whole set.
Not if I can help it!
Sora!
TK, catch!
In order to succeed, sometimes you have to
step on people along the way.
Oh, man!
Quick, let's run!
We just ran out of room.
This isn't the escape plan I had in mind.
No way!
Can we jump?
It's too far!
Welcome to the dead end!
Don't be a keychain like your friend.
We can't just sit here.
We've got no choice.
We have to climb down.
It's too high, TK.
If we slip, we're goners.
Kari, we're going to have to try.
Look, TK, where'd that basket come from?
Who put that there?
A rope!
We can use it to climb down the side of
the mountain.
I didn't know you were a sick charmer,
TK.
Do you think we should climb it?
I don't know.
Mom always said never take candy or rope
from a tree.
I'm strangers.
What am I thinking?
We have to climb it.
Sora told me to be brave no matter how
scared I get.
Looks dangerous.
You go first.
Oh.
That's it, Kari.
Pretend you're in gym class.
Listen!
Open!
I must quit this.
It costs me a fortune in new doors.
Keep climbing.
I'll distract him.
Digimon!
Anjumon!
Ah!
You get him, Anjumon!
No!
Drop everything!
Don't give up!
No!
I'm scared.
It's okay.
Great.
Wait, now Kari's afraid.
I can't let her see that I am too.
I've got to be brave.
Anjumon will be fine, but you've got to
keep on climbing.
Don't let that Joker Piedemont scare you.
Okay.
You've reached the end of your rope!
TK!
No!
Sorry if I gave you a reggie.
Let go of him!
Let go, Kari, or he'll get you too!
No, I won't let you go, TK!
Sounds like you two are falling,
Burichella!
TK!
Hurry!
TK, don't ever give up.
Matt?
You can do it, TK.
I have faith in you.
But it won't help if you don't have faith
in yourself.
No matter what happens, you have to fight
to the very end.
I promise you, Matt, I'll never give up
the fight.
If I don't do it, then this world and our
world will be destroyed.
I have to do it for Matt, for Anjumon,
for everybody.
TK?
TK!
I am Magna Anjaman.
I have eight shining wings and a beam
shield.
I wield the mighty sword Excalibur.
And my devastating attack is the Gate of
Destiny.
Chew on this!
I'm not hungry.
I guess my sword trumps yours.
Now to bring our friends back to normal.
Magna Antidote.
What a weird dream.
I had an incredible urge to carry some
keys.
Car, TK!
You did a great job, TK.
If it wasn't for your advice, I don't
think I would have been able to do it.
Huh?
Wow, when did Anjaman teach evolve?
You look great.
Turn around, let me see.
Very well.
Oh!
So, those Diddy Destin think the Dark
Masters are that easily defeated, hmm?
Well, guess again.
You're not the only ones with an army of
friends that can help you.
Ta-da!
This is more fun than a barrel of flying
monkeys.
Diddy Destins, meet the Vilemon.
Their nightmare shock will give you a rude
awakening.
We're surrounded.
Oh no!
We can't escape!
Come on!
Toughen up!
I'm with you, TK.
Our only chance is if we all combine our
powers together.
But the problem is we're still missing
some of our friends.
Wait for me!
Sorry, we're late!
It's Mimi!
Are we too late for the party?
Come on!
I sliced!
I guess I'm gonna have to work on my
swing, huh?
All right, gang!
Give them the full Digimon attack!
Super Thunderstrike!
Hornblaster!
Nice shot!
Purple Whack!
Car the Junkers!
Zulomon!
Most Impressive!
Twinshot!
Hornbuster!
Yay!
Flower!
Gate of Destiny!
Remember us?
Terra Force!
Gigamissile!
The last remnants of Spyro Mountain are
disappearing!
The Dark Master's control over the digital
world is finally gone!
Good riddance!
Bye, friends!
Goodbye!
You know, I'm starting to think we have a
strange-looking group of friends.
They might not have
the best fashion sense,
but they're the best
friends we've ever had!
Hm.
We have email from Jedi.
What's it say, Izzy?
Not now.
I need a nap.
It's coming in now.
Is he congratulating us?
Jedi says here that the Dark Masters
aren't the real enemies.
Huh?
It says here that the real
enemy is an evil force whose very
existence warped the Digi-World
and created the Dark Masters.
So according to this, I don't think we're
out of the woods quite yet.
Wait a sec.
If it's not the Dark Masters, then who do
we fight next?
What?
What's happening?
What is the evil force that Jedi was
warning the Digi-Destined about?
Find out on the next Digimon Digital
Monsters.
What?