Agobon, Warf Digivolve 2!
Warg Raymon!
Gabobon, Warf Digivolve 2!
It's Warg Raymon!
It says here his attack is
Terra Force, gathering the
energy around him and
focusing it in the palm of his hand.
Metal Garurumon has his Metal Wolfclaw
attack.
He shoots a powerful cold blast at his
enemies, then blows them to pieces.
Mega Digimon!
They Digivolve into their Mega Digimon
forms.
That's great, because we'll need them to
beat Venom Iotismon.
Yeah, that's for sure.
Good luck!
I'll wait here.
Mon,
you creamed him!
I think.
Look!
There we go!
Get after him, Warg Raymon!
Put his lights out!
First Wolfclaw!
Close it!
Solid!
Your
miserable attempts to destroy me have
failed!
Now you will pay!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Oh, whoa!
Aaaaah!
Everybody out!
Get clear of the van!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Jim, how's Dad?
Is there any improvement yet?
No.
Still exactly the same.
All right.
I'm tired of fooling around.
We have to defeat Myotismon once and for
all.
Our parents always protected us.
Now it's time we came through for them.
Mimi!
If we do it together, we can beat him!
Think so?
Mm-hmm!
I'll try.
You will?
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
We already tried.
So we'll keep on trying, Joe.
Because Digimon never give up.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Like I always say, all for Mon and Mon for
all.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
You're right!
We can do it!
Let's get him, guys!
You'll have to excuse Joe.
He's a little hyperactive.
Oh!
Please take care of our parents,
Jim!
Good luck, you guys.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Kory!
Get him, Archibon!
Look, Izzy!
All the others have Digivolve too.
There's Ikakumon and Togamon and Bergamon!
I'm going in!
Digimon!
Digimon Monster and Digimon are the
champion!
Kabu-Terry!
Digital monsters, Digimon!
Everyone, attack at the same time!
Okay, how about a little needle spray?
Harpoon torpedo!
Meteor wing!
Electro shocker!
End of face!
Celestial arrow!
And now to wind things up!
Mega Claw!
Aw!
You
think you can defeat me?
You've only awakened the beast within!
What is that thing?
How about out, you so-called
digi-destined?
You've stood in my way for the last time!
It can't end like this!
I've let everyone down again.
I wish I could have done more.
It's impossible he survived that.
Maybe we should surrender.
This is scarier than the movies!
I will never give up!
Huh?
My crest!
Everybody, look at your crests!
They're all starting to glow!
Oh!
Woo-hoo!
T-destined, curse you and your lousy
crests!
Let go!
Look at that!
Mega freaky!
I wonder if that monster represents
Myotismon's actual form!
WarGreymon!
Pass me the ball.
Nice pass.
Shoot!
Terra Force!
What happened, Jim?
It must be Joe and the others.
They did it!
They won!
We did it, Ty!
We did it!
Dang!
Wasn't that cool?
Great job, Sunomon!
Look!
A stray Digimon!
Don't you recognize me?
I was Gatomon!
What do I have to do, cough up a furball?
That's Salomon, the rookie form of
Gatomon.
Isn't she cute?
Much more cuddly than her ultimate form of
Anjuomon.
But I guess she's back
to being a rookie because
she used up all her
energy during the fight.
What are we gonna do?
They don't allow pets in our apartment.
Dread!
Hey, look!
The sky's clearing up!
What?
No way!
That's... not possible.
Huh?
There's a... giant island... floating in
the sky!
Upside down!
Things just keep getting weirder.
Man, why does this have
to happen now, when we
were just feeling good
about beating my Otismon?
It's like the world is turning upside down
or something!
Hey!
What's going on?
Whatever it is, it doesn't look too good
for our side.
Oh, Jim!
Have you seen my children?
Do you know where Tai and Kari are?
No, but I have an educated guess.
I'm gonna search where the monsters were
fighting.
I'll come back when I find them,
okay?
Hey, I...
What's going on?
This isn't making any sense.
It looks like an entire upside down
continent in the sky.
But it doesn't show up on radar or on any
satellite pictures.
In fact, no instruments
of any kind can confirm
that whatever it is,
is really even there.
TK!
Where are you?
Mama!
Oh, TK.
I was so afraid I'd never see you again.
You must have been terrified, TK.
Nuh-uh.
Matt was with me the whole time.
Matt.
Hey, Mom.
Pat!
And Daddy, too!
Oh, Matt.
I'm so proud of you.
Thank you, son.
Yeah, whatever.
Don't be like that.
Please, Matt.
Nancy?
It's been a long time, hasn't it?
Yes, it has.
It's been a really long time since all
four of us were together, huh, Matt?
Yeah, I guess so.
Check this out, guys.
I've been monitoring the news reports.
The Air Force is sending
in everything they've got to
figure out what this
continent in the sky really is.
They don't know anything so far,
but they're assuming it's dangerous.
This talk I want.
Mayday!
I have to admit that
I'm a little jealous that
Matt and TK found their
parents and Izzy, too.
I just hope my Mom and Dad are all right.
I know how you feel.
Me, too.
Huh?
Someone's coming.
All right, my brother!
Hey, I didn't tell him he could ride my
scooter.
Jim, have you seen my Mom and Dad?
All the other families that were at the
Convention Center are fine.
They're all back to normal!
Awesome!
Zora, they're safe!
Great!
Shh!
Let's check the news.
The latest report we have from the Air
Force Chief of Staff confirms that the
mysterious landmass in the sky is not an
illusion of any kind.
It is very real and, after several
confrontations, apparently very dangerous.
It's covering the whole sky.
It has to be Myotismon's work again.
But that's impossible, isn't it?
We defeated Myotismon for good this time!
Yeah, we get booty!
Well, you heard the news report.
It's definitely dangerous.
Who else could be doing it?
What does it matter who's doing it?
We just have to stop it.
There's something familiar about that
mountain.
It looks like Infinity Mountain!
Hey, Ty!
Grab your telescope and get us a closer
peak at that peak right there!
Huh?
Which one?
There!
The big one I'm pointing to!
Oh, like that helps me.
Alright, I'm looking.
Man, there are dozens of mountains up
there.
Which one?
The big one!
The big... Did you find it?
What I found is a jet line!
What?
Ground Control, this is flight 224.
We have lost our vector.
Over.
Strange.
Why not the answer?
This is 224 to Ground Control.
Control, do you copy?
Repeat.
We have lost our landing vector.
Commit Ground Control.
We can't land here now and we can't turn
back with the fuel we have left on board!
What?
The alarm!
All systems failure!
We've got about two seconds to figure out
what's wrong here!
No use!
Nothing's responding!
We're going down!
Oh no!
The airplane reached the edge of that thing
in the sky and just headed straight down!
Veomon!
Captain!
Roll out!
We'll break up at this speed!
Oh, he falls!
If I can just get there in time!
It's Kalagamon!
Where did he come?
Electro Shocker!
It went right through!
Kabutari Mon!
Get away!
Don't touch him!
Whoa!
Nice going, Bergeron!
You brought the plane down safely!
Guys, how'd Kuwagumon get here?
He came out of that land in the sky!
I was right all along!
Huh?
That giant continent is actually the
digital world!
That's why you recognize that mountain!
Yeah, you know, it does look sort of
familiar!
What's it doing here?
Guys, better have a look at this!
We bring you now new footage of some truly
bizarre scenes!
No official explanation has yet been given
for what you are seeing here!
Kuwagumon again!
And if we touch these Digimon,
we'll freeze!
Just like the airplane's wind!
And when I fired my Electro Shocker,
it passed right through!
Man!
What's going on here?
Solomon, is that your world up there?
I think so, but the last time I was there,
it was definitely right side up!
Just a minute!
We've been back in the real world for only
a few days!
But up there, time is much faster!
Years and years have passed by!
And since we left the
DigiWorld when it was such
a mess, it had years and
years to just get worse!
I can only imagine what the place looks
like now!
And all the problems
in the digital world have
become our problem
here in the real world!
That's that!
We've all got to go back!
But how?
How are we supposed to get there?
The first time we went to the digital
world, our Digivices let us!
You guys try it again!
You're coming too, Joe!
We're all in this together!
Alright, everybody!
Hold out your Digivices!
We're going back!
Next stop, the digital world!
Keep your arms and legs inside the ride at
all times!
Here we go, everybody!
I think!
You're all in this together!
I think it's working, Ty!
This light must be here to guide us!
Now all we have to do is follow him!
Back to the digital world!
TK!
Huh?
Mom!
Oh, I'm sorry we have to leave now that
we're finally back together again!
You can't!
Let him go!
No!
We've made some selfish decisions of our
own, remember?
We have to let them do this!
This could be more important than we
realize!
The whole world is doomed if we don't do
something, Mom!
You know we have to go back!
We're doing this to protect you!
Matt!
You guys better get crankin'!
Although it's hard to
believe the fate of the
world's in the hands of
a bunch of kids like you!
I guess if the sun doesn't come up
tomorrow, we'll know you messed up!
Stop it!
You've got to have faith in your brother
and his friends!
What they're doing is incredibly brave!
Whoa!
Sorry, lady!
I didn't mean anything!
It's okay.
He was only kidding.
And besides, I'm gonna make darn sure the
sun does come up!
Joe, I didn't know you had it in you!
What a man!
What's happening?
Alright!
Here we go!
Matt!
TK!
Take care of each other!
Sora!
I love you, Sora!
Please come home soon!
I'll be waiting here for you!
Bye, Mama!
Mama!
Papa!
Bye, Dad!
Bye, Mama!
Oh, Ty!
Be careful!
And take care of your sisters,
son!
I'll be alright!
Don't worry!
We'll all be back!
I never thought we'd volunteer to leave
our families behind.
It's weird.
I'm not sure if we'll ever see them again.
But I'm not afraid.
It's like... Just knowing that they love
us gives us the power that we need.
Bye-bye!
What powerful new enemy waits for the
digi-destined in the digital world?
Find out on the next Digimon Digital
Monsters.
Books of desktop trying to run forward to
all parts of the crispy tankers.
We'll be waiting for you for visitors,
etc.
More such as free-熱唱ers.
We'll be able to achieve a better if you
can use this.
SelenaZer 22 Jobets Thank you.