After we landed in the forest,
Palmon and I crossed over to another
floating island, where we found Izzy and
Tentamon.
While Izzy was busy doing something or
other with his computer, Centauromon,
with a black gear stuck in him,
attacked!
Izzy somehow started
talking to me through
my digivice and led
Tentamon and I to safety.
Well, almost.
Our little partners digivolved just in
time, driving out the black gear.
Leomon, who was still under Devimon's evil
control, appeared.
But Izzy and I used our digivices and
chewed that bad kitty away.
Digimon, digital monsters, digimon are the
champions!
Change into Digital Champions,
to save the digital world!
Digimon, digital monsters, digimon are the
champions!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
I, Devimon had completely separated those
seven brats and their pesty Digimon!
That is, until that Tai and Mimi caught up
with Matt and Izzy.
But I'll make sure they never find their
other friends.
Especially with the
plans I have for Sora and
Joe on that lovely day,
the Bakuman Holiday.
There's one thing I've learned in
DigiWorld.
Beds don't make good boats.
Did I just hear you eating again?
Uh-huh.
Didn't I tell you not to eat all the food
since we don't know when we'll find land?
I told you that we'd need to ration,
which means to save food for later,
as in much later.
But it is later, Joe.
You told me that 20 minutes ago.
20 minutes is not much later.
Please tell me that there is still some
food in the bag.
Well, no.
Since you can't handle
eating and floating
on the ocean at the
same time, I ate it all.
Besides, I need food to digivolve in case
we run into bad Digimon.
So, have we seen any bad Digimon?
No!
If I starve, who are you gonna protect?
That's enough about food.
Things will get better soon.
Hang in there, buddy.
That crate is gonna hit us!
Maybe it's full of fruit, vegetables,
bread, milk, cereal, hot dogs,
cookies, candy, soda!
I wish!
You wish!
We wouldn't need more food if you hadn't
eaten ours!
You're strong when you're hungry.
Starvation is a good motivator.
Looks like I'll need a jackhammer to open
this.
Hmm.
Let's see.
Um...
Come on!
Right, you little digi-pest!
Pummelwhack!
Come out of the sea, marching fishes!
I'm not scared of some sickin' fish!
There!
One second thought that really hurt!
What powerful force could
cause this evil digimon to be
driven back and out-muscled
by a bunch of small fish?
When the small and meek join forces to
fight for a good purpose, they can often
bring about the downfall of the big and
powerful.
Yeah!
Get off me!
Then again, sometimes they haven't got a
chance.
And neither do we!
And now for you meeks!
Gumbamon, hitchy-miles too!
Hey, cuckoo-miles!
You're bigger now.
I'm so scared.
Not.
Here's some hand-to-hand.
Come a-whack it.
Harpoon torpedo!
Yo!
You've got to climb up on my back!
Cowards!
Go ahead and run!
See how far you get!
Pretty cats, come back and fight!
I dare ya!
Come on!
Oh, man.
I don't like adventure.
I'm a stay-at-home-and-read kind of guy.
Huh?
I'm tired, hungry, sinking.
Sinking is bad.
Ikakuman, hey, wait a minute.
I thought you were supposed to be some
sort of super water mammal.
Whoa!
Gah!
Catch anything?
Not yet.
Give me time.
I'm hoping to catch something big.
I'd even be happy if you caught me a
little sardine.
I know how hungry you can get.
If I caught a huge any kind of fish,
you'd be right there eating it with me.
Right?
Well, since you put it that way... Do
you really think you can make a big catch?
Oh, look!
Maybe there's one now!
Oh, boy!
It feels like a whale!
This is a whopper for sure!
Pull harder!
I'm trying to!
Let me help!
Help!
Oh, my!
That's a person!
Joe!
Then a large crate drifted over to us.
Ogurran popped out and attacked us.
Goodness.
How horrible.
It was, but I did evolve and we escaped
him.
But then my strength left me.
I just couldn't seem to keep my energy up.
The next thing I knew, I was sinking
deeper and deeper.
And when I opened my eyes and looked
around, I finally spotted Joe nearby.
He was unconscious at the time and sinking
fast.
I tried to get him to the surface,
but my strength was giving out again and I
knew I couldn't hold my breath much
longer.
And that's about the time your fishing
line hit me.
So I grabbed that line and wrapped it around
Joe and hung on until you pulled us in.
Oh, my goodness!
I'm so glad that the both of you are okay.
But I'm worried about Joe.
You are?
Joe's going to be just fine, Gomamon.
Well, yes, physically, but I'm worried
about his confidence.
Fighting Ogremon back there really knocked
him out.
He needs to rebuild his self-confidence.
How can we help him?
Very simple.
We just make him our leader.
Huh?
Oh!
Hey!
Where's Ogremon?
Huh?
He's gone!
But we've got a bigger problem.
We can't find the others.
What should we do?
We're stuck on this deserted island with
no leader.
So I guess you're going to have to lead
us, Joe.
What?
I'm Forim!
And me!
Not me!
I am not a leader!
You have to!
You're the strongest one here!
Not to mention the bravest!
Come on, Joe!
Remember how you fought the Unamon?
I am brave!
You're right!
I am the brightest one here!
Well, let's not get too carried away.
Oh.
But if I fail, who will save you or me?
My fish line?
Huh?
Did you hear anything?
Yeah, it seemed to come from up there.
What do you suppose it is?
Looks kinda like a church.
Wherever there's a church, there's usually
people!
Maybe our friends!
Someone should check it out.
I'll go!
Wait, Biomon!
Huh?
Joe's our leader now!
What?
Well, lead us!
What if we see a bad Digimon?
I, uh... I need a moment.
Okay.
Two, three, four...
Oh, you're left!
Two, three, four... You're left!
Two, three... Must he keep
up that army march drivel?
Halt!
Notice anything?
It all looks sort of familiar to me.
As if it's a place I've dreamed about,
or deja vu.
You know, like we've been here before.
You're right.
This definitely looks like the part of the
island that broke away.
Yeah.
Yep!
So, we should find
everyone else, or at least
some other people,
taking shelter in that church!
You're assuming quite a bit there.
Fine!
That's my opinion!
I'm just giving you another view.
I'm the leader here!
Okay, excuse me.
Let's move out!
Wow!
We've created a monster.
Hey, you think a black ear got him?
Go Maman!
Okay, step lively now, troops.
Let's have no stragglers.
Here's the church.
Who's going in?
What are you waiting for?
Huh?
What's wrong?
Well, boss?
Joe, you're the leader.
Do you want me to take a peek?
No, I don't want you taking a peek.
I can't wait to go in there!
I think it worked.
Okay.
I'm afraid.
I was right.
Just a normal group of people.
Oh, hey guys!
There are people in the church dancing
badly, I might add.
Huh?
There are people.
They're dancing and they're wearing masks
like it's Halloween.
Hall-o-what?
They're celebrating the Bakuman holiday.
It reminds me of Halloween.
We'd love to have you join us.
We don't have a lot of young people
around.
And no holiday is complete without them.
You arrive just in time for some fun.
Like trick or treat?
You do that for Bakuman?
Yes.
Wait, Bakuman?
As in Lord Bakuman?
Yes.
But the only Bakuman
I know of is a horrible
Digimon who lives
among ghosts as their ruler.
Why would you honor and celebrate someone
like that in the words of our friends?
He's like a loser.
You got that right.
Don't you dare come in here telling us who
to honor or not.
Now, now.
Back off.
You're a little touchy.
We just want to know when the trick or
treating starts.
You're not afraid?
No.
Well, you should be because it's a trick.
Huh?
And you're the treat!
The masked man was the evil Digimon Lord
Bakuman in disguise.
No one had ever seen him in his true form.
Bakuman?
It is Bakuman!
Trick or treat!
The dancers!
Who I bet are ghosts too!
That's mine!
Oh!
Zoro's lister!
Gomaman!
Digivolve too!
I need food, you were right.
I shoulda saved some earlier.
Bayamon!
Digivolve!
I'm hungry too!
Can't Digivolve!
Let me go!
Oh, I'm allergic!
Ow, allergic to pain!
Get out of there!
Guilty!
It's my dream!
You're in a dream!
Okay, don't panic.
I'm still in control and feeling strong.
Okay.
I don't want to be somebody's appetizer!
I'm supposed to go to med school!
And pepper!
More!
Why not?
Salt and pepper?
You're not really gonna eat us,
are you?
You're a little on the
scrawny side, but you'd
be surprised what the
right seasonings can do!
You think we can finagle him into dining
on someone a bit bigger?
What kind of fiend is this guy?
We're just kids!
There must be a way out of here.
Maybe we've been looking in all the wrong
places.
There's not much room to look in this
place.
Hey!
What?
We may be able to trick the guard and
escape.
We may be able to trick him?
I think that's a given.
He doesn't look too smart.
Right, so first we have to try and wake
him up.
How are we gonna do that?
Look at him!
For a ghost, he sleeps like a log.
We just have to get his attention or we'll
never escape.
Uh-huh.
But I'm all out of ideas.
I think I have just the thing.
Hey!
What's the idea?
So when do you start?
Start what?
Start taunting us, you floating bag of
wind.
What?
You give bad Digimon a bad name.
But I haven't learned how to taunt anyone
yet.
It's easy!
You just find out what we want,
then don't let us have it!
Huh?
Here's how you taunt.
We're starving and want to eat, so
you show us food, but don't give it to us.
Got it?
I think I gotcha!
You know, I got a bunch of bananas.
Then taunt us with them, come on!
Okay.
How's this?
Looks good, doesn't it?
I can't see.
Come a little closer.
Huh?
Uh, here?
You have to come even closer to taunt us.
We can't really see ya.
You bet.
See?
Oh!
Oh, my gosh!
That was a pretty good idea.
Never get between a Digimon and his meal!
You don't want to eat me.
I mostly gristle anyway.
What's that supposed to mean?
Are you saying they should eat me first?
Oh, can't you see?
It's curtains for both of us.
Oh, go have your pity party somewhere
else!
Lunching you both will be a treat!
We're scary ghosts!
We like to boo!
Now it's time to chew on you!
What will be with her??
We were scared.
Whoa!
Mikakuma!
While we get out of here!
Phone torpedo!
Meteor wing!
Whoa!
He's sure putting up a good fight.
Lord Bakuman is tough.
His power comes from evil, but I know that
good can beat him with time.
Oh, what if it's too late?
It's never too late to
fight evil, but we have to
weaken Lord Bakuman
to help our friends prevail.
We?
You're the leader, not me.
Don't be a quitter!
So what makes you think that we can beat
him?
I once saw a show about this Roman
physicist.
He believed that repeating a phrase helps
you focus mind over matter.
Let's focus on running.
No, we focus on making Bakuman lose his
power.
Okay, you're in charge.
Start focusing.
Bakuman lose your power.
You can jump in any time now.
Well, help!
Right, but I don't know.
That is, I just didn't... Uh...
Oh... Well... Good.
Yeah, we'll use my lucky hat.
Bakuman lose your power.
It's your win!
Take a hit!
Hit the highway!
We gotcha!
Way to go, guys!
You got Pokemon!
It's an earthquake!
But we're not shaking!
Uh-oh, those are Black Gears!
Lots of them, huh?
Ow, we're shaking!
Wow, I'm sure glad those Black Gears
broke.
And I'm glad Bakuman's gone.
Look, it's Infinity Mountain.
And that's where we're going.
Yeah.
Maybe our friends are there, Sora.
I hope so.