We got away from Edamon, but not for long.
I wanted us to be ready, and knowing the
crest and tags could create a digivolve,
I tried to give as much energy to Agumon
as he could take.
But things didn't go so well.
Edamon attacked us with an evil Greymon,
and when my guy tried to fight,
he was just too full of food.
That's when I made a mistake.
I forced him to digivolve again.
He turned into Skull Greymon and defeated
the evil Greymon, but then he turned on us.
Thankfully, he ran out of energy and
returned to a Coromon state.
I'll never do that again.
DIGIMON!
DIGITAL MONSTERS!
DIGIMON ARE THE CHEMPIONS!
DIGIMON!
DIGITAL MONSTERS!
DIGIMON ARE THE CHEMPIONS!
Change into Digital Champions to save the
digital world.
DIGIMON!
DIGITAL MONSTERS!
DIGIMON ARE THE CHEMPIONS!
DIGIMON!
DIGITAL MONSTERS!
DIGIMON ARE THE CHEMPIONS!
Starlet champions.
Digimon.
Digital monsters.
Okay, so I may have made a slight mistake,
and who hasn't?
But that techno-doofus Edemon nailed us
big time with that other Greymon.
Our Greymon used up so much energy fighting
him, he digivolved back into Coromon.
Man, this desert is so hot, even a lizard
would need sunscreen.
Zora, can you carry me?
Not even... A crew cut would
look nice on you, and it's cooler.
Do I look fat?
No, you look hot, especially with a fur
coat.
That thing really needs a zipper.
Or maybe just removable shirt sleeves.
Hey, how about resting our feet?
There's no place to sit except on a
cactus.
Great view up here!
Next time I ride.
You look terrible, Coromon.
If only I hadn't acted like such a
bonehead, you never would have digivolved.
Don't be so hard on yourself,
although come to think of
it, you really have made a
super icky mess of things.
Thanks, Mimi.
Oh, don't mention it, Ty.
I'm glad to help with the pep talk now and
then.
Mm-hmm.
I haven't sweated this much since
cheerleader tryouts.
Ah!
Coromon doesn't look so good.
I'm worried.
You know what we need right now is a whole
bunch of shade.
A big umbrella or a really big tree.
Or maybe I could grow into
a giant cactus and smile down
onto all of you as I provide
cool, refreshing comfort.
It's official.
The sun has just turned Palmon's brain
into a french fry.
Earth to Palmon.
Come in.
Palmon?
Ah!
No!
Wowie!
I did that?
Gee, I'm pretty amazing.
Yeah.
You better believe it, Palmon.
Come on, everybody.
Let's head for some shade.
Yeah!
Woohoo!
Go on!
What happened to the shade?
Huh?
It was just a mirage.
We've been tricked.
Well, well.
It's about time you got here.
I was just about ready to give up on you.
It's Jedi!
Jedi, we found the tags and a couple of
crests like you wanted, but when we got
it, it's coming to trouble our Digimon
couldn't Digivolve.
They ended up worse off than when they
started.
Take a look at poor Agumon.
He is just not himself.
And I'm supposed to be helping him.
I think those thingies are more trouble
than they're worth.
Calm down, kids.
Let me explain.
The tags and crests are extremely
important.
Please make sure no one else gets a hold
of them.
In the end, you shall
see that they will work
together to help you
create total harmony.
In English?
Just trust me.
After all, I'm the floating glowing guy.
As for Coromon, he
wouldn't be so helpless if you
had known how to care
for him in the proper way.
But I did the best I could.
Patience is what you need to learn,
my friends, and you will learn it in time.
But I want to have Agumon back now.
I'm starting to lose my connection.
That's something you're going to have to
figure out all by yourself.
Good luck.
Wait a minute!
Sorry, I'm on a tight schedule.
It never fails.
Every time I need to know about something,
he hangs me out to dry.
Are we being cared for properly?
If we were, Agumon wouldn't have
digivolved backwards.
Come on!
Don't freak me out!
I'm better with computers.
That's ridiculous.
As far as I'm concerned, you're the best.
You look bummed.
How am I supposed to take care of you?
Is there a handbook somewhere?
I feel very inadequate.
Me too.
Huh?
Is that a battleship?
Could be.
But it looks more like a fancy cruise
ship.
The passengers will want their money back
when they see this place.
Yeah.
It could be just a mirage.
Yeah, it looks pretty real to me.
Talies!
Oh!
Ahoy!
Huh?
Noomomon!
Oh.
Hey fella, could all of us come aboard and
freshin' up?
If you don't mind, this needs a woman's
touch.
Well, hey there, big boy.
Your ship looks so, so inviting.
How about letting us on board so that we
can check it out?
Oh, please?
Is it safe?
Oh, what?
No linen tablecloths?
Well, I guess we can rough it.
Whoa!
Nice!
Look!
We can take a shower!
I'm in heaven!
We can spend hours just pampering
ourselves!
Totally yes!
Yeah, we were getting pretty smelly.
Oh, wow!
They've even got little tiny soap bars!
Check out the incredible spread!
It appears to be highly edible.
Might I propose we eat a bit and take the
leftovers with us?
Let's eat it all now!
Oh, I can't believe it!
Remember when the food was just an
illusion?
Another alien plot?
It doesn't smell like an alien plot.
Excuse me.
After extensive deliberation,
I've come to the conclusion
that it would be rude to allow
this cuisine to become cold.
Yeah!
Let's go for it, guys!
I'm confused, Joe.
What do you think Jedi
meant when he said we
weren't taking proper
care of our Digimon?
Uh, I don't know.
We've done everything but give him an
allowance.
Aha!
I see a couple have taken the bait.
Time for me to get started!
They'll never forget this cruise.
I'm Cockatrymon!
My cock-a-doodle-doo will blow out your
eardrums!
Mess with me and you'll be packed into
surrender!
Antimon will reward me
greatly when he learns
I've trapped the
Digi-Destined on my ship!
Ah!
Step it up, fools!
I'm getting very impatient here.
Know what I mean?
If my network's offline, then everybody
crashes.
Let me tell you why.
Because I'm Antimon!
You don't want to make something of it?
No way!
You'll
scream and shout!
Cause I'm the hippest Digimon in town!
Oh, yeah!
So who gave you permission to dance?
Now y'all get back to work before I get
myself upset again!
Yeah!
Something's wrong.
Edemon's network appears to be down.
Ah, who needs him?
I'll have the pleasure of plastering their
feathers all by myself.
Cock-a-caw-caw-caw-caw-caw!
It's amazing how my brains surpass my good
looks.
Now hear this.
I have an important message for ya.
Listen up!
This is the deal.
I'll give you Numamon an
extra serving of dried bread
and even throw in some
jelly if you capture those kids.
They need me!
Ah!
Don't you know I'm claustrophobic?
What's gotten into you Numamon?
No!
You better keep your hands off!
Digivolve!
Digimon!
Wow!
He's back!
Ah!
Pepperbred!
Point!
Petra!
Fire!
Ah!
Poor Agumon!
Gomamon!
Look!
They left me a present!
Oh!
Raa-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
You're sucked without these!
But I wouldn't be too upset.
Now you've got yourself a couple of nice
Digimon garden ornaments!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha
It's your turn!
No!
Petra, fire!
They've been turned into rocks!
Impossible!
Poor Tokomon!
Where are the rest of the children?
Uh, we don't know.
I'd do anything for a good moisturizing
shampoo.
Ah!
You little chickenies think you're so
smart!
Ah!
They won't get away that easily!
It's Han Katrina!
Is that the Easter chicken?
He's bad news!
But Head has Ty in Joe's turrets!
I ran into several of your friends over by
the pool.
Oh, but... Don't get
your heads in a spin!
They're just drying off!
Nothing like little sun-baked faces!
Fried to a crisp with curly corn spuds and
lots of coleslaw!
Oh!
Where are the Digimon?
Don't worry about those guys!
Confidentially, I find them to be a little
bit on the stiff side.
But that just happens to be my personal
opinion.
Your opinion stinks!
Now you're going to meet the same fate!
You've cackled once too often!
Spiral Twister!
Poison Ivy!
Petro... Fire!
Come back, you chickens!
Who's he calling chickens?
What do we do now?
We're trapped!
Huh?
Trap you!
Digimon!
Do your stuff!
Yeah!
Digimon!
Okay!
That has not zero!
Huh?
It's your turn.
Right.
Evolve 2!
Meteor wing!
Needle spring!
We're out of here!
I say we do the same as they are in an
abandoned ship.
I guess it's a little late for a mutiny.
Don't worry.
The captain's already been fricasseed.
Oh, my head!
You may have ruffled my tail feathers,
but I can still...
Okay, so maybe I've lost a little bit of
my doodle, but I'm not finished yet.
Oh!
Well, the weather sure hasn't gotten any
cooler.
Oh... Do you hear something?
Huh?
That's one mad Digimon with his feathers
at a joint!
What were you expecting?
An outlet mall?
Hurry!
Get over on the other side!
I can fly!
Oh, I can't fly!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh!
Bigger
than a skyscraper!
You're right!
What's a skyscraper, Mimi?
Look up there!
Check it out, you guys!
Oh!
Maybe it's a crest!
He was right!
It's just like Jenai said!
The tags and crests somehow work together,
Mimi!
Oh?
It's the crest of sincerity!
I don't deserve it, but if it'll help me
take care of Palmon, I'll keep it!
Thanks, Mimi!
But I think I'm gonna have to teach you
some manners!
Do you know that you slurp when you eat
soup?
But don't worry, a single leaf on that
pretty little head!
Mimi's gonna teach you...
Sure, Mimi is sort of a ditz, but she's
really sincere and a good friend!
That's why she ended up with the crest of
sincerity!
If you ask me, that was a good call!
Totally cool!