So let me bring you up to speed.
Me and the other six kids were kicking back
at summer camp when a freak snowstorm hits.
We find these digivices and bam!
The next thing you know, we're transported
to this whacked out island.
One by one, we make
friends with these creatures
who are known as digital
monsters or Digimon.
Everything was cool till Kawagamon showed
up.
Our new friend somehow digivolved into
bigger Digimon and scared him off,
or so we thought.
Talk about your cliffhangers.
Digimon, digital monsters, Digimon are the
champions!
Change into digital champions to save the
digital world!
Digimon, digital monsters, Digimon are the
champions!
This version of the
CPUなので cookies, and simply
click on the shadow
button into the key.
Wow.
This is something right.
Hey,
I wasn't worried.
What was that?
A floating fish market?
Lucky for us, those fish were having a
school reunion.
Hmm?
I'm kidding.
Those fish are good friends of mine,
and I just asked them for a lift.
And all these years, I thought I was
allergic to seafood.
Thank you.
Um, I guess it's not Bukamon?
Gomamon now.
Gomamon.
Hm.
And I guess that you're not Tokamon,
are you?
Mm-mm.
Now I'm Patamon.
It's all because we digivolved.
I don't think that word's in my
dictionary.
So digivolving is what
happens when they advance to
the next level and become
more powerful than before.
Right.
All of us digivolve.
I went from Molimon to Tentumon.
I digivolve from Yokomon to Biomon.
First I was Tsunomon, then Gabumon.
And I changed from Tamomon to Palomon.
And me, I was Koromon.
I digivolved into Agumon.
Mm-hmm.
When you digivolved, you certainly got way
bigger.
Does this mean you're something different
now, or are you still Digimon?
Digimon?
But I needed your help, Ty.
Me?
For what?
You see, digivolving is a very difficult
process.
In order to be successful, I had to share
your energy.
Really?
I guess you guys don't run on batteries.
Sure don't.
But how do you access my energy?
Even we don't know everything.
Thanks for my magical powers!
The whole thing makes my head spinny.
So I help you change!
That is so cool!
Yep.
Sure is.
My folks warn me about strangers.
I'm not a stranger, Joe.
I'm your friend for life.
Hmm.
Okay, come on.
What are we gonna do?
If only there was a payphone nearby.
We could call the police, or fire
department, or my mother.
But we don't even know where we are.
But we know where we started, up there on
that mountain.
I say we forget about going back and
explore around here.
I'm not exploring anywhere.
I say we stay right where we are.
Yeah, let's wait for that giant bug to
come get us.
We need to find a road leading some place
to get away from here.
Hmm, that's right.
But without a compass, we don't even know
which way is north.
Wait, I do.
Well, which way is it?
It's the opposite of south.
Ugh.
I shouldn't wear these pants.
They ride up when I do a lot of walking.
You know, if we could get back
to where we were before, we might
at least find some clues as
to why we're here in this place.
Wait, are there more monsters around like
that big flying beetle?
Yes indeedy.
Ugh!
Those monsters don't scare me.
Are there humans?
Humans?
Others like you?
Mm-hmm.
You're the first ever.
There's never been anything but Digimon.
So, okay, you're all Digimon.
But what about these monsters?
They're all Digimon, too?
It's creepy.
And dangerous.
And what happens when it gets dark?
Who says it ever gets dark here?
That phenomenon would be unnatural.
And you call this natural?
Well, we're not gonna find out anything by
sitting around here.
Where do you think you're going?
Up on that cliff.
That's where I saw the ocean.
The ocean?
Yep.
There might be a boat or something.
That's a water ski home.
Oh, funny.
At a time like this, I think it would be
far better off just to find a cave and hide.
We keep our eyes open and when
a camp counselor comes... Hey Joe!
Huh?
Everyone's leaving us!
Wait for me!
These trees are beautiful.
Yeah, they're really different.
And I just thought they were subtropical.
Whatever they are, they're aggravating my
hay fever.
Hey Joe, is there anything you don't
complain about?
Digital monsters.
Exactly who came up with that name anyway?
Just call us Digimon.
We like that.
I only ask because your composition isn't
at all machine-like.
Oh, really?
Hey, watch!
So, Paramon, can you really fly?
Of course!
Wow, that's cool!
But you're going the wrong way!
I'm faster than that!
Watch!
Wouldn't it be faster to walk?
Huh?
Palmon, I've been meaning to ask,
who does your hair?
It's natural!
I wake up in the morning like this!
Wow!
Maybe you can let me work with it!
Do you think you put too much emphasis on
appearance?
Well, honestly, I've never really thought
about it.
Honestly, I kind of like my hair the way
it is!
Once I get back, this is going to make one
great story.
Yep!
But, of course, not a single soul will
ever believe me.
That Kawagamon back there, he was huge!
And he's not the only one!
Ah, nothing like the ocean!
Ha-ha!
Everybody in the water!
Hey, let's build a giant sand castle!
Oh, I forgot my bathing suit!
Wait a minute, listen!
What's that?
A phone!
Either that or we're all hearing things.
I told you!
All we needed was a phone!
We're safe!
Why'd it stop ringing, Ty?
Wrong number?
Well, that's bizarre.
My theory is aliens.
They've set these phone booths out as a
trap.
If we could find a place that delivers,
let's order pizza!
Whatever you get, no anchovies for me!
The question is, what are these doing here
at the beach?
So people can call their parents for a
ride home.
Parents?
What exactly is a parents?
That's it.
I'm out of here.
Does anybody have any loose change?
Why?
Obviously, I'm gonna make a phone call to
get some help.
Ah, use my phone card!
The aliens can bill me!
Here!
Maybe there's a quarter in one of the
slots!
I'm calling Daddy!
I'm hooking up to the Internet.
I'm calling Colette!
Libs on Booth 4!
Hey, guys!
Wait for me!
Come on!
Hello?
Hey, Mom, it's me!
At the town, the time will be exactly 45
miles per hour.
And 90 seconds.
Something's wrong or Mom's flipped.
Tomorrow's forecast calls for clear skies
with occasional ice cream.
What do you wear for that?
This number only exists in your
imagination.
Please hang up and don't call back.
What planet did I dial?
I'm telling you, it's a twisted alien
joke.
Why don't you try that one over there?
I don't think it's any better.
No telephones are working in your service
area.
Hang up and have a nice day.
Huh.
Any luck?
No.
Weird.
I got a strange feeling about this.
Maybe this one will.
To leave a message, press one now.
To leave a fingerprint, press two now.
Fifteen dollars for the next three
minutes.
Okay.
Next one.
Very curious.
Does Joe always behave like this?
Every single day.
No matter what number or how many times he
dials, those phones aren't gonna work.
Well, I'm gonna keep searching for a boat
or something.
Hey, wait a minute.
Even though we can't call
out of here, there's always
a chance someone else
might be able to call into us.
It's a waste of time doing nothing but
sitting here.
I'm going to stay here for a little while
and see if anyone calls.
Besides, everyone could use a little rest.
And I'm getting pretty hungry,
too.
You know why?
Because we haven't eaten anything all day.
Okay, break time, everybody.
Does anybody else have any food?
I think the only thing I have is...
Huh?
Is that gadget that fell out of the sky at
camp.
I forgot all about those weird gizmos.
If anybody's got a pink one, I'll trade.
What are they anyway?
We wouldn't have them if they weren't
important.
If I could take mine apart...
Um, that is, after I get something to eat.
I'm really famished.
Well, the only thing I've got is my
emergency supplies.
It's got a first aid kit,
some bandages, and
some medicine, but
that's about all I've got.
I have my trusty laptop computer.
And a digital camera.
Oh, and I've got a small cell phone,
too.
Of course, not one of them's worked since
we got here.
I can't believe you dragged all that
computer stuff to summer camp.
And what do you have?
Uh, let's see.
There's my mini telescope.
Sorry, but I don't have anything to eat
either.
Hey, look at what I got!
Hmm?
Check it out!
Wow!
Look at all those goodies!
Why don't you be a good little boy and
share those treats with dear sweet Mimi?
Aw, you don't have to be so nice,
Mimi.
I'm happy to share.
You're the best.
Isn't she cute?
Forget it.
I'm so hungry, I could eat a horse.
I'd settle for a small cow.
Mimi, what have you got in that big bag?
Some hairbrushes and makeup?
Uh, well, let's take a look.
Here's a compass, cooking
fuel, flashlight, one of
those knives with all the
things, and some other stuff.
Why didn't you tell us you had a compass
back when we needed one?
I thought it might be kind of fun to see
how far we could get without one.
Besides, it's broken.
Well, so much for finding our way out of
here.
Although, we could use the cooking fuel to
make a signal fire.
That's true.
Or I guess we could barbecue some
telephones.
Oh boy, check out the genius.
See?
He's trying to call the telephone repairman
because the telephones don't work.
Problem is... Look!
Joe's got the emergency food!
What?
No way!
Joe!
Hey Joe!
Look!
You've got all the food!
Hey, don't you know it's rude to interrupt
someone when they're on the telephone?
But that bag...
This?
I just brought it to give to Mimi.
Today was her day to carry the bag.
Think he likes ya?
No way!
Ugh.
Mimi, you have got to
stop thinking of yourself
and do something to help
somebody else for once.
Take a little responsibility.
But... that bag's too heavy for me.
Listen, you never hear me complaining.
Guys, guys.
Listen, the most important thing now is
that we've got some food to eat.
So let's sit down and have some lunch.
Uh-huh.
Hmm... Hmm... Hmm...
Hmm... Okay, let's figure this out.
There's seven people in the group,
times three days.
Times three meals,
that comes to... 63 meals.
Ah, right.
So split evenly between us, we
have, uh... Enough food for three days.
Right!
Oh, uh, exactly.
I guess you knew that.
But you guys, when you
add in the Digimon, we
really only have enough
for about half an hour.
Oh, that's right.
Not a problem at all.
We Digimon hunt and forage for ourselves.
You do?
No need to include us in your
calculations.
You sure, Biomon?
Oh, absolutely.
We can do all right for ourselves.
Okay, now that that's
taken care of, let's go ahead
and divide this between
the seven people here.
This is great.
I could eat a dozen of these.
Just what do you think you're doing?
I'm glad we never hear you complaining.
Hmm.
You people make me crazy.
Uh-uh.
Now what's the matter?
Trouble.
Oh.
What's that?
Shellmon!
What's a Shellmon?
Something that gets mad for no reason.
Attacked by two digital monsters in the
same day.
And doesn't Shellmon know I'm allergic to
shellfish?
Everybody, up here!
Agumon, you show them!
Cycleprix!
Blue Blaster!
Viral Twister!
Super Shocker!
What's happening to them?
They look like they've lost their powers.
Poison Ivy!
Why is it only Agumon?
We're just too hungry.
What?
Gabumon, I don't have any strength.
That's it.
Agumon is the only one who had anything to
eat.
Now I see.
Then the other Digimon don't have enough
strength left to fight.
Agumon!
Looks like it's just you and me now.
Then give me a diversion!
Hey Shellmon!
Ugly!
Over here!
No, don't!
Agumon!
This'll work!
Huh!
Bye!
Whoa!
Fingiball!
Oh, Fingiball to.
..
Greymon!
Whoa, he did it again.
Now he's Greymon.
Now you're getting him.
Go, Greymon!
DigiNova Blast!
Do you have anything to eat?
Come on, I know you're there.
Operator?
Operator!
There's really no reason to stay here now.
Who wants to break the bad news to Joe?
If you want some more, just say so.
Shellmon wasn't destroyed.
He was just temporarily removed.
We should pack up and leave before he
decides he wants to come back for round two.
Good idea.
In that case, we should go
right back to the forest, because
if anybody's looking for
us, that's the place they'll go!
Joe, I said this before.
We fell off a cliff and
floated down a river to get
here, and getting back
there's a really big job.
And we could run into Gwagamon!
Now listen, logically
speaking, if there are
telephones here, then there
must be people to use them.
So, I think it makes good sense to try and
find those people.
That makes sense?
It certainly does.
Hmm.
Then let's all get going.
Anywhere you want to go, I'll go,
Ty.
You just pick the direction.
Then let's get out of this place.
And let the monsters beware.
Mm-hmm.
Well, my plan is to avoid all monsters.
Yep, that's my plan.
Okay, here we go!
Digimon!
Yay!
I'll take a break!