Matt and Ty were arguing about whether or
not to climb Infinity Mountain.
Ty figured from up there, we could see a
way off the island.
Matt thought it was just too dangerous.
I don't know what came over me, but that
night, I took it upon myself to climb it.
On the way up, me and Gomomon saw a black
gear embed itself in Unamon.
It was no surprise when Unamon attacked.
I was in quite a bit of trouble.
That's when Gomomon digivolved into
Ikakumon.
He rescued me and, using his harpoon
torpedo, destroyed the black gear.
I don't think I'll climb any mountains for
a while.
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Change into Digital Champions 2!
Save the Digital World!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Digimon!
This place could really use a good bus
system.
Yeah, but it looks like we're at the end
of the line.
We're doomed.
Trapped on an island.
We'll never get out of here alive.
I knew I wouldn't like camp.
But would my folks listen to me?
No.
Oh, I wanted to go to summer school.
Another black gear.
I sense danger.
Come away!
Leomon, you may be mighty, but now you
face me.
Your kind-hearted leadership is
unimpressive.
Ogre-man, you are truly the most evil of
the bad Digimon.
There is no limit to your ruthlessness.
No one asks you here.
No one wants you here.
I strongly suggest that you go now while
you still can.
The endless attack of black gears which
keep dropping from this mountain is
transforming perfectly peaceful innocent
Digimon into monsters.
And I have come here to make it stop.
What a joke.
You have been warned.
Both of you stop.
Cease this foolishness.
I command that the two of you work
together for me, not fight.
You will win for me.
I'll never do that.
Neither will I.
Be silent!
For I am Devonod, ultimate ruler of the
demon underworld.
You must obey my every command.
Sir, you don't need that, Joker.
I can handle whatever you want done
without anyone's assistance.
I think not.
It is the Digi-Destined kids we'll be
fighting.
The Digi-Destined?
Where are they?
They're already here on Infinity Mountain.
Now find them and destroy the entire
group.
Destroy them?
I'll destroy you for having threatened the
Digi-Destined.
Fist of the Beast King!
Freeze, Neoman.
I am not requesting your cooperation.
I am demanding it.
Prepare for the touch of evil.
Now you will obey my every command.
Yes, I will obey.
Hmm.
What you doing?
Making a map of the island.
That way we'll know exactly where we are
and where we've already been.
Yes, that works in theory.
What?
Did you say map or mess?
No question, man.
You are the dude of doodles.
If you follow that map, it'll lead right
to a headache.
Well, I can read it just fine,
and that's all that's really important.
We don't need a map to know.
We're totally lost.
I figured that out a long time ago.
I just figured out that these gloves
really don't go with this dress.
How sad.
What's that?
I don't know, but I have a feeling we're
going to wait here to find out.
At least it won't be a long way.
Don't worry.
Leomon is our friend.
With big teeth.
He just uses them for smiling.
He's a just leader and role model for all
Digimon.
I want the children.
Huh?
Call me paranoid, but I think it's time we
run!
Oh no!
My map!
Ty, come back!
Forget the map!
Uh-oh.
Peppa breath!
Sorry about your map.
That's okay.
At least it didn't fall into the hands of
the enemy.
Don't slow down, Joe.
He's right behind us.
And just where do you think you're going?
Ah!
Well, children, so good of you to stop by.
He looks hungry to you.
We're too small to eat and I'm full of
junk food.
Well, he's not against the little snack.
Make it easy on yourselves.
Give up now!
Or else!
I don't see an exit door.
This proves the theory that well-executed
teamwork is efficient even for bad guys.
But Leomon has always been Argumon's worst
enemy.
What's happened to him?
Ready, Leomon?
Time!
I don't know!
Ackumon, Digibob 2.
Raymon!
Calmon Digibob 2!
Togomon!
Tiamon Digibob 2!
Tabu Terrimon!
Gomomon Digibob 2!
Ikakumon!
They've all Digibobbed!
Come with me, TK.
Let him have it, Graymon!
Nova Blast!
Harpoon torpedo!
Kato Spray!
They have learned the secret of teamwork.
This group of six attacking together is
quite dangerous.
But why hasn't the Patamon Digibobbed?
Are you ready?
Avalanche, watch out!
Howling Blaster!
VPR Wing!
Electro Shocker!
Nova Brast!
Everybody okay?
Oh yeah, like a day at the beach.
I think I need a facial.
Huh?
What?
Agumon, speak to me!
We aren't wounded, TIE.
We're all just a little exhausted.
Two Digivolutions in one day, no wonder!
Poor B.O.
Hey, what happened to the bad guys?
They just disappeared!
Are you sure?
Do you think that avalanche knocked them
both off the cliff?
Hello!
Unless they can fly, they're goners.
Neither one of them had wings,
so I'm sure they weren't airworthy.
Nothing is logical here!
Anything is bound to happen, including
flying monsters!
For once?
You might be right, Joe.
Something bothering you?
It's that avalanche.
I can't figure out what set it off.
Stress accumulates until
a crack develops, and with
excess weight, the terra
firma suddenly isn't so firma.
You think so?
It looked to me like something blasted it
loose.
They are more powerful
than I suspected, but I shall
strike while they are
exhausted and destroy them all!
I'm intrigued that our Digimon were able
to digivolve twice in one day.
Well, it was sure lucky for us that they
were able to do it.
I think the Digimon are growing stronger.
I wonder if that's a normal
part of their evolution,
or if we are bringing out
something special in them.
A fascinating hypothesis.
If only we could test it.
I think today was too much for them.
Palmon's looking very tired.
I've been tired before, don't worry!
Admit it, Palmon!
We need to stop and rest!
You know, to be perfectly honest, I think
that would be a good idea for all of us.
Rest where?
I don't want to sleep on the ground.
Look!
A mansion!
Or maybe it's a hotel!
Come on!
We may have found other life forms.
Look at the grounds!
I mean, somebody had to have mowed the
lawn!
What a place!
I can't believe my eyes!
It's just too good to be true!
I hope they have a hot tub, just as long
as it's not too hot.
Wait, you guys!
Don't just go charging in there!
It might be dangerous!
Hey, was this on your map?
Hmm.
Somehow, I don't think so.
Go ahead, Joe.
Open the door.
Maybe we should knock first.
Joe, nobody knocks on the door at a hotel.
This place should be on your map.
Agumon, if you recall, you burned up my
map.
Oh, yeah!
Well, here goes.
I don't see a desk clerk.
Anybody here?
Looks weird.
Feels weird.
Well, it doesn't look or feel weird to me.
Perhaps my definition of weird is
different than yours.
I'm with you.
Think about it.
Are we safer in the open
woods with no shelter, or
here in a sturdy building
we could defend from attack?
I have to admit, you have a point.
That's beautiful!
Hmm?
Oh, yeah.
Look it!
It's an angel!
What's an angel, TK?
Something special that watches over you.
Kind of like you guys.
If this is a spooked-out
haunted house, would
there be pictures of angels
hanging on the walls?
I don't think so.
Relax.
We just want to be careful, and talk
quieter, or you'll wake everybody up.
They're out like a light.
I hope they have a dress shop.
I've never worn the same thing two days in
a row before.
Let's take a nap later.
Well, no crowds.
We must have missed the summer rush.
We keep missing everything.
This is one kooky, mixed-up world.
Let's go!
Huh?
Do you smell that?
I don't smell anything.
What is it?
It's the delicious odor of food.
Food?
Are you sure?
Very sure.
And plenty of it.
Show us where, Kabuman!
It's this way!
Follow me!
Wait for us!
Oh, boy!
Hurry!
Huh?
Hey, wait for me!
Look at that spread!
Wow!
Sorry for saying this, everybody,
but this looks like a set-up.
Matt is right.
It could be some sort of trap.
What?
Agumon, are you guys sure that food is
safe to eat?
Everyone's eating, but their table manners
are appalling.
Guess that's because they like it.
That's it.
I can't bear to look any longer.
I'm gonna eat it.
At least I won't die hungry.
On your mark?
Get set?
Oh.
Uh.
Mmm.
Lobster, maitre d', is there a table with
a view?
Oh, peanut butter and pickles,
this is the best pizza ever!
Okay, if one of us gets sick, we all get
sick.
Hey, pass the mashed potatoes.
That's teamwork, too.
Potato chips, chocolate chips,
fish and chips.
Oh, dear.
Any kind of chips.
Oh, this is delicious, but I'm not allowed
to get it.
Chief, what are we having for dessert?
Heads up, Matt.
Watch the hair, dude.
Is that what that is?
I thought some bird made a nest on your
head.
Warm water is perfect for removing soil
and epidermis.
You know, dirt and dead skin.
Whenever my skin gets dirty, I just shed
it.
That would be difficult for me.
Uh, may I join you?
Hey, don't be shy.
There aren't any girls here.
Come on in.
So far, we haven't found any sharks in the
water.
No big ones.
It looks cold.
Humans can be so silly.
Humans aren't the only silly ones.
Where's Gabumon?
He's not silly.
Just shy.
I'll get in, but I won't guarantee that
I'll like it.
Why do they have to be so noisy?
Okay, I like it.
Relax.
Forget about them.
I've never been so relaxed in my whole
life.
Gabumon, you're not supposed to be over
here.
Get back to the boy side!
Hey!
Let go!
Whoa!
Beds!
Boy, this feels great.
The last time I had a bed this soft,
I was dreaming.
How I've missed sleeping on soft,
silky sheets.
Hmm.
I'll tell you what I don't miss.
I don't miss hiking through the blazing
hot desert.
And another thing I really don't miss is
starving in the jungle.
Oh.
We are a long way from home.
Sorry.
That's okay, Joe.
We all miss being home,
and I'm sure that we're
all wondering if we'll
ever get back there.
I'll bet our disappearance caused a big
fuss at school and all over town.
But we've been gone so long, everybody
must have given up looking for us by now.
Mom and Dad wouldn't stop.
I'm homesick, aren't you?
We'll find our way back.
Don't worry, Mimi.
Let's just go to sleep and try to have
nice dreams.
Good night, guys.
Good night, girls.
Good night, everyone.
It was so easy to deceive them.
Even the Digi-Destined appeared to have
childish and simple minds.
Ready?
What a joy to be rid of the Digi-Destined
at last.
And you, Leomon.
I cannot disobey your orders.
I can go to the bathroom by myself.
I don't mind keeping you company,
Ty.
It's dark and scary here.
For your information, I happen to like the
dark.
Stop treating me like a kid.
I should have known it was you who were
afraid to go to the bathroom by yourself.
Oh, Ty, don't be upset with me.
I'm not afraid.
I didn't really have to go to the
bathroom.
I just came along because I have to
protect you.
Then what are you doing in there?
I don't even want to talk about it,
Ty.
I don't know if that ugly green guy scared
you, but he really scared me.
And who knows where he is now?
Now I am going to destroy you both.
Wake up, everybody!
Ogremon is here!
Oh, boy!
I must obey.
Destroy them.
The children.
Why do you hate me?
He hates you because I commanded him to
hate you.
Whoa!
Get ready, Ty.
Now the real trouble starts.
Agumon, who is that?
That's Devamon.
He looks bad.
He is.
This is the guy who invented the
nightmare.
I have no further use for this imaginary
building.
Wake up, everybody!
Something's wrong!
What happened?
Huh?
Because together you are
strong, I will use my touch
of evil to scatter you
throughout the Digiworld!
I hope this is a bad dream.
Ty!
What?
I'm too weak to walk, even after all that
food I've eaten.
Huh?
The food, the bath, the building,
none of it was real.
I created all of it in your imagination.
Listen, you.
If you don't bring back my friends,
you're gonna be in really big trouble.
That's amusing.
My concerns are much more important than
your friends.
That's my only concern.
You bring them back now!
Bring them back?
You impudent brat, you dare to order me?
Allow me to show you who's really in
control here.
You see, I have discovered the secret of
the Black Gears from below.
I call them forth to do my bidding.
You and your friends happened upon this
tiny island, which is just one of the
fragments of the old world, scattered
across an enormous ocean.
You pretend you are strangers who know
nothing of this, but I am aware that you
are the DigiDestined who were sent to
rescue this world from my domination.
You got us all wrong.
We were just some kids at summer camp who
somehow got sucked into your world.
Your little act no longer amuses me.
It's time to bring an end to the
DigiDestined.
I will destroy them.
What?
Everyone.
Now the boy.
Yes, then the others, one by one.
Once those irritating children are out of
the way, nothing will be able to stop me.
Now, do it, Leomon.
As you command.
No!
Help!
Don't waste your breath.
What are you waiting for, Leomon?
Do it!
It's the black gear.
The light drove it out.
Devamon no longer has control over Leomon.
I think you're right.
How do you feel, Leomon?
I am free of Devamon's powers.
Leomon, do you know what this thing is?
I can tell you that for me it is proof
that you are one of the DigiDestined.
The Digivices are powerless.
In the hands of anyone else.
That's right.
And you are no match for me.
Do not harm them.
Leomon is helping us.
We're going to be fine.
This isn't over, Leomon.
Why have you forgotten your old friend?
Ogremon!
Here, Leomon!
Your soft card is your weakness.
We will never join as allies.
And you will never know true power.
You may defeat me.
But the DigiDestined will be out of your
reach.
No!
Yes!
Go now!
Why?
You're our last hope.
Without you, my world doesn't stand a
chance of survival.
My life is insignificant!
You can escape too!
I must prevent Devamon from pursuing you!
Be careful!
Feel the touch of evil!
Leomon!
The DigiDestined survived our first
encounter.
But it won't be the last.
I can promise them that.
They must not interfere with my plans.
They must be destroyed!
Will you do this for me, Leomon?
Your every order.
I shall obey.