I guess it's my turn to fill you guys in.
First, we have a close call with these
twin metal dinosaur-looking creatures.
Then, when we're about to crash for the
night, wouldn't you know it?
We're camped out right
on top of a big wicked
serpent thing who goes
by the name of Seedramon.
That's when things got intense.
I got snatched up and Gabumon digivolved
into a huge blue wolf called Garurumon.
Lucky for me, Seedramon was no match.
Whenever we're in danger, our Digimons get
bigger and help us.
Now THAT'S COOL!
Digimon, digital monsters, Digimon are the
champions!
Change into digital champions to save the
digital world.
Digimon, digital monsters, Digimon are the
champions!
Digimon, Digimon are the champions.
Digimon, enter champions.
Digimon, digimon...
Whoa, hey!
Whoa, did you hear that?
It seems to be some sort of aircraft.
It looked like a big flying gear.
Admit it, my alien theory is becoming more
plausible.
Yeah, they hit us with an anti-gravity ray
to make us all crooked.
Or maybe that sign's just crooked.
Whoa!
TK!
That was scary.
Watch it.
That could have been a snake, or worse.
Oh boy, I'm sorry.
Hey, Biomon, are there really snakes here?
No, just giant flying killer bugs and
other unpleasant Digimon.
Don't you worry, TK.
I'll take care of them.
Okay, now that that's settled,
let's get going.
Nothing's settled, and where would we go?
We don't even know where we are.
This is silly.
I say we keep moving and see if we can
find any signs of intelligent life here.
Hey, wait a minute.
Is he saying that Digimon are not
intelligent?
Is that what he's saying?
Not at all.
But I think Ty is right.
We need to keep moving in hopes of finding
out where we are.
We need to stay calm and stick together.
Let's remember, we're in this together.
Together sounds good.
We can do it.
This will take teamwork.
And I'm sure we'll figure out exactly
where we are and how to get back.
There's no point in splitting up because
then, once somebody did figure it out, we...
Hey, Sora, open your eyes.
Well, thanks a lot for waiting.
Moving right along, folks.
Keep it moving.
Our next stop on the tour will be the
forest of irrelevant road signs.
No pictures, please.
We're lost and these guys are making
jokes.
Hey, wait up.
My shoelace is broken.
You need new shoes.
Ooh, new shoes.
Look!
Telephone poles.
I say we follow them and see where they
lead.
They'll just lead to trouble.
Look, it's the alien saucer again.
And it's headed for a close encounter.
Why, it's so hot I can feel the heat
coming up through my socks.
Well, TK, maybe you should put your shoes
back on.
Oh, this hot desert air is destroying my
complexion.
How much further is it?
Is that all you're worried about,
Mimi?
We'll be lucky if we even survive this
hike.
Hey, does anybody besides me see that these
telephone poles have no connecting wires?
She's right.
I wonder if these actually are telephone
poles.
Maybe they're some odd alien equivalent.
Hey, remember those phone booths and that
streetcar?
Yeah, what about them?
Oh, nothing.
I was just wondering if anybody else
remembered.
That's it.
Doomed.
The heat has baked our brains and we're
all gonna end up like roasted piglets.
Just remain calm, Joe.
We've only been walking for two minutes.
Izzy, come here, Izzy.
I think we'd better find some shade for
Joe.
And quick.
You won't believe what happened to my
favorite watch.
Hmm?
What?
The sun melted the numbers right off.
Mimi, for somebody who hates hiking,
you sure have a lot of compasses.
Huh?
Of course, none of them actually work.
Oh, this dirt contains small traces of
metal which could affect the compass needle.
Oh, well.
I'm always late anyway.
This is one weird world and I don't like
it one little bit.
I think we should start looking for water,
guys.
Otherwise, we could dehydrate in all this
heat.
Yeah.
But we're doing okay for now, aren't we?
Help!
I've taken a soil sample,
measured the barometric
pressure, and analyzed
the relative humidity.
And what did you find out?
It's really, really hot.
Hang on just a little longer.
Don't give up now.
We're gonna be okay.
Just keep moving along.
My head is baking.
If this goes on too much longer,
I'm going to look like a wilted salad.
Here, you wear my hat for a while.
Well, you need it more than I do.
Thank you, Mimi.
Hey, you.
What's that yucky smell?
Ugh.
Here's a thought.
Now you know why they call them sweat
socks.
This beach would be a lot more popular if
it just had a couple more things.
Like an ocean, a gentle breeze,
snack bar, hunky lifeguards.
Hold it.
I have to stop.
I just don't think that I can go any
faster.
You have to stay positive.
Let's all pretend that it's rainy.
Yeah!
That's a great idea.
I simply adore the rain.
Me too, but it's time for a reality check.
This isn't getting any better.
It might be a good idea to turn around and
get out of this desert right now.
You mean before we all have a power
outage?
I'll vote for that.
Wait.
Hold on for just a second, everybody.
If I'm seeing what I think
I'm seeing... What is it, Ty?
Mm-hmm.
It's not a mirage.
It's real water.
Water?
This is fantastic.
Now all we need are some lemon,
sugar, and some big fat ice cubes.
That looks like a village.
Maybe we'll find people.
And Shaggy.
Maybe they'll have hats for sale.
Hang on.
Water and food.
I'm hungry enough to eat broccoli.
What's broccoli?
Is that a joke?
Great.
Let's get out of this desert.
Yay!
Hooray!
From so far away, everything looks so big.
But they're so cute and tiny.
Okay, question.
Who here knows where we can get a drink?
And just what do Giant Digimon drink?
Me?
I'm no Digimon.
My friend Zora is what's called a human
being.
Yes, we know they look funny.
In spite of this, they are all actually
very nice.
What's a human being?
If you are not Digimon, what are you doing
here in DigiWorld?
This is great.
There is no way we are all going to fit
into this place.
Relax, Joe.
At least the natives here are friendly.
Oh, my.
I would just love to
take one home and put it
on my bed with all my
other stuffed animals.
Hmph.
There she goes again.
Do you think Mimi hears the same things we
hear?
I'm not sure anymore.
Maybe she's an alien spy.
Kike is tired and hungry.
He's not the only one.
Beelon, just when did you digivolve?
When I met Sora, we share a special bond
which is magical.
You don't talk like us anymore.
Is that how all Beelon talk?
No, it's how the big ones talk.
I suppose I just picked it up from Sora.
She is a wonderful and kind human being
and I've already learned a lot from her.
We still don't understand how you
Digivolve.
What is it about being around human beings
that makes it happen?
Sora needed me.
I had to protect her.
She had to protect me?
Power came flowing through me.
I didn't know why I was.
Wait a sec.
Now I get it.
That's why she's always following me
around.
All of a sudden I realized I had
Digivolve.
When Tai needed him, Agamon Digivolve to
Graymon to protect him.
And Gururumon did the same for Matt.
They Digivolve for us.
We're lucky kids.
Sora!
We're invited to have dinner with the
Yoko's.
They said they'd be willing to share their
food with all of us.
Oh, wow.
Yay!
I wonder what they will be serving.
Perhaps some bone with meat?
Lettuce topped with fish?
Water!
Water?
Look everybody!
A fresh water fountain!
Hooray!
All of the water here is piped in from a
spring at Mihirashi Mountain.
It's the best water in the world.
Forget the world.
Mount Mihirashi water is the best in all
the galaxy.
Where's Mount Mihirashi?
Out there!
That's a live volcano.
Yes, but the heat boils away all the
germs.
If I'm not mistaken, that noise precedes
an eruption.
That's cold, but I still didn't get a
drink.
What is happening?
The water evaporated!
That's okay because the lake is always
full of water.
I'll check it out.
Let's all go.
The water's all gone!
Goodness, where did it go?
Somebody pulled the plug.
Alright, let's not panic.
Huh?
Dry as a bone.
I won't give up.
Huh?
Look!
Ty's doing a little dance for us!
Is that supposed to stop the fire or bring
down the rain?
Hey!
Do you remember that flying gear we saw
earlier?
It crashed right into a hillside.
Great.
Of all the hillsides out there,
the gear crashes into Mihirashi Mountain.
That's the place where the water comes
from.
That's right.
The water comes from a lake on the top of
Mount Mihirashi.
So a gear crashing into the mountain could
affect our water supply.
Mm-hmm.
We don't dare go up there.
The mountain is guarded by a fiery Digimon
called Merimon.
He's hideously dangerous.
I want a closer look at that mountain.
You say this character Merimon is a fiery
Digimon?
What does he look like?
Never mind!
There he is!
He's coming!
He's coming our way!
He burns up everything he touches!
He never comes down off the mountain
though!
This is very strange behavior for him!
Ah!
I'm burning!
Too hard!
Merimon is a fiery Digimon!
There's no reason he should be in pain
from his own flames!
That's his nature!
This is weird!
He's crying!
Burning!
Sounds like he's out of his mind with
pain!
What do we do?
Burning!
Look!
He's coming straight toward the village!
Hey everybody!
We gotta understand what we're going to
do!
I've never seen him move so fast!
He's already reached the foot of the
mountain!
And now he's starting to enter the forest!
Ah!
Everybody freeze!
Stay very still!
You're gonna need more than sunscreen to
stop me!
Don't move a muscle!
Burn!
Unfreeze!
Okay, settle down!
There's room for all of you!
Will you please stop squirming!
Here's the next batch, Matt!
Easy now!
You'll be okay!
Who's not here?
The Yoko's!
I'll take care of them!
This is bad!
Run!
Come on!
Everyone keep moving now!
Just follow the one in front of you!
Hey, you've got to save yourself!
Come down while there's still time!
I can't leave here until all my friends
are safe, Sora!
Alright!
I suppose I'll just have to come up there
after you then!
Hurry!
Sora, you'll never make it!
Hey, where's Sora going?
Sora, come back!
Oh, good!
They're all safe now!
Watch out!
Viamon!
He's right behind you!
Go away, Marymon!
Leave us alone!
We're not bothering you!
Viamon!
I'm coming, Viamon!
Woo!
Are you okay?
Sure!
I hope I never do that again!
It wasn't very fun!
Thank you for coming to rescue me!
Don't mention it!
That's what a friend is for!
You can say that again!
My friend!
Uh-oh!
We're still in great danger, Sora!
What?
You stay here!
It's my turn to rescue you now!
You think you're really hot stuff!
Well, you're in big trouble now!
And I'll spiral twister!
Ha!
Okay, Big Red, take that!
And that!
Is that the best you have to offer,
Wigley?
We gotta help her out!
He's too big to handle!
Yeah!
Fireball!
Catch!
Oh no!
She's hit!
Be your mom!
Come on, everyone!
We can beat that monster!
What we need is teamwork!
I'm ready!
Give him a shot!
Yikes!
We need a fire extinguisher!
That made him bigger!
Ugh!
Why do I suffer so?
If we knew why he was crying, it might
help to stop him!
Uh, fire's not affecting him!
I'm guessing it's not heartburn!
Maybe this monster just has growing pains!
Growing pains?
Meh!
This is not a time to joke!
Better get ready!
Here I come!
Ah!
Zara?
We're all in trouble now!
Merrimon can not be allowed to win!
My friends need my help now!
Come on!
Digivolve to...
Reimond Digivolve to rescue us!
What's wrong where you're not afraid of
me?
Let's fight!
Here!
Have a...
Don't turn your back!
It was a gear!
What is it?
It made him crazy!
Right!
I suppose if you had
a big black gear stuck
inside of you, you'd
act a little crazy too!
The poor guy!
Yay!
Bill Mom did it!
Every time I'm in danger, Bill Mom comes
to my rescue.
That's what I call a friend.
Are you alright?
Oh, Sora!
Oh, B.
I was so worried about you.
You're great.
I can't begin to tell you how proud I am
of you.
I wasn't the least bit afraid.
All I could think about was saving you
because...
Well, you know...
Miramon, why did you attack our village?
I couldn't stop myself.
That must have been awful for you.
If you couldn't control yourself,
who was controlling you?
The last thing I remember is being hit by
that gear.
Well, we're just happy to see that you're
back to normal.
I hope nothing like this ever happens
again.
You're needed to protect Mount Mihirashi.
Goodbye, Miramon!
May you always stay well!
Goodbye!
And please, try not to burn down our
village anymore, okay?
Hey!
I just remembered you never got that
dinner we promised you.
You must be starving.
My tummy's ready for some action.
What is this stuff?
Be polite and just eat it.
A gracious guest never insults his host
cooking.
Hmm... I can't tell if it's even been
cooked.
Eat as much as you want.
We have more than enough for seconds.
Yeah, well, there's probably a good reason
for that.
You know, that's exactly what I was afraid
you were going to say.
It smells better than broccoli.
Who knows?
Might taste better.
Has anybody noticed?
We talk a lot about food.
Nah, I'm not hungry.
I'm skipping this one, too.
I just don't like to eat on an empty
stomach.
Besides, I don't even know what that stuff
is, but I'm sure I'm allergic to it.
And so ends my biggest adventure yet with
Beomar.
One thing's for certain, for being so
little, she sure has a huge heart.
and I can.
Batteria and