I certainly had my hands full looking for
that elusive eighth child, and at the same
time trying to hide Tentemon from my
parents.
For some unexplained
reason, there was a
strange Digivice signal
moving all over town.
It confused everybody, including
Demidevilmon.
Meanwhile, Kabuterimon really got a nose
fill when he went up against Raremon,
a very odorous Digimon with a body
structure unlike any I've ever seen before.
But ultimately, he was no match for
Kabuterimon.
Most curious, with all this excitement,
you'd think he were back in the Digiworld.
Greg Platt Digimon!
Digitle Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
istaigg gloryistッ character
Digimon, it's your champion.
Digimon monsters, Digimon are the
champions.
Digimon, Digimon monsters, Digimon are the
Digimon, Digimon...
Ah, darkness.
The perfect cloak for my evil.
Ideal conditions for producing fear.
Human blood always tastes better with a
dash of fear in it.
What is that?
A carriage?
I hate this fog!
Master, where are you?
I'm getting mildew on my wings!
Aha!
Finally!
Sheesh, you couldn't take a cap like
everyone else!
At
last, I was starting to worry!
Calm down.
I went out to have a bite to eat and to
get familiar with the city.
It is always so difficult to get a good
meal when one is away from home.
Yeah, right!
So what do we do next, boss?
We are continuing the search for the
eighth child.
The details are of no concern to you.
Well, as I always say, uh, whatever you
say!
Aw, come on.
Where did I put that thing?
Junk.
Stuff.
More junk.
More stuff.
Man, I was a messy kid.
I can't believe how unorganized I was.
Whatcha doin'?
Looking for my old phone book.
It'll have exactly what I need.
And I'm helping!
How come?
And now, today's top story.
The monsters that are plaguing the city.
Still no official
comment on where the
creatures are from or
what they might be after.
We will keep you updated throughout the
day.
Meanwhile, in other news,
health officials report young
women all over the city are
being hospitalized for anemia.
Just a moment!
No word on whether the cases are
connected.
But doctors are voicing
concern that so many seemingly
healthy young women are
being struck down so suddenly.
Ty, it's your friend Izzy!
Coming!
Oh!
Hey!
Ready to go?
Agumon, you digivolved!
You bet I did!
All I needed was a good meal!
Psst!
It's me!
Tentomon!
Nice disguise, dude!
Thanks, Ty.
I put it together myself.
Wait till Mimi sees you.
I need one, too!
Yeah.
Any ideas?
Mm-hmm.
Yes, I think so!
Hey, Charlie!
Over here!
Yeah, real inconspicuous.
So, Ty, did you find your address book
from school?
Oh, uh, well, Sora was in my class,
so I thought we'd just use hers.
Uh-huh.
Couldn't find it, huh?
All right, listen up, everybody.
I called you all here today because,
well, uh, there was nothing good on TV.
Ha-ha.
Very funny, Ty.
So where are the others?
Hey, wait!
Don't start without me!
Good morning.
Okay, so where's Mimi?
She's probably out buying clothes.
Oh, get out and walk!
You're too heavy to push!
Mimi, how's that going to look?
I'm supposed to be a little baby!
You just grew up.
Now get out!
Hey, did you guys see it?
It was all over the news on TV this
morning.
More and more of Myotismon's digibozos are
popping up in the city.
And they're very real.
What do you mean?
The last time we came back, there were
Digimon all over the place, like now.
But only Kari and I could see them.
Everybody else walked right by them,
as if they weren't even there.
Now even normal people see them and
they're on the news and everything.
It's like they're really here this time.
Maybe it's because this time they came
through the gate that Myotismon made.
I don't like it.
If they can be seen, then they're
physically here.
And if they're here physically,
they can do a whole lot of damage.
Yeah, like what?
Do I really need to remind you what those
evil Digimon are capable of?
Creepy!
Complete systems failure.
So what are we sitting around here for?
We better get out there and find that
eighth kid if we want to stop these guys.
Save the Digi world and we'll save our
own!
Go, Ty!
Uh-huh.
What's the plan?
Well, I've got a few.
I want to hear Izzy's theory!
Don't start until I get there!
I love Izzy's theories!
Hold on!
Alright, we won't start without you.
We've already concluded that when the
Digimon attacked four years ago,
all of us, including the eighth child,
were there.
It is also safe to assume that each of us
were given Digivices for a reason.
Last night, I picked up an unidentified
Digivice reading.
I think it was the eighth child.
Obviously, I lost a signal.
But it's clear that the eighth child is in
this vicinity.
That's why the monsters are here,
too.
Monsters worse than snakes!
And this is supposed to help us?
I'm lost!
My conclusion is that the eighth child is
somewhere in one of these address books.
Somehow, we have to
make a lot of calls and patrol
the city for monster
attacks at the same time.
Well, I guess I could do some calling,
as long as my folks don't find out.
But I really gotta do
some serious studying, so
I won't be able to go
on the search with you.
What?
Joe, it's summer!
I'm getting an early start.
This year, I'm really gonna be prepared.
Here, then!
If you're not coming with us, then you
might as well do my calling for me, okay?
Thanks!
Joe, we're talking about the fate of the
world here.
If you're gonna chicken out, you can call
all the names in my book, too.
See ya!
Yes, it might make more sense
having one person concentrate
on all the phone calling
rather than split it up.
He has a point there.
Good luck!
Wait a minute.
No, Ty!
Not yours, too!
Please!
I'm not that kind of guy, Joe.
Don't worry.
It's my job, and you've got enough on your
plate.
Oh man, Ty, you're a totally great guy.
Thanks a lot.
Well, you know.
Mr. Generous.
I bet he couldn't find his address book.
Well, how'd you ever guess?
Whoa, look at all that damage from last
night's battle.
And there'll be a lot more, too,
if this goes on.
We've gotta hurry up and find that eighth
child.
We will.
We're not called the Digidestined for
nothing.
Master, are we almost there yet?
Cause all this water's making me queasy!
Those Digidestined brats are probably
miles away by now!
Look,
that fog's coming in again.
I've never seen anything like it.
At the same time, we're having the hottest
weather on record.
And I heard that somebody saw snow falling
last night.
The ozone layer must be messed up worse
than we thought.
Welcome, O Great One.
All is ready.
Perfect, Gatomar.
As always, you have done excellent work.
Hey, Whiskers, what do you think you're
doing?
I don't think I know why I'm here.
I'm finding the eighth child.
That's my job, furball.
I'm in charge here.
Yeah, right.
Listen up, Puss in Boots.
Quit sucking up to the Master.
I'm the Master's cute little pet.
Get me with a furball!
It's really hard to feel threatened by a
bowling ball with feathers.
Just keep out of my way.
I'm finding that kid, not you.
Got it?
Take a catnap, kitty litter!
That flappy-winged Joker couldn't find
water if he fell out of a boat.
Okay, so we'll split up into pairs so we
can cover more of the city.
Got it?
Got it.
Let's go!
Good luck, everybody!
I see food!
Agumon, keep your mind on our mission,
okay?
Anything?
You can't catch me!
Come on!
Yeah!
You got it!
No, there's nothing yet.
Aw, it doesn't look like he's down here.
That would have been too easy anyway.
Yeah, right.
Hi, I know this is kind of strange,
but I was in second grade with you.
Hey, stop pushing!
I am not pushing you!
You're kicking me!
You crossed the line onto my side,
you big cheater!
I am not a cheater!
You're a liar!
I'm telling!
Knock it off!
If you two keep fooling around,
someone's gonna get hurt!
I know how they feel!
Just walking around in this heat's enough
to make anybody cranky!
You know what this is, Sora?
A big fat drag!
Hey, dude!
What silly creatures!
Pea-brained dolts!
Laugh it up!
When my Otis-mon is through, you won't be
laughing!
Miko!
Come back here!
Where'd you go?
Miko!
What a funny looking kitty!
Hi there!
Are you a friend of Agumon?
Huh?
Are you one of them?
Meow!
What's your name?
Wait!
Don't go!
Hmm... So, she
knows about Agumon.
Hmm... Is it possible this
little squirt is the eighth child?
Hey!
I know you're there!
You can come in if you want to!
Mom's not home!
Weather experts can't explain the
unseasonable fog.
In fact, they have no
explanation for any of the
bizarre weather conditions
we've been having.
Including this heat wave.
I'm not meant for this kind of work.
If I ever have a baby, I'm gonna hire
somebody to push her around.
That's for sure.
Hold on!
How about a break, okay?
Again?
We'll make it quick.
Ahhh... Last night I got to
sleep in a soft bed with the A.C.
cranked up.
Watching my own TV.
Wasn't that the best, Palmont?
Dinner was really something, too.
Wasn't it great?
My mom knows all the best take-out places
in the city.
She never has to cook.
Zora's mom made our dinner and it was
terrific!
Well, all of it except for this kind of
green mushy stuff.
What's it called?
What?
Spinach.
Now let's see.
Where was I?
Hmm... Would you look at that?
She's not even tired.
You're different.
You like to take things easy.
Finding this kid's harder than finding a
good sail.
Hey, Sora, if we
really want to find this
kid, we should go where
lots of people gather.
You thinking of any place in particular?
Yep!
Right there!
Uh-huh!
Besides, we can see the whole city from up
there.
Really get the lay of the land,
you know?
Charging addition.
Wow, look how high it goes!
Look at the whole city yet!
Ah, there!
Isn't that better?
Nice and cool!
I knew this place would have A.C.
Feels great!
Should've guessed you had an ulterior
motive.
Isn't your house over there?
Yeah.
It sure is strange being back in our own
world again.
Does it feel like it's getting warmer?
Yeah, it does!
Let's move over closer to the blowers!
There!
That's more like it!
Wonderful!
What happened to the air?
Maybe this heat wave finally got to be too
much for it.
Ah!
Look at that weirdo wearing a coat in this
heat!
And such an ugly one, too!
Hey, Mimi, be quiet!
He'll hear ya!
Oh, and what's he gonna do?
See?
He heard ya!
I told you!
Uh-oh!
I guess that explains the coat!
Is it me, or did it just get hotter all of
a sudden?
I didn't notice!
Look up at the tower, it's almost like
it's bending!
Impossible!
Wait a minute!
Oh, no!
We got trouble!
Get ready for my needle spray!
Hey, hey!
Oh!
Tell the heart!
Explain this to us, Albumon.
Just who is this guy?
He's Skull Merrimon.
His element is fire.
He's tough and he can sure dish it out.
Metal Fireball!
The tower is going to fall on the city.
Grab it, come up to remind us!
Know not to play with fire!
Are you ready?
Yeah!
Agumon, did you fall?
Ramos!
Great,
now we've really made him mad.
He swallowed that Nova blast like a hot
fudge sundae.
All it did was make him stronger!
Unless Greymon digivolves again,
he's toast!
Lights me, Jimmy!
Watch out!
This guy is scary!
Metal fireball!
While the Clash of the Monsters caused
extensive damage to the tower, no casualties.
..
She isn't so bad, for a human.
Better company than some Digimon,
that's for sure.
But fear is in the air, and there's a
general feeling of public unrest.
Now back to our regular programming.
Still, orders are orders,
and I'm not going to
be the one who lets
the eighth child get away.
Hi!
Huh?
Uh... Come here!
Are you going already?
But you'll come back again, right?
Her sweetness makes me lose my edge.
But I'll be back, and next time I'll be
ready for her.
While no one knows where these monsters
are from, or why they're here,
it's clear the Earth is at some sort of
crossroads.
The question is, down which road does our
destiny awake?
That's okay.
Tomorrow...
That's great.
This was a bad.
This is from Conference从 Games將.
Welcome to
the에서도 Cookie Fくbpo Island.
Subscribe and share of our newsletter
moves at somebody else's class.
It's out to join us.
Create cyber nikki a lunatic course.
It's two eggshells that are right.
So just wait for any good stuff.
Now I can change okays territory,...
Is a social worker's way to leave it in.