We had to get across town to find the
eighth child, so he took the subway.
Yokomon got mad at a baby and nearly gave
us all away.
Next, the other kids bought food with our
traveling money, so we had to find a ride.
Luckily, Sora's cousin came by and picked
us up.
He turned out to be a real jerk,
though.
He accidentally knocked Izzy off a bridge,
and Tentomon had to save him.
Then Gesomon appeared, and Akakuman had to
take him out.
What a nightmare.
And to think, there are people who do this
commute every day.
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Change into Digital Champions to save the
Digital World!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Digimon!
Defeated?
You say those little punks beat Mammothmon
and Gasoman?
Right!
Gadamon really bungled it when she hooked
up with those nincompoops.
I guess she's no better than the rest of
us.
Think that's funny?
Of course not, boss!
Then knock off the chatter and find the
eighth child before I lose my patience.
Aye, aye!
My Otis Man rules!
You'll see!
Gee, Ty, I sure hope that your sister
Kari's over her nasty cold.
Me too.
You know, it's really weird.
The last time we were here, she remembered
what had happened four years ago.
Oh, wow!
Do you think it's possible that Kari's the
eighth child?
Here, Miko!
Meow!
Is everything all right, sweetie?
Hi!
Everything's just fine.
What was wrong with Grandma?
She took a bit of a fall, that's all.
She sprained her ankle when she was out
for a walk, but it's not serious.
She has to stay in the
hospital for a day and she's
hopping mad because it
cuts into her dancing lesson.
That's Grandma.
Here.
Thanks, sweet pea.
Grandma was worried
about your cold and said
Daddy should remember
your sweater next time.
I feel back to normal now.
Oh!
You look much better, but let's just check
to make sure.
You feel about as cool as a cucumber.
I'm back!
Hi!
Ty?
Why are you here?
Camp was canceled because it snowed.
Snow?
Who would have thought at this time of
year?
The weather's getting so unpredictable
these days.
Oh, what's that?
Huh?
I brought Kari home a present.
Great.
Give me your dirty clothes so I can wash
them.
Mom!
Ty, did something happen?
I'm glad you're here.
Of course I am.
What's this all about, son?
Oh, is something wrong?
Oh!
Huh?
Really?
I'm sure your kids aren't that bad.
I'm telling you, you're so lucky to have a
boy like Izzy.
He's the perfect example of a gentleman
and so smart.
You know, my little
rascals are always fighting
all the time and never
listen to a word I say.
Mom, tell Billy to get me back by truck.
Like, don't stick your tongue out at your
brother.
I'm home!
Izzy?
Hi, Mom.
I came home ahead of schedule.
Didn't you like camp?
Huh?
The food was inferior.
That's all?
And then it snowed, so they cancelled
everything.
Oh.
Never think about how I feel.
I just wish they were as good as your
Izzy.
Sometimes he's too considerate.
So why can't I use the door?
Izzy, is something wrong?
Hide!
What am I, a molemon?
Honey, are you alright?
I'm fine, Mom!
Huh?
Right now?
Uh, yeah, I'm borrowing one of his
reference books.
I'll be back in a nanosecond.
A suspicious life form has been spotted in
the bay.
There's speculation that it is some kind
of monster.
It's possible that it could be a whale,
but it seems very unlikely.
There may be some connection
between this monster and
the giant elephant and bird
that attacked a nearby town.
Time for sports, starting with baseball.
I'm back!
Dinner's almost ready.
My parents won't appreciate this,
but I think it's imperative.
Why?
What's the big deal, Izzy?
We'd be in big trouble if my mom and dad
came in here and discovered you.
I'm positive that they'd never comprehend
our situation.
I guess you have a point there.
Oh, by the way... What?
I don't know too much about
humans, me being a Digimon
and all, but I can tell
you one thing for sure.
Your mom is a really kind lady.
And if you don't mind me saying so,
she's not bad looking for a human.
Mm-hmm.
I have to say I completely agree.
She's cool.
Darling, one of these
days we're going to
have to tell Izzy the
truth about his birth.
Couldn't we wait just a little bit longer?
I'm afraid that if we tell him now,
it'll be too big of a shock.
I wouldn't want it to affect his
schoolwork.
But sometimes I wonder if he doesn't sense
it.
He's smart.
I have a strange
feeling that he knows he
was adopted, that
he's not really our child.
Why do you think that, dear?
Did he say anything?
No, it's just a mother's intuition.
Oh, my gosh.
Yoo-hoo, Digimon to Izzy.
Huh?
I'm sorry, pal.
I guess I kind of zoned out.
Izzy, are you in there?
Uh, what is it?
Dinner's ready.
Just a minute!
If you have a friend over, he can join us,
too.
I thought I heard someone speaking to you
in a funny-sounding voice.
Is that what I heard?
Izzy?
Oh, no, no, Mom.
That was me, yeah.
I'm practicing my new comedy act.
Uh-huh.
They're having a talent
show at the children's
center, and the winner
could win a new computer.
Who tell jokes?
Why was Newton surprised when he was hit
on the head by an apple?
Gee, I don't know why.
He was sitting under a pear tree.
Oh!
What's black and white and green?
Two skunks running over a pickle.
I'm sorry.
I guess I'm not very funny.
What do you mean?
You were hysterical.
I can't believe it's my son.
My boy, the comedian.
Who would have known?
You were wonderful, dear.
You're a chip off the old block.
And all this time, I never knew you had a
sense of humor.
Bravo, Izzy!
That was a great performance for your
first time.
You really think so?
Sure thing.
Don't quit your day job, but you were
really very good.
That's right.
We're absolutely thrilled for you,
darling.
Well, thanks.
Oh.
Hmm.
Ugh.
Uh, Mom, would you mind at all if I ate
the rest of my dinner in my room?
Don't worry.
I won't make you eat anything that you
don't want to.
No, Mom.
It's nothing like that, really.
The way you cook is gastronomically
outstanding.
Thanks.
I appreciate everything you do.
Aww.
In fact, I believe you're the most
extraordinary Mom there is.
Oh, I left the water on.
Can I have some more?
Ty, this is your third helping.
It's been a long time since I've had such
great cooking.
Hey, mister, if you're
buttering me up for a
raisin allowance, you
can just forget about it.
Not only is your mom nice and pretty,
but she's an awesome cook.
Sure is.
Did you hear him?
He said that he appreciated us.
I never thought we'd be so lucky as to
have a son like him.
You're right about that, honey.
What is it, Ty?
You seem bummed.
Uh, I don't know.
I'm glad you're back.
I missed you when you were gone.
I missed you, too.
By the way, Kari, do you
remember something that
happened about four years
ago in Heighton View Terrace?
Tell me everything you know.
I remember that Koromon got really huge
and fought with a big bird monster.
And he beat him.
That's something I'll never forget.
Huh.
This may sound strange, but do you have
something called a digivice, Kari?
No.
What's that?
Like this.
Don't think so.
Well, forget about it.
I'm so sleepy.
Yeah, I am, too.
Good night.
Sleep tight, sleepyhead.
Sweet dreams, you're party poopers.
Oh.
Miko, where are you?
Talk about finding a needle in a haystack.
Sheesh!
What's that?
He's nearby!
The A-child had better watch out,
because he's a sick duck!
Jen and I made some modifications to my
computer that are truly awesome.
Ugh.
Now, this looks intriguing.
I wonder what it does.
Ugh.
Too bizarre.
How about another?
That's very demented.
Here's something.
It's a map of Tokyo.
What's that indicator?
There's an unidentified Digimon lurking in
the bay.
You're the only one that's still awake.
Ah!
Tentamon!
Hello, Mrs. Kamiya, this is Izzy.
I was wondering if time might be available
to come to the phone.
He's sleeping.
So, would you like me to wake him up?
No, I'm sorry to bother you.
I know it's late, but is Sora awake?
Is Matt home?
I'll call back tomorrow.
Gee, I guess everyone's asleep.
You should go to bed too, Izzy.
No way!
Jenna just told me that there's an
unidentified Digimon in the bay.
With everyone sound asleep, we may have to
tackle this Digimon by ourselves.
And I was having such a nice dream.
So, are you up for a challenge?
I'm with you, Izzy.
But may I suggest I wear a disguise so I
don't attract any unwanted attention.
He's about as repulsive as they come.
That Digimon is raremon.
Raremon smells like rotting fish,
looks like the inside of a trashcan,
and is someone you never want to meet in a
very dark alley.
What's wrong?
It's the eighth child.
He's very close.
Whoa, talk about bad timing.
If we lose that signal, we'll be doomed.
You search for the missing child while I
take care of old sewer breath.
I just hope his stink isn't contagious.
You can do it.
Do I have any other choice?
Are you ready to Digibob?
Yep.
Digimon.
Digimon are the champions.
Digimon monsters.
Digimon.
Tencomon Digibob 2.
Kabuterimon.
Digimon.
Look, it's my turn now.
Ty, sweetheart, wake up.
What is it, Mom?
I didn't want to wake
you, but Izzy called on the
phone, and he seemed to
be nervous about something.
Huh?
I wonder what's up.
Electro-sucker!
Breath of the cave!
He's here!
Hmm.
Huh?
This indicates he's moving.
Over there.
Hello?
Can I help you?
Oh, hello, Ty.
I hope that you had fun at camp.
It's a shame it was cut short.
And thank you for loaning Izzy that
reference book.
Iszy, we'd like to talk to you.
Are you asleep?
I'm sure he's very tired out from camp.
We should let him get a couple of Zs.
You're right.
I'll just tiptoe in and check up on him.
The door's locked.
He's closed.
I'll get there first!
We should be connecting soon.
Oh, don't worry.
I'm sure there's nothing to be concerned
about.
I know you're right, but he's acting
peculiar.
Izzy's never locked the door before.
He is getting older now.
I guess so.
But he was only at camp for half a day.
I wonder what happened to make him change
so much.
The signal's gone now.
What are you doing here?
It's a sucker!
Oh no, it's my face!
I'm gonna get you next time!
Wah!
I'm here at the scene of
the monster sighting, but
the predator in question
seems to have disappeared.
One wonders if there really was a monster
at all.
Hm?
Wait a minute, folks.
Look up there!
It looks like a giant flying cockroach,
and I don't think it's friendly.
Sorry you weren't able
to find the eighth child, but
at least we got rid of that
stinking mass of blubber.
Right!
I've been doing some extensive
calculations.
My theory is that the eighth child is
located here in the city.
It seems Ty had the right idea in the
first place.
We have to get back to his house right now
and give him an update.
Okay!
Unthinkable.
Is there no Digimon strong enough to
defeat these children?
I will have to deal with them myself.
It's very late.
Maybe we should wait until morning,
Tentamon.
All that exercise made me ultra-hungry.
I hate to be a pig, but you wouldn't
happen to have anything to munch on,
would you, Izzy?
I guess you do deserve a nutrition break.
I'll go look in the fridge.
Gee, thanks!
Ever since he got back, he seems like he's
been hiding something.
I just can't put my finger on it.
He's keeping something inside, and
he doesn't want to tell us what's wrong.
Even if he is, you can't blame him.
After all, we're hiding something from
him.
It's probably just a phase he's going
through.
Oh, I didn't mean to make them so worried.
I hope they forgive me.
I'm sure it'll be absolutely fine,
but I'll try to talk some sense into him.
No, don't.
What do you mean, hon?
Everybody thinks that he's always perfect,
but that's too much to expect of him.
We've got to give him some freedom to
become his own man.
You know, he's got to make mistakes.
That's part of what it is to be a kid.
Don't you think so?
Hmm.
I wonder what Izzy was all hyped up about
when he called tonight.
What happened to Miko?
He disappeared.
Oh, he'll be back.
It's the eighth child.
Gotta go!
The eighth what?
What a pretty star!
Ah!