Hey, Sora here.
Well, we had just finished crossing what
seemed like an uncrossable desert when we
found a village made up of thousands of
Yokomon under attack by Miramon.
He was really mad
because he had one of those
weird flying black gears
stuck inside his back.
We tried to get all of the
Yokomon away from the
village, but there were
just too many of them.
Biomon digivolved to Bergemon and was able
to drive out the black gear and destroy it.
Then Miramon and the village went back to
normal.
We'll just see how long that lasts.
Digimon, digital monsters, Digimon are the
champions!
Change into digital champions to save the
digital world!
Digimon, digital monsters, Digimon are the
champions!
Digimon.
We've passed this place before!
You mean we walked all the way around the
whole planet?
That just can't be.
I can't walk that far, can I?
I'm so tired.
My feet are hot.
Looks like we're taking a break.
Well, it's not like we have some place to
be.
I guess you're right.
There's no reason to hurry.
Check out Izzy.
I bet he's trying to email the aliens.
Maybe he's asking them to beam him up.
Still crashed and the warranty's expired.
Hey Izzy, I know how to get it to boot up.
You just gotta give it a couple of subtle
adjustments.
Hey, quit it!
Are your brain cells malfunctioning?
Gosh, you're acting like I'm hurting the
dumb thing.
Too bad your brain isn't as big as your
hair.
Maybe Izzy doesn't want grimy fingerprints
and dents all over his computer.
Huh?
Hmm.
What?
Hey, look.
Do you guys see that smoke over there?
I'll check it out.
Hey, Ty, wait for me!
The attention span of a gnat.
Uh, whatever.
We got graphics, we got sound.
Beautiful.
Up and running.
Huh?
But it indicates the battery needs
recharging.
Ah.
That's odd.
Hey everybody, get over here quick!
Huh?
We're coming, Ty!
Looks like some kind of factory.
Let's hope they can manufacture a way for
us to get home.
Hmm.
I wonder what they make in there.
I don't know, but wouldn't it be great if
there's a manufacturer's outlet store?
They always have killer deals!
Don't ask me how, but there doesn't seem
to be anybody here.
There's gotta be someone running the
equipment.
Uh, I don't know.
It appears to be doing quite well all by
itself.
Matt, what are the machines making?
You got me.
Maybe parts for robots or spaceships.
Somebody's gotta be moving those belts!
And people gotta eat!
So is there a cafeteria in this place?
Cause we can really use a good meal!
Hello?
Is anybody here?
Wait a minute!
Don't go any further in this direction!
What's the matter with this direction?
It's just as good as any other direction,
isn't it?
No, wait!
Hey!
What is it, Biomon?
I'm not sure!
I heard something!
Yeah?
Ah!
Doesn't sound good to me!
I say we go inside and have a look around!
Ah!
Prodigious!
Now a battery like that could run my
computer forever!
I wonder if there's a way to access its
power!
Hey!
Huh?
What do you suppose happened to him?
Who knows?
But let's see if we can help!
It's just a busted robot!
It's not a robot!
It's Andromon!
What?
This big clunk is a Digimon?
Yes!
And very much advanced!
Poor thing!
I guess he got caught in the gears and
that's how he got mangled!
Maybe if we work together we can pull him
out of there!
Uh, my mom really doesn't want me moving
any heavy objects.
Looks like a bad knees!
Relax!
We'll do it!
Right!
Hey!
What are you doing Izzy?
I'm trying to tap into this power source!
If I can get this baby to fire up, then we
can use my computer to get some help!
Hey, something's happening!
He's coming loose!
I think he's slowly coming too!
He needs a couple of whacks for a jump
start!
I am Andromon!
Where's this movie where a robot came to
life and ate everyone?
He looks friendly enough!
And I'm sure if we're nice to him,
he'll be nice to us!
Huh?
Forget what I said about him being
friendly!
I shall punish alien intruders!
Andromon is one of the most powerful
Digimon of all!
His body is a tireless machine capable of
almost anything!
Let's give him all we got!
Ah!
Spiral Twister!
Too bad we didn't catch him on a good day!
Watch out!
Maybe it is a good day!
This is not good!
Uh...
Well, Ty, what do we do now?
Agumon, how about trying to blast the
roof?
Uh-huh!
Boy, he's gonna have one ugly headache!
No doubt!
Now let's get out of here!
Whoa!
Hey!
This place would be a lot more interesting
if there was a tour guide to explain it!
Ooh!
Maybe with a little plaid outfit and a
bullhorn?
Aha!
I've located an access panel to the
interior operations!
Hey, let me see, Izzy!
Ooh!
What exactly do you think this is?
These markings are binary annotations of
some sort.
A computer program.
A very complicated program, indeed.
Hey!
Who turned out the lights?
I break out in hives in the dark.
What was that?
I hope it isn't Andromon.
It might be a good plan to keep on moving
so we don't have to find out!
Well, I'm for that.
Or we could just stay here frozen till the
monster gets us!
Let's sneak away!
Uh, can anyone explain why we're tiptoeing
instead of running for our lives?
Intruder sighting!
And Andromon doesn't like intruders!
Lightning Blaze!
Huh?
That was a smooth move, Izzy.
Scratch that theory.
Could I have possibly deleted the wrong
program?
I think that is a distinct possibility,
Izzy.
Why don't you try to undelete it?
Capital idea!
A stroke of metallic paint right here.
YOLA!
They didn't pay their power bill,
is that it?
You know, you have no imagination.
That's rather mysterious.
And just what is so mysterious about it?
Well, you see, batteries
are driven by an acidic
chemical reaction,
which generates a current.
But this one produces its own current
independently.
And what does that
mean in plain English for
those of us who didn't
major in engineering?
Give me a nano here.
I'll even give you three.
If I can decode this
particular program, then I can
trace its base functions
and figure a way out of here.
Let's get out of here!
Get closer!
Oh, this is not good!
I don't like this!
Come on, you guys!
Lightning wave!
And fire!
Recruiters!
Andromod will exact his vengeance!
Hey!
Come on!
Vengeance?
We're the ones that jump-started you,
remember?
I admire the way you keep working while
your friends are out having fun.
Don't you ever feel sort of left out?
Not at all!
So you would rather spend your time with
puzzles than with people?
Precisely.
What could be more fun than breaking a
cryptogram that nobody else can figure out?
I can think of a lot of things,
like relaxing on a nice warm beach and not
worrying about being trapped in a small
room with no exit.
But that's just me.
I'm just trying to determine how we all
got to this place.
And I'd like to learn more about you,
Digimon.
Perhaps prove some of my theories.
What are you theorizing about?
What's the big mystery?
I am who I am.
I'm not hiding anything.
Really?
I simply can't understand this
preoccupation with who you are.
Is there some kind of deep dark secret in
your origins?
Oh, well.
Don't you think it's time we told Izzy the
truth, dear?
No, I'm afraid.
If we told him now, it might be too big of
a shock.
I know you're trying to do what's best,
but I worry that once he finds out,
he'll be upset we didn't tell him sooner.
Well, we just can't think about that now.
Izzy?
Huh?
Oh, what did you say?
You were off in another world.
Look at the screen.
Huh?
It's acting rather strangely.
Perhaps you should stop focusing on the
problem and start looking for a solution.
Your friends are in trouble.
Can't you feel it in your bones?
Ah!
And my Digibus has been activated.
Boy, that's productive.
This thing puts the pieces together and
then it takes them apart.
Tentermon to Izzymon, are you reading me?
This is merely scientific
speculation, but I believe I've
stumbled onto something
more than just a simple computer.
And I'm about to abandon my alien theory
as well.
Oh my, it's getting hot in here.
Ow!
I'm burning up!
Do something quickly!
I'm being sad!
What's going on?
Hey!
Oh, ouch!
I can't stand it!
Help!
Hmm.
Is it short-circuiting?
Oh, yeet!
Mercy!
Yay!
I'm dancing like I've never danced before!
I'm disconnecting the power!
Well, I may never figure the mystery out.
Oh, well.
Oh, I don't like computers.
What happened to my Digivice?
Andromon will exact his vengeance!
Oh, yeah?
Just try it, you tin can!
Well, come on!
Could you please stop taunting the
deranged androids?
Oh!
Yeah!
Ground interrupt!
Altitude reading abnormal!
Matt, I'm bored.
Gray is really my least
favorite color, and all
this deconstructionism
is so ten minutes ago.
Why are we still here?
We're still here because we're trying to
figure out what gets built in this factory.
So far it just seems designed to put
things together and then take them apart.
I really, really hope they designed it
with the door!
There's no door!
It's based on perpetual motion.
Nothing ever stops or leaves this place.
Fire!
Hey, everybody!
You'll never guess what I just discovered!
Tensions!
So what's up?
Well, the computer program
operating this factory is
what's producing the
generating power to keep it going.
Even more incredible!
In DigiWorld, basic data and simple
information are a living, viable substance.
It's alive!
Hey, you guys!
Listen up!
I don't like the tone of his voice.
We have got to get out of here now!
What do you mean, Ty?
Capture intruders!
Sensors detect hostility!
Bring intruders into firing range!
Uh, Mr. Whatevermon, are you talking to
us?
Bring missiles to position!
And fire!
Oh, TK!
Look out!
Gabubon!
Digiball to...
Garuruma!
Digiball!
Digiball to...
Challenges Andromon!
Get him, Greymon!
Recycle that hunk of tin!
You puny ones dare to challenge me!
Lightning blade!
He's more powerful than either of our
Digimon!
Maybe because he's all machine.
It's almost like he's Digiball far beyond
the other Digimon.
Is it possible that we could lose?
He's beating them both now!
Looks like there's no hope!
Try re-entering that program that
activated your Digivice!
What for?
I believe that's the key to my
Digivolving!
Yes!
It's gotta work.
If I can just recall the exact sequence...
It is close?
Yeah...
idee... Carter Morse!
We've got the Level and done!
Look at your Digiball You
have to... Kabuterimon.
Bring
missiles to position.
And fire!
Boy, doesn't that Andromon ever run out of
gas?
Huh?
That's it.
Good as power!
Demobilize his right leg and will
interrupt his energy source!
Electro shocker!
He stripped the gear.
That must have hurt.
That's wicked!
That black gear reprogrammed my system
somehow.
I'm normally a non-violent Digimon.
You could have fooled us.
No kidding.
I told you he's a Digimon and not an
Android.
I never meant to hurt anyone.
Don't give it another thought.
Hey, we all make mistakes.
I can't answer your
questions about how this place
came to be or what it's for,
but I can be of some help.
The best way to escape from here is to
follow the underground waterway.
The labyrinth begins just beyond this
point.
Thanks for your help, Andromon.
I hope you find your way
home and no matter what, try to
remember the big guy that
turned out to be not so bad.
There's one thing you can count on.
We'll never forget you, Andromon.
I know I can do this.
Really, I can.
Okay, ready, set...
Okay, that only took four minutes.
Let's get out of here.
Am I the only one who
finds strolling leisurely
through the sewers just
the slightest bit disgusting?
Tell me the truth, Izzy.
Was it your computer that made Tentomon
turn into a superhero?
Prodigious, huh?
Could your computer make Paddlemon become
a superhero?
I suppose that is possible.
Wow, okay!
Let's see now.
What's happening?
That's strange.
Hey!
The program's right.
But nothing is happening.
Just give it a few whacks.
That'll do it.
Let us try.
Sorry guys, but a computer is not a toy.
Now that you boys have holes in your head,
maybe your brains will get enough oxygen.
Ha ha ha!