As we floated there in the middle of the
ocean, we thought we were done for.
That's when, out of
nowhere, Waymon rushed in to
whisk us all off to the
safety of the Briny Deep.
But our battle with the Dark Masters was
far from over.
They sent the Divermon after us,
and soon they were hot on our tail.
We led them on a deep sea chase, but
the pressure was just too much for them.
When we finally came up for air,
we thought we had made it to safety.
But as bad luck would
have it, Metal Seedramon
had followed us, and
he had other ideas.
I'm tired of playing around with you,
War Greymon.
Say goodbye!
River of Power!
So much for your impenetrable chrome
digizoid armor.
Looks to me like it got a little rusty.
Next time you decide
you want to rule the waters,
do everybody a favor and
take a bubble bath instead.
We won!
DigiDestin, please, save this one.
Oh my god!
Waymon!
Where did he go?
Everyone!
It's happening to Metal Seedramon,
too!
They're floating in the sky!
I know where they're going!
Spiral Mountains Peak!
No, that's the real reason for all the
shaking!
Over there!
Huh?
The ocean!
It's, uh... disappearing!
You don't.
..
see that every day!
Tag, I'm it!
Metal Seedramon out!
Puppetmon in!
Spiral Mountains Ocean is almost
completely gone!
But why?
The Digital Ocean is being reconfigured
because we kicked its Dark Master's butt!
Quite interesting, but does this affect
us?
Absolutely!
It changes everything.
If we're gonna get any surfing in,
we better hurry!
Those wimpy Dark Masters are no threat to
Super Joe!
That's the DigiToot I like to hear from
you humans!
Alright!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Wait!
Huh?
We're not through here yet!
Mimi!
What are you doing?
In case you haven't noticed, some of our
friends are gone!
Oh!
Sorry!
That one is to remember Wizardmon!
The one next to it is for Pixiemon!
That one's Chumon!
And this one here is for Waymon!
Mimi, they're not dead!
It's more like they've been downloaded to
a different computer!
That's right!
We're digital!
Our information just gets reconfigured!
What better reason do we need to get the
Dark Masters?
Payback for making our friends leave!
I'm not going!
Huh?
What are you saying?
I have had enough!
Every time we fight we wind up losing
another friend!
This is war, Mimi!
And sometimes people we like get hurt,
so deal with it!
Stop it, Ty!
Enough!
Why don't you stop and think about other
people's feelings for a change?
Huh?
What are you talking about?
We all know you're right, Ty, but just
give us a little space!
Huh?
We miss our friends who fought alongside
of us!
Not everyone has ice running through their
veins like you do!
What?
Calm down!
You're so busy looking forward that you
never take time to look back!
We've lost some good friends here, Ty, and
it's nice to remember them once in a while!
If we always stop to do that, we'll never
have enough time to save the world!
You still don't get it!
I know you hear me, but you're not
listening!
Stop it!
You're making everyone upset!
You two are supposed to be friends!
Don't cry, Mimi!
Where are sitting ducks out here?
Let's find some place a little less out in
the open!
I'm not as cold as Matt thinks,
am I?
Maybe I was a little too rough on Ty,
but he's gotta respect our feelings!
I've never seen Matt so upset before!
This is terrible!
We should be concentrating on fighting our
enemies, not each other!
I just know they're all thinking about me!
That's why no one's talking!
Everyone's so tired and cranky!
You okay?
Walk?
Hmm...
Why'd you stop, Kari?
Did you hear a noise just now?
What kind of noise?
You mean you didn't hear someone speaking
a second ago?
You mean a voice?
No, I didn't hear anything at all.
Weird.
Come on, let's get back to the others.
There's safety in numbers.
Hmm.
Where were you two?
I thought I heard something, but it was
just my imagination.
It's dangerous out here, so stay with the
group.
Okay, I'm sorry.
If these kids take any longer to get here,
I will develop wood rods!
Have patience, Rome wasn't built in a day.
Yeah, but I was, and I'm tired of waiting!
Huh?
What's this?
Why are the trees running so fast?
What is going on?
Things aren't moving faster!
We are!
The ground we're standing on is
accelerating!
This is more fun than the time I was
fumigated for termites!
Wee-hee!
Woo-hoo!
Now where did I put those dogs?
I haven't seen some of these toys since I
was a sapling.
We've got to jump off!
Now this part's moving!
Obviously, someone's trying to get us
somewhere and in a big hurry.
I bet you're right.
And why do I get the feeling that
someone's not too friendly?
No, no!
This is the first time I've been carsick
without a car!
I've got a plan.
This was always good for a few laughs.
Master!
Yes, that's very entertaining, Lord Puppetmon,
but there's no sign of the children.
What?
They were here a second ago!
Where are they?
Not here!
I need our new cable company!
I have a hunch that one of the dark
masters is behind all this.
I'll bet you're right.
We have to do something.
I say we either keep going or fill the
nest.
Well, I say we have to fight whoever it is
sooner or later, so let's get to it!
Oh, come on!
Again with the fighting?
Why don't you just go to a neutral corner
already?
Come on, Matt!
Please stop arguing!
You, keep out of this!
All right, Matt.
Let's try it your way.
We'll stay up here and wait for the enemy
to get us!
That's not what I meant!
Stop it, Matt!
Where'd Ty go?
He disappeared!
Oh, did he fall?
Oh, no!
He vanished into thin air!
Look!
Now Mimi's gone!
Mimi, come back!
Maybe their screensavers are on sleep!
Joe!
Hurry!
Everybody's disappeared but us!
Ah!
What's going on?
Oh!
Huh?
How'd we get over here?
We've been transported.
Whoa!
I hate mud!
Ah, come on!
I think it's over!
But now we're separated from everyone
else!
Don't worry!
We'll be all right without the others,
especially Ty!
Huh?
TK?
Yeah?
Just stick close to me and I'll protect
you no matter what happens!
Listen, Matt.
The only reason we got this far is because
we worked as a team.
Each one of us has played a part along the
way in keeping us together, including Ty!
But I... Uh... Uh... And I don't need
you to protect me all the time either!
If you haven't noticed, I've grown up a
lot!
I've fought alongside you guys since the
beginning and I've always held my own!
TK... That's not what I meant.
What I... What I wanted
to say was... What?
I'm pushing everyone away.
One, two, three!
You're still in the tree!
You know, Kiwi Mom, this isn't as much fun
as I thought it would be.
I should just destroy them all!
Then you won't have anyone left to play
with.
Good boy!
Hey, Joe!
Are you all right?
My stomach!
What's wrong?
Does it hurt?
No!
I'm just doing this because it's fun!
Joe!
I've got a new game I wanna play!
Come here!
Whoa!
You too!
Oh, brother!
And for you... Whoa!
This is like playing chess with the Digi
Destin!
Corey!
No!
Oh!
Whoa!
Fascinating!
Maybe for you... Where am I?
We've reached the turning point!
Impossible!
Whoa!
Welcome back!
Goochie-goochie-curl!
Whoa!
Huh?
I don't know what's so funny, but this is
no laughing method!
Huh?
Matt, you're back!
TK!
You know, I'm getting tired of doing
nothing!
I will be some cat stuck in a tree!
Let's go look for them!
Good idea!
I'll start by looking for TK!
Oh!
This is awful!
You said it!
How could it get any worse?
Look!
I'll tell you how!
The branches are starting to crack!
Wow!
They should learn to fly!
I think I found a new toy to play with!
He looks very easy to scare!
You want me to get him for you?
No!
I'll get this one myself!
Hm!
TK!
Are you alright?
I guess so, but I felt like something was
tickling me and I couldn't stop laughing!
I wonder if there's something wrong with
me?
Are you sure you're not hurt?
Hey!
Stop being so worried about me!
I told you before that I know how to take
care of myself!
Okay!
Huh?
TK!
What do you say?
Stay close!
Time to play!
Sounds like the voice is getting closer!
Keep your hands off my brother,
Puppetmon!
Or I'll chop you into firewood!
Aw, come on!
Be nice!
All I wanted to do was play a little game
of war with TK!
Play?
You mean like pretend?
But of course!
At least in the beginning it will be
make-believe anyway!
But then it's bye-bye!
And it will be time to destroy you for
real!
If I got rid of you now, I'd have no fun!
TK, he's just trying to scare you!
Don't listen to him!
Don't lie to him or your nose will grow!
Ah!
I can't move now!
Are you okay?
Matt!
What?
Now, shall we get going?
Forget it!
I don't want to!
Hmm... Well, if you don't
come with me, it's no fun!
Maybe instead I'll destroy your brother!
What do you say?
Okay, I'll come!
That's a good boy!
TK, it's a trap!
Run away now while you still can!
Shut up!
So, is it a deal?
We'll have lots of fun!
Now you hide and I'll seek and destroy!
That's good!
Keep running!
You make the game interesting!
Hey!
Someone's coming!
Who could it be?
Sounds to me like Lord Puppetmon has found
a new play toy!
Oh, hi there!
Bye!
Wait, I'm hiding back here, so don't say
anything, K!
No problem!
Hey, you guys!
You didn't happen to see a little kid run
back here, did ya?
He's got a green hat and a backpack!
No!
We didn't see anything like that,
boss!
All we saw was a kid wearing a backpack
and a green hat!
He's hiding over there!
Losers!
Come out!
Wherever you are!
Especially if you're behind the door!
Aha!
Hey look!
A house in the middle of the forest!
I wonder if anyone inside has seen TK!
What's
going on around here?
K!
Matt!
TK!
TK was taken prisoner by Puppetmon!
Puppetmon?
Oh no!
We have to help him!
Where'd that creepy little toothpick take
TK?
I don't know!
Get a hold of yourself, Matt!
It shouldn't be that difficult to find
him!
I'm sure that first road we were on leads
directly to Puppetmon!
Then we'll all be trapped!
It's worth it to save TK!
I agree!
Let's go get him!
Who are you?
No one may interfere with Master
Puppetmon's playtime!
You're all staying right here!
Oh no!
It's Kiwimon!
An ancient Digimon that was said to be
extinct!
Although he's a bird-type Digimon, his
wings have degenerated so he can't fly!
Pummel pack!
Have some... Peppa Bread!
Ah!
Final Twister!
Electro Shocker!
Ah!
Hmm... What these dolls are for?
This one looks like Joe!
Joe, what happened?
Why does this stuff always happen to me?
Weird!
What?
I didn't see anyone push you!
Joe's on TV!
Let's see what else is on!
Oh!
Hmm!
Now that's what I call remote control!
Yoo-hoo!
There you are!
I found you!
The game's over!
Oh!
I'm gonna destroy you in a minute!
But first I have to smash my legs!
Hmm... I guess that's what I get
for having a leg made of poison oak!
I can outsmart him!
Hmm... How boring!
I'm not having any fun at all!
What?
I'm the life of the party!
I put the fun in fungus!
Ha!
You just play the same game over and over
again!
Boring!
I've got friends!
Yeah?
Then how come I haven't met these
so-called friends of yours?
All right!
I'll get them and introduce you right now!
TK!
Panamon!
I like to make friends!
Hey!
Where are you keeping TK?
Oh-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho!
Answer me!
I know how you feel, Matt, but first we
have to defeat Kiwimon!
How can you understand how I feel?
I understand that if we don't beat him
first, we won't be able to fight TK!
No!
First we find TK, then we'll fight your
war!
Right, Matt!
Kabumon!
Warp digivolve to... Huh?
It won't glow!
What's going on here, Matt?
How come I can't digivolve?
Pummel pet!
There!
Done!
I said I like to make friends and I've
made one!
Huh?
TK?
Why?
It's Lord Puppetmon's new toy!
Where's he going?
We're gonna place your rights!
Maybe he doesn't know how to play!
Yeah, that's it!
TK!
Thanks a lot!
You're welcome!
Be-o-mon!
Be-o-mon, what did you do?
Look what your Digimon did!
Without Kiwimon, we'll never find TK!
Calm down, Matt!
Hey!
It's TK!
Hey, everybody!
Hi!
I'm back!
TK!
See, everybody?
I told you I could do it!
I can take care of myself just fine!
You're the man!
Nice going, TK!
Great job, buddy!
We were worried about you!
Boy, for a little kid, that was a pretty
big escape!
Stop it, guys!
You're embarrassing me!
What's wrong, Matt?
Huh?
I also smashed the remote control that was
making the ground move underneath us!
That's terrific, TK!
Rodigious!
Everything's gonna be alright now!
Puppa Mom was using these dolls to control
us!
That's why all those weird things were
happening!
Is this me?
I don't look anything like this!
Huh!
Wow, Mimi, your doll is really pretty!
What?
No way!
I would never wear rags like this!
Oh!
I could take her to the mall for some new
clothes!
So he didn't want to play with me,
huh?
TK, you'll pay for this!
Can anybody see where Matt went?
He's right over there!
Huh?
I don't get it!
He and Gobble Mom were there a second ago!
They vanished!
Here we go again!
Will Puppet Mom take revenge on TK?
Is he behind Matt's disappearance?
Find out on the next Digimon Digital
Monsters!