So there we were, falling like crazy.
That's when Gomamon
tells all the fish in the river
to swim close together
and make a boat for us.
Later, we find a beach with a whole bunch
of these foam booths.
We tried calling home, but none of them
seemed to work.
Next, we got totally thrashed on by
Shellmon.
He sprayed seawater like a fire hose.
My butt, Agumon, got stepped on,
and that made him mad.
We digivolved into Greymon and gave
Shellmon a ride he won't forget.
Then he turned back into Agumon.
Dudes, this place is wild!
Digimon, digital monsters, Digimon are the
champions!
Change into digital champions to save the
digital world!
Digimon, digital monsters, Digimon are the
champions!
Digimon!
Digital monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Digimon!
Digital monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Digimon!
We've almost searched the whole island and
we still haven't found any people.
Just some monsters with attitude.
But they couldn't beat our Digimon friends
who can turn into these awesome fighters.
Like when Agumon Digivolved into Greymon
and kicked Shellmon to the curb.
He was so cool!
Yo, Agumon!
What's up, Ty?
I like it when you're Greymon.
No offense, but why don't you just stay
that way?
I can't.
But even superheroes need a rest.
Who's that Digimon?
It's a monochromon, but don't worry about
him.
He's a laid-back Digimon.
Although it is wise to be a bit
cautious with the monochromon,
they do tend to get a bit
miffed when they're hungry.
Then he must be starving, because he looks
really mad!
And I think he wants to eat us!
There are two of them!
We're caught between a rock and two sets
of teeth!
Something must have set those monochromon
off!
They're fighting over territory!
They can just have it then!
Hey!
Don't leave without me!
They definitely don't need us hanging
around!
I
don't walk this much unless I'm at a mall!
And as you can see, we're nowhere near
one!
Mimi, stop whining!
No!
My feet hurt!
Maybe if you'd take off your boots and
socks, you'd feel better, Mimi.
It's much more practical, I think.
I'm not walking and dirty my bare feet!
I love the feel of dirt under my feet,
especially between my toes!
Gross!
It appears that we may be losing our light
source.
What a weird sunset.
This whole island is weird, and who knows
what will come out at night!
Wait!
I detect water!
Stay here while I check it out!
Yes!
As usual, I'm right!
It's a lake with fresh, clean water and a
variety of tasty fish!
It's a perfect campsite!
Maybe I can finally soak my poor achy
feet!
Yay!
We get to swim!
Go, Maman!
You better wait and make sure it's safe
first!
That's why I think we should keep walking
and stop all the complaining!
Everybody's hungry!
We have to find some food!
That is a good plan!
I like that plan a lot!
It should be safe to rest here tonight!
Yeah, I love camping outside!
If I won't walk in dirt, what makes you
think I'll sleep in it?
Mimi, do you see a hotel here?
Whoa!
What's that?
It looks like a trolley car!
That's odd!
The lights just... came on!
Well, maybe there are some real people in
there!
Let's check it out!
Maybe they can take us back home!
In air-conditioned comfort!
Mimi, wait up!
Bummer, it's empty!
Totally empty!
No trolley cars this clean!
Oh, goody!
These cushions are comfy!
Something's wrong!
Remember those weird phone booths we saw
on the beach?
Something just as freaky could happen
here!
Yeah, like this suddenly moving all by
itself!
Possibly, but then again, maybe that's how
we're going to get home!
So we have nothing to lose by staying
here!
Oh, can we eat now?
That's right.
I forgot.
Go, Momon!
Stop playing in the water!
I can't catch any fish if you keep on
warning them away!
Yum, yum!
You can't get too many berries down the
hatch!
Oh!
Oh boy, you better watch that killer
breath of yours, Pot-Omon!
Those are bad mushrooms!
You shouldn't pick them!
They'll make you sick!
Oh!
I'd be a big mess without you,
Palmon!
You're the best!
Hasta!
We're all set to cook dinner!
Now all we need is the grub!
Great, but how are we supposed to light
the fire?
Like this!
Wow, Agumon!
You're the man!
Aww!
Hey, look it!
We caught a bunch of fish!
Awesome, Izzy!
Let's eat them!
Thanks, Squirt!
This is where I wish we had a microwave!
Huh?
Me too!
Because you're about to lose your fingers!
Why don't you use a stick?
How did you come up with that,
Matt?
Because I'm the man!
This is surprisingly good!
Mmm!
Delicious!
Matt, Mom only lets me eat fish sticks!
I won't tell!
I'll never eat with my fingers!
TK, it's alright!
Yeah, you're hanging with the big boys
now!
Kay!
Hey, Sora!
What?
Matt doesn't treat TK like a brother,
only like he's a bother!
Is it just me, or have you noticed that
too?
Yeah.
I wonder... Matt's still
learning to be a big brother!
Maybe.
Hmm... Hey, Joe!
Whatcha looking at?
I'm trying to figure out
which direction we've
been going, but the stars
seem to be all mixed up!
I haven't been able to find the North Star
anywhere!
I know!
I don't recognize any of these
constellations!
You're forgetting your astronomy!
If you can't see the North Star, then it
must be on the other side of the world!
Do you think we could be in the Southern
Hemisphere?
Yes, I guess it's possible!
That is, if we're still on Earth!
What is that supposed to mean?
Look!
Panamon's tired!
I'm getting really tired myself!
Wait a second!
I think we should take turns standing
guard!
Alright!
Who wants to go first?
How about if each of us stands guard for
about an hour?
Not TK!
Aw, come on!
Me too, Matt!
No!
You're too young and you need your rest!
I'm getting cold!
I need a warm blanket to help me sleep!
Hey, Gabumon!
Watch it!
Mimi may sneak up on you and steal your
fur, so if you feel a little tugged,
it might be her about to cut your tail
off!
Stop talking!
That's not funny!
Quit it!
What are you bugging about?
Gabumon told you to stop!
So knock it off!
Hey, you can't tell me what to do!
You guys stop fighting!
You'd both make great guards!
Who goes first?
I will!
I'm next!
How about if Izzy takes over after that
and then I finish up the night?
I propose that the rest of us trek back to
the bus and get some shut-eye!
I can't sleep with all of you here!
Quit complaining!
So it's not perfect!
Just be glad we have a place to sleep!
That's right, Mimi!
Good night!
Don't let the monochrome on bite!
Thanks for reminding me, TK!
My feet still hurt!
Why is there a trolley here?
Maybe it's the aliens!
Maybe they knew we needed it!
I hope I don't get any monster cooties!
Gabumon?
Yeah?
Go over and lay down with my brother!
Why, Matt?
Because your fur's making me sweat!
Now go!
Because you want me to keep TK warm!
Hey, I didn't say that!
You just don't want to admit it!
Whatever!
Thanks, Matt!
Ty, you don't want to fall asleep on your
first night watch!
My eyes won't stay open!
I'm going to the lake and splash some
water on my face!
Huh?
Who's there?
Oh, Matt!
Don't you think I can handle this?
I couldn't sleep!
Oh!
And why not?
Look, I'm sorry about earlier!
I didn't mean to get so mad, it's just
being here and having to watch TK!
Do you guys even live in the same house?
Not anymore!
We're half-brothers and we don't get to
see each other much!
Well, that explains a lot!
Matt...
Oh!
Huh?
Matt's a little strange.
What a wonderful sound!
Maybe to a St. Bernard with a horn on his
forehead.
Hmm...
Huh?
Oh!
Watch out for the fire sparks!
What's that horrible sound?
It's an earthquake!
The trolley's starting to move and I don't
think it's taking us home!
It's taking us toward that sea dragon!
Oh no!
Sea Drummond!
We're gonna get eaten for sure!
The land's moving!
Hold tight!
We're going for a ride!
It's like we're on a monster longboard!
He's pulling us along by his tail!
I don't even think he realizes we're here!
Perhaps not!
He's a bit dense!
As long as he doesn't see us, we should be
safe!
Don't be too sure!
You guys jinxed us!
Now he knows we're here!
What?
I didn't do anything!
Whoa!
Guess he does know we're here!
The
red thing was his tail!
It wasn't my fault!
He's coming back and he's not happy!
Here!
T.K!
Matt, I'm just letting you know my fur's
gonna get wet and I'm gonna stink!
Great!
He left us right in the middle of the
lake!
I don't suppose we could trick him into
taking us back!
Get ready!
He's attacking!
Come on, you guys!
Let's send him back to the fishies!
No problem!
Viral Twister!
Ah!
Pleasimany!
Super Shocker!
Peppa Breath!
Agumon!
Digivolve!
I've been trying, but I can't seem to do
it this time!
Ty?
You have to!
Maybe my body hasn't recovered from the
last fight!
But if you can't help us, how are we gonna
stop Seedramon?
Take him!
Over here!
Matt!
Be careful!
Go, Momon!
Go!
Hurry up, Matt!
Get out fast!
It's Seedramon!
He's back!
Go, Momon!
You can do it!
Right!
Hey!
New blaster!
Ha!
It's all my fault!
Matt was only trying to save me!
I'll never forgive myself!
No!
Oh, no!
This is not good!
Seedramon may be a bubble brain, but
once he finds his prey, he won't let go!
Matt!
Hang on!
Seedramon's way too big!
I just don't have enough power now!
Gobblemon, you're stronger!
How about you?
You're right!
Matt is in trouble, and I must help!
Gobblemon!
Hey!
Don't give up!
I'll find a way to save you,
but the last thing I do... Matt!
Matt!
Hold on!
I don't understand any of this,
but I have to save Matt!
What's a little stinky fur compared to a
friend like him?
Gobblemon!
Ah!
Digiball 2!
Gobblemon!
Yeah, but where's Gobblemon?
Shhh!
Garurumon's fur is legendary!
It's strong as steel!
He's like a growling torpedo!
That's astonishing!
Mini must be invincible!
Well, that's what I've heard anyway!
We'll soon find out!
I hope you're not
exaggerating, Tento-mon,
with another one of
your wild fish tails again!
He could be!
But I heard about it!
Roar!
Flying's sure a good way to keep my fur
dry!
You digivolved into Garurumon just in
time!
Oh, Gobblemon, thanks for saving my
brother!
Any time, little friend!
Matt, you were so awesome against that
monster!
You think so?
You know, you were the man!
And you're the wolf man!
Okay, very funny, but how are we supposed
to get back?
Just watch!
Gobblemon,
may I use your fur pillow?
I promise, I won't take your fur!
Actually, there seems to be a pattern
here.
This time, only Gobblemon could digivolve.
Yeah, Izzy's right!
Gobblemon was the only one who could do it
before!
Hmm...
Hang on!
I can't breathe!
Greymon!
Get me out of here!
You're right, it's all beginning to make
sense!
Agumon digivolved when I was in danger!
That has to be the answer!
Our Digimon digivolves when we're in
trouble!
Wow, that must be it!
Hey, watch it!
Is it time to go to the mall?
We've been here one day and I think she's
put some muscle on her.
Yeah, maybe if she
puts in some effort,
she'll become a hard-bodied
machine like I am!
I hope she grows pink wings just like my
wings!
You must be kidding!
Oh!
Oh, big bro!
Oh, you're the best.