Joe and I were tired of all the fighting,
so we decided to sit one out.
We saw what looked like a giant meatball
fall out of the sky.
Turns out it was Edemon, except he was a
lot shinier.
He was now Metal Edemon, and he was
looking for revenge.
The other kids were able to get inside of
Puppetmon's mansion, and with the help of
some of his unhappy guards, used some of
his toys against him.
Joe and I found Ogremon, who'd been
wounded.
When we fixed him up, he couldn't believe
we were being so nice to him.
Things seemed fairly quiet for a change.
Of course, quiet never lasts long here.
Next time we have a hit.
Hey, don't you come any closer.
Wait, I won't hurt you.
Do we believe you?
It sounds familiar.
Wait, I don't trust him.
Don't give me any of your job,
baby.
Come out, come out, wherever you are.
I'll explain everything later.
Right now we need to get out of here.
Hey, wait up.
Don't leave me here with this whacked out
monkey.
Supreme, I'm fired up and ready to go on a
mean streak.
Slow down, you four-footed giant furball.
This is certainly more convenient than
waiting for a taxi.
If I'd known we were gonna go riding,
I'd have worn long pants.
Me too, I need a side saddle.
This place doesn't look very lively.
It's kind of spooky.
Look up there.
I think I'm gonna barf.
That's the restaurant where they made me
work like a slave.
I'm still trying to get that greasy spoon
smell out of my sweater.
But this is all wrong.
It's supposed to be near a lake.
Everything's changed.
Hurry, we'd better find shelter.
This place is depressing.
There's not even a clean chair to sit on.
Awesome!
Leomon, you are not gonna believe what you
missed.
I can't believe it's you!
I am truly happy to have finally returned
and helped my friends.
You digivolved!
A lot has happened
to me since being set
free of the Black Gears
and their evil power.
Being exposed to the digivice has now
enabled me to digivolve.
But there is one problem.
Huh?
I am unable to control it.
I haven't learned the secret yet.
It's all still new to me.
What makes you special, you oversized
doggy chew toy?
Let's just see how many lives you have
left.
Huh?
Dirty cat!
There is nothing more pathetic than a
whiner.
Clearly you don't deserve to be called a
Digimon.
Puppetmon!
Huh?
Who's in there?
Show yourself!
Please don't switch us!
We're friends!
The last thing we want to do is cause
trouble!
Oh, Palmon, look!
They delivered the triple hot fudge
sundae!
Princess Katie!
Yippee!
Oh,
no!
Well, we are shooting at him!
I bet they don't invite Puppetmon to their
birthday parties.
I think it's a good thing that they're
finally releasing their hostility.
Get out now!
Friends, I hate killing my toys!
I'd say that you need to learn a little
more about good manners.
We're not hurting anything except maybe
you.
We've had it with you, Puppetmon!
You're toast!
So now you want to play, huh?
How about a game of...
Come back here, you puny toothpick!
You play with us and you're gonna lose!
It's a trick!
My best move.
Well, Puppetmon, CGK, I have friends here.
And what they don't like, they destroy.
Kill us!
Red Vegemon have extremely volatile
tempers.
That's why their faces are always red.
Not exactly the friendly type.
It's time to do some weed whacking!
How come you two were hiding?
What happened to your palace?
The palace was completely destroyed by
those creepy Dark Masters!
Yeah, it was horrible!
They attacked just for the fun of it!
We all had to run for our lives!
We were all separated and we've been
hiding here ever since!
How awful!
Those guys make me sick.
Who do they think they are anyway,
picking on poor defenseless Digimon?
I mean, is that fair?
The Dark Masters have to be stopped if we
expect to survive.
I've spent all this time searching for
you, but it hasn't been easy.
The Dark Masters have seen to that.
You two have the power to
defeat those beasts, but you must
work together and join forces
with the other Digi-destined.
Only then will you succeed.
Are you saying we wasted our time fighting
everyone else?
I mean, I could have stained my clothes
with perspiration.
Listen, girlie.
If you would have fought
those guys at the start,
you would have broken
way more than just a sweat.
Maybe.
But what about the good Digimon on File
Island that sacrificed themselves to help us?
Oh!
Mimi.
This is true.
What do you mean?
I think you were brought
to File Island to prove
that you were capable
of working as a team.
It could have been a test to make sure
that you were the Digi-destined.
Did we pass?
You did.
It actually makes sense.
If Devimon had defeated you, then you would
not be ready for this bigger challenge.
Devimon's power was nothing compared to
the Dark Masters.
He was merely the beginning.
But you've proven
yourselves over and over
by defeating one evil
Digimon after another.
You're ready to take on the Dark Masters.
Come on.
We must find your friends immediately.
So tell me, where did they go?
We can't do this all alone.
Some of us needed a time out from each
other.
You know how it is.
You needed a time out?
Yeah, you might say it's another kind of
test.
Electro-shocker!
Meteor away!
And a bank out!
Useful as a load of stinky rotten
vegetables!
Try to stop us now!
Pokemon Wolf Digimon!
Turn!
Digimon!
They truly are the champions!
Oh, he's got me strung up!
lesson!
Mu urgent раза We're great, mom!
Don't get close!
I don't know what he'll make me do!
Mu ah
Feet ofرفalack K lightly Digimon Digimon
Digimon Digimon Germanfun
I'm not afraid of you.
I'll get you.
If I were you, I'd reconsider.
Huh?
Wait, we must be careful.
The Digi-Destined are strong.
Stronger than I suspected.
Don't underestimate them, Puppet Mono.
It could be disastrous.
What?
Spit it out already.
Are you saying that I might lose?
I'm only saying, take them seriously.
The Digi-Destined have something you
don't.
Hmm, what does he mean by that?
I got more powers than I ever will.
Fools, I'm never gonna lose to you.
Watch!
I know something you don't.
It's showtime, baby.
It's Metal Etymon.
He never quit.
Huh?
You trying to pull a number on me,
bro?
Well, I'm gonna lay it on the line,
cause I'm so fine.
Deal with me.
Then we shall see who's fine.
Leomon Digi-Vault II!
Saber Leomon!
Whoa!
Well, I see we've been
taking our vitamins, but
it's time to put the cat
out with the garbage.
Saber Leomon may have
a heart of gold, but he'll
crush his opponents
with his claws of steel.
Don't do it!
I'll be all right.
Now run before it's too late.
Howling Crusher!
We're in a slam!
I'm not gonna sit here and watch this.
Hey guys, wait for me!
Digimon!
Dom-a-Mod!
To...
Income-a-Mod!
Digimon!
Mimi!
They need me!
What should I do?
Mimi?
Harpoon Torpedo!
Wait!
What do you mean, wait?
We've gotta help him out!
But don't you think it's a better idea to
leave like he told us to?
Bajow!
Twin Fang!
I really think we'd better leave before
it's too late!
What about Leomon?
You call that your best shot?
Metal Punch!
Ha!
He's nothing!
If you want a real challenge, it's right
here!
What?
Ogremon, don't be ridiculous!
You're no match for him!
Hey listen, I can take on this 10-can if I
want to!
No!
Mimi!
You're in no shape to fight!
Now stop it!
And quit trying to be a hero!
Huh?
No, everyone's welcome!
As a matter of fact, little darlin', today
I'm offering a special group discount!
Besides it saves me time to destroy all
you at once...
Aaaaaaah!
Mimi, no!
Whaaaaaaah!
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!
Okay, that does it!
Digimon!
GAMBIU!
Erikakumon!
Digimon!
Oh, tell me!
Please
tell me you're all right!
Vulcan's Hammer!
As you can see, that didn't even faze me.
My metal's Chromadigizoid, the absolute
strongest metal there is!
Then maybe you'd like this!
Vulcan's Hammer!
No matter what you attempt, it's useless.
Cause I'm invincible!
I'm breaking apart!
This is terrible!
I lost my luster!
Why does this keep happening to me?
Because my hammer is made of
Chromadigizoid metal!
I'm afraid it isn't your moment to shine!
That can't be!
Twin Fang!
Uh-oh!
You'll pay me down!
He did it!
Get them!
Do some major damage and I want no
fall-ups!
What's with you?
Daydreaming again, huh?
No metal gururu mom!
Sock it to him!
Hey, this isn't working here!
Remember, you're supposed to obey me!
I'm the boy!
Think again!
You're washed up, Puppet Mom!
Nobody's gonna be on your side because you
don't care about them!
I'm still strong!
And it doesn't matter what they think!
They're still gonna do what I tell them to
do!
Ah!
No muscle!
Cherrymon, what is it that those
kids have that I don't... Friends!
Thank you, Matt!
Huh?
Unmon's been defeated!
The forest is disappearing!
Run!
We've gotta get out of here and find a
safe place!
Leumon, it's me!
Come on now!
Yeah, wake up!
This stupid toilet paper isn't gonna be
any good this time!
Ah!
The forest... the forest is disappearing!
It's a sign that something positive has
happened.
Your friends must have defeated Puppet
Mom.
That's good.
I expected that they would.
Oh, Leumon, please don't leave us!
We depend on you!
You have no reason to worry.
I must go now and rejuvenate myself at the
primary village.
But...
Ogrimon, I'm very sorry.
Now is not the time for us to resolve
things.
But I promise we will meet up again.
You're a good rival.
Mimi, let's go to the primary village.
Yes, we need help and if what Leumon said
is true, we'll meet some old friends there.
Wouldn't it be just great to see Chumon
and Pixiemon again?
Well then the matter's settled.
We're making a trip to find the primary
village.
Alright?
There's only one problem.
It doesn't exist.
Huh?
There isn't anything there.
It's a ghost town.
It was destroyed after the Dark Masters
poisoned it with their evil.
No one is left.
It can't be!
It will never return to the way it was
until the Dark Masters are eliminated.
Any ideas?
I say we throw them out and then save the
village.
That would be great and it's better than
sitting around and doing nothing.
Okay Mimi.
The only way out of this mess is to defeat
the Dark Masters.
Are you up for it?
We need your help Mimi.
Please say yes.
For Leumon and everyone, the whole Digi
World needs us.
Yes, you're right Palmon.
Sniveling is for babies and I've done too
much of that already.
Ogremon, are you going to come along with
us?
Hmm?
Huh?
Well, I have no intention of joining
forces with you crazy kids.
However, if we all happen to be going the
same way, I'm stuck tagging along.
Don't worry, Ogremon.
We won't blow your cover.
Now that it's decided, we need to seek out
a few allies.
Allies?
Where?
There must be others
who are willing to fight
the Dark Masters and
get their hands dirty.
I know they're out there.
We just have to find them, that's all.
Yeah.
Hey, Princess, how about if we come along
to help out?
No way.
Huh?
Come on!
Only if you stop calling me Princess and
call me Mimi instead.
Our pleasure, Mimi.
So can we come now?
Of course you can.
Some call this a crossroads in life.
In the past, I might have avoided it by
going to the mall.
But you know, it feels good to do the
right thing.
Even though at times that might be a
dangerous thing.
Which we may soon find out.
The DigiDestined are gathering allies.
But separated, will they be able to survive
the combined attack of the Dark Masters?
Tune in to the next Digimon Digital
Monsters.