Ty left me to watch his sister Kari while
he was off playing the hero.
Izzy, with some help from
Gen-I, snuck into the TV
station to try and sabotage
Myotismon's fog barrier.
Joe and TK were still trying to get home,
but Megasidromon was guarding the harbor.
Ikakumon digivolted Zudomon and saved Joe
at the last minute.
All the while, the kid and I were just
sitting on our hands.
Phantomon showed up and things got very
intense.
Kari told the creep that
she was the eighth child
and that she'd go with
him if he'd leave us alone.
How am I gonna explain this to Ty?
Two digital champions.
I'm gonna jump in.
Kari, don't!
You don't know what you're doing!
You can't give yourself up to Myotismon!
He'll destroy you and gain control of both
worlds!
It's not your fault.
Yes, it is.
I blew it.
Ty asked me to protect her and I couldn't.
I let everyone down.
Alright, Matt.
It seems to me there are two things you
can do about this.
Number one, you can stand there and beat
yourself up about the whole thing.
Or number two, we can find a way to rescue
Kari.
What's it gonna be?
You're right.
Let's get her.
Hurry, Agumon!
The convention center is up ahead!
That's where my parents are being held
prisoner!
And keep an eye out for Myotismon!
Huh?
What's that?
Well, Gatoman, is this the eighth child?
Uh-uh.
Myotismon!
What is it?
You'll love this, boss.
I found the eighth-digit destined!
You did?
Huh?
What?
How did he do it?
Oh, no.
Not Kari.
You hear that?
It's over!
Well, I have no use for these little brats
anymore.
Right.
What should I do with them, oh evil one?
Make them go to sleep.
I'll find a way to deal with them later.
Myotismon, where could he be going?
They didn't stand a ghost of a chance.
Ty, you made it inside!
Mimi, where are the others?
They're all fast asleep.
Myotismon put them under some kind of
spell since he found the eighth child.
Oh, no.
That means he's got Kari.
Huh?
Kari?
Let's go!
Hey, look!
There's Matt and Sora!
What?
Matt?
What's he doing here?
Ah!
Monsters!
Actually, sir, the technical name is
Digimon.
You see, they're not like the
pretend monsters you've seen
in those old movies destroying
a bunch of Japanese cities.
Hey, well, maybe that's a bad example.
But anyway, the Digimon Matt's riding on
is definitely on our side.
What do you mean, our side?
Well, you see, there are good Digimon and
bad Digimon.
The good Digimon are our friends,
just like Tentamon here.
I'm more than good.
I'm exceptional.
I wouldn't dare doubt you.
But Joe, why does Wizardmon have a tag and
a crest?
Hmm.
He said it belonged to the eighth
Digi-destined.
You think it could be true?
Hmm?
Are you awake?
Huh?
Who are you?
I'm TK.
Nice to meet you.
Kari.
Huh?
Where's Kari?
Kari?
Who's Kari?
You've got to give this crest to Kari.
Whoa.
You mean you want us to give that to Ty's
little sister, Kari?
Whoa.
But if we have to deliver the crest to
Ty's sister, Kari, then that must mean...
She's the eighth Digi-destined child we've
been looking for all along.
Gee, I'm always the last one to find out.
We have no time to waste.
Kari and Gatomon need this crest.
Gatomon?
But she's one of the bad Digimon that
works for Myotismon.
Are you saying that Gatomon is one of the
good guys?
Exactly.
Huh?
Matt!
Sara!
Hey, you guys!
Hey!
Izzy, what are you doing here?
Oh, Matt!
Dad!
I told you to stay out of sight.
I'm sorry, Dad.
Oh, Matt's Dad.
Good to see you again.
What do you mean again?
Who are you?
Have we met?
You know me.
I Digivolve from Gabumon.
Gabumon?
That's you?
Hey!
Joe!
TK!
Hey, Matt!
Daddy!
TK!
Dad!
What are you doing here?
When I saw all that stuff on television,
I just couldn't stay home anymore.
Mom wanted to come too, but we couldn't
bring her.
It's okay, son.
I missed you, Daddy.
It's Wizardmon!
What are you doing here?
Hmm.
She was attacked by Myotismon,
wasn't she?
So what if she was?
What's this?
Wizardmon?
Hiya!
Stop!
Don't attack him!
Wizardmon's a good Digimon.
He's got the tag and crest.
TK, he could be lying.
No, Sora.
It's all true.
Just look!
Huh?
This tag and crest belong to Kari.
We've gotta help Gatomon.
She was captured by Myotismon.
Gatomon?
Yeah.
Wizardmon said Gatomon belongs with Kari.
What?
Now, where is Kari?
Well?
He's got her.
Chennai sent me some email a little while
ago.
If I recall correctly,
he said the TV station
is the center of
Myotismon's fog barrier.
Hey!
Look!
It's Myotismon!
He's got Gatomon.
But not for long.
Come on!
Let's head for the viewing platform!
Right!
I'll show you the way!
away.
Leave this battle to us.
We could handle these Digiclowns.
We'll get Kari.
Come on, everyone, let's go!
Hey, Wizardmon, are you all right?
Hey, let me give you a hand.
Here.
I've got you, my pretty.
And your little cat, too.
Grimont, hurry!
They need your help!
You got it!
Little girl, why have you chosen to show
yourself to me?
Do you have any idea what's about to
happen to you?
I've got a guess.
Then why?
Because you were hurting all those people.
Huh?
Someone had to stop you from hurting
innocent people!
My, what a thoughtful little girl you are.
Gatuma, why won't you look at the eighth
child's face?
Because she's now the eighth child.
Who is she?
I've never seen her before in my life.
Huh?
Is that right?
Help!
Kari!
Kari, interesting that you know her name
since you've never met her before.
Hurry!
It's up here!
Got it, Dad!
Wait here!
Thanks for the help.
Are you sure you're all right?
Yeah, Digimon, he'll fast!
Kari!
Together again!
Hmm...
Too bad it'll be short-lived!
Thank you!
Grizzly!
Wing!
Tentermon!
Digivolve to...
Kabuterimon!
Electroshocker!
Flower!
Cannon!
It's getting a little noisy in here.
Let's find some place quieter.
Not so fast!
We're Garurumon!
Digimon!
Garurumon!
We need you!
Get Kari!
Garurumon!
Oh, that's got to hurt.
What?
Kari, here!
Catch!
Oh!
It's Wizardmon!
So you're still alive?
That's right!
It'll take more than the likes of you to
destroy me!
We will see!
No!
Wizardmon!
Now give that to me, you little brat!
No!
That wasn't a request!
Wait!
Huh?
Mimi!
You just picked on the wrong guy's little
sister, Mr. Fang Face!
Kari, here!
Catch!
Hiya!
I got the Digivites!
You can thank me after you take over the
world, boss!
That's nice work!
Go get them, Phantoman!
Digimon!
Digimon
are the jungles!
Digimon are the jungles!
Great!
Time out!
Go get them, MetalGreymon!
Digablaster!
But how?
Hornbusters!
Vulcan's cover!
Wing blade!
He's strong!
Too strong!
Are you done?
I'm done!
I'm bored!
It's time to finish you off!
Hmm!
Nightmare!
Digimon!
Unjumun!
Panda fake!
Have you
had enough, or do you want some more?
Actually, I was about to ask you the same
question!
Grizzly Wii!
Kari!
Next time, don't get in my way!
Oh no!
Wizardmon!
You're gonna be alright!
Please don't leave!
Wizardmon!
Are you alright, Gatoman?
You saved me.
I'm sorry.
About what?
Sorry I got you involved in this.
Don't be sorry.
I don't have any regrets.
If I had met you, my life would have had
no meaning.
I'm glad that you and I were friends.
That's forever.
Thank you for everything, Gatoman.
Wizardmon, are you okay?
Please answer.
Look, it's Kari's piggy rise!
I can't hold on!
Kari, here!
Not her, no!
Digimon!
Digimon, you've tried to destroy the
DigiDestined and attempted to conquer Earth.
In doing so, you have ruined the lives of
Digimon and humans alike.
How can you justify yourself?
I don't have to explain myself to the
likes of you.
It is my destiny to
plunge this world into
darkness and become
king of the digital world.
And no angel or Digimon has the power to
stop me.
My Otismon, don't you have any regrets for
the things you have done?
Huh.
Nightmare!
Heaven's Charge!
My power!
It's... it's brewing!
No!
Everyone, give your power to Archimumon!
Hornbusters!
Wing!
Giga Blaster!
Boys and girls!
Hey, Digimon!
Celestial Arrow!
My Otismon is gone!
Kari!
Hi, Digimon!
We
finally destroyed my Otismon!
That wasn't so tough after all!
Great!
Yeah!
Hopefully, now the real world will return
to normal.
Hey, you two!
What's wrong?
Huh?
Look up there!
What is it?
The fog!
It's getting thicker!
Impossible!
Huh?
But... My Otismon is gone!
Maybe not.
Maybe he's still out there somewhere.
What if we just made him stronger?
Is my Otismon truly gone?
Or has he digivolved to a more powerful
form?
Find out on the next Digimon Digital
Monsters!