After reaching the continent
of Server, we found a
Koromon village, but it was
occupied by the Pogomon.
Later, during dinner, Poyomon digivolved
to Tokomon.
That night, little Toko was taken from our
campsite.
Agumon finally found him and all the
Koromon in a cave.
They were being guarded by the Gazimon,
who were also planning on giving us to
their leader, that rock and roll digi-jerk
Edimon.
He used his music like a weapon and tried
to destroy the village.
We found the crest for Tai's tag,
and it created an escape for us.
Never a dull moment.
Digimon, digital
monsters, Digimon are the champions!
Digimon, digital monsters, Digimon are the
champions!
Until Edimon can't follow us anymore.
I don't think there is such a place!
We certainly can't stop here in the middle
of nowhere.
For one thing, if we were attacked,
there'd be no place for us to run to.
This is starting to look bad.
Everyone's becoming so timid and afraid.
Hey, come on, you guys.
Why'd we stop?
Why is everyone so scared?
After all, we do have the crest,
you know?
That's true, but do we really know the
crest will help Agumon to digivolve?
Of course.
Right, Agumon?
Hmm?
Listen, buddy, this is your big chance.
Don't let me down.
You're the only one that can digivolve
further, so either you try to get to the
next level and save us from Edamon,
or I'll go and get myself a new Digimon.
Not much of a choice.
Arrgh!
By the way, how are we supposed to use the
crest to digivolve again?
Well, from what we've
seen so far with the
other digivolutions, it
takes a lot of energy.
For example, they can't digivolve if
they're hungry.
In addition, the partner of the Digimon
must be in some sort of danger.
You know, like being under attack or
something.
But since it's a higher
level of digivolving,
my theory is even
more energy is needed.
So we'll provide the food, Edamon will
provide the danger.
You better watch out, you digidescent
kids.
I'll find you.
And when I do, you'll wish you'll never
cross, Edamon.
I'll get you.
Hey, no more.
Just one more teensy bite.
Ready for the second course?
Oh, stop your belly aching and open wide.
You've got to keep on eating.
Listen, everyone's giving you their food
so that you can digivolve.
Isn't that right?
Yeah.
We didn't give him our food.
He took it from us.
Of all the nerve.
Well, the food won't do us any good.
We still can't digivolve.
So those of us who don't work don't eat,
huh?
But I'm hungry.
Hey, I can't hear you.
I said, is that right?
That's right.
See, that's why you've got to try your
best to protect everybody.
Now, come on, buddy.
Keep eating.
I guess there's not much else we can do to
help.
I don't know if Agumon can take much more.
Yeah, Tai is really pushing him.
Agumon's stuffed like a Thanksgiving
turkey.
Eat up.
You need that energy.
Tai's personality has taken a turn for the
worse lately.
I remember him being friendlier even to us
younger kids.
Actually, now that you mention it,
he was cool during soccer camp.
Tai, pass it to me.
I'm open.
Now's my chance to shoot.
Here I go.
Nice pass, Tai.
I thought you were going to take the shot
yourself.
Remember, there's no I in team.
Tai might look like he's trying to run
things all by himself, but whatever crazy
action he takes, he does it for the good
of the team.
Uh-huh.
But now all this...
We're the only ones who can help now.
So you've got to keep eating, okay,
Agumon?
I can't.
Tai's personality seems
to have changed ever
since he got a hold of
that crest of courage.
Boy, I'm hungry.
Hmm?
Hey, guys.
My tag is blowing.
It must be reacting to something.
The crest must be nearby.
You think so?
Hey, look!
There's something out there.
It looks like a big building or something.
That must be where my crest is.
Whoa!
What's a cable doing out in the middle of
nowhere?
Whoa!
What is it, Lord Edelon?
Ha-ha-ha!
Something's caught in my network.
Ha-ha-ha.
The intruders in the L7 sector.
Let's see.
L7, L7.
How's this thing work?
Oh, here it is.
Where is it?
Ha-ha-ha!
It's near the Coliseum.
That's where I hold my annual Tribute to
Me show.
I wonder what they're doing all the way
over there.
You got any idea?
Well, maybe they want to get good seats,
boss.
Oh, we'll have a perfect view for the
surprise show I've planted for them.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Hello, Area L7.
Can I help you?
It's Edelon.
Yes, sir.
Hey, little bunny.
You should be having some guests soon.
You better get ready to welcome them.
Welcome them?
So do you mean...
Bingo, bunny.
As you wish, sir.
Amazing.
It looks like the Roman Coliseum.
What's the Roman Coliseum?
Well, Tentomon, it's an ancient arena.
But the ancient one didn't have big
screens.
Or soccer goals.
Okay, guys, let's all split up and look
for the crest.
What's wrong?
I can't move anymore.
Let me rest for a little bit.
Come on, get up!
You can do it!
I can't!
Give him a rest, Ty.
Hm?
The only clue we have is my tag.
So Gumamod and I will search for the
crest.
You guys relax for a while.
Later!
Wait, I'll go with you!
A soccer ball!
Hey, anybody up for a game?
Yeah, that sounds fun!
That's a great idea.
The human team will play against the
Digimon team.
What on earth is soccer?
It's easy.
You use your feet to try to get this ball
into the goal.
You can also use your chest or your head.
Here I go!
Oh, that's really using your head.
Oh, and I forgot to tell you, you can't
use your hands.
Unless you're the goalkeeper, then you can
touch the ball with your hands.
Yeah, you should be the goalie for your
team, Palmon.
Here!
Huh?
I can't believe you're playing soccer at a
time like this.
Will you use your heads for something
other than hitting the ball?
The sooner Joe finds the crest,
the sooner we can leave.
Your tag is reacting again.
Yeah.
The crest must be around here somewhere.
Huh?
Who's the king?
Oh!
He's here!
Ekumon's here!
Hey!
Wait for me!
Agumon!
Hey!
We're trapped!
Gold!
I sure did it!
I scored a gold!
The whole thing was a trap!
Does he really think he can trap us with a
simple...
Now, now, listen up!
If you do that, you might get hurt.
You see, there's electricity running
through that net.
It's a shocker, I know it.
I really wanted to be there in person to
do this myself, but I'm way too busy.
You know how us rock and roll legends are.
But don't worry, the axe substituting for
me is a very rare treat.
Let's see if you can
put your puny little heads
together and figure out
who our special guest star is.
Well?
How would we know who it is?
I'm sure you'll be surprised.
Here he comes!
It's a different Grey Moth!
Hey, I knew you'd be surprised.
I'm so evil.
Let's get started.
It's time to go.
Okay, here's the show.
It's time to Digivolve!
Digimon!
You've
got to Digivolve!
Boy, this doesn't look good.
We're done for if you can't Digivolve
again!
Digivolve, Greymon, you've got to!
What's he waiting for?
Why won't he Digivolve to the next level?
It's not working, Ty.
The crust isn't reacting at all.
Maybe you gave him too much to eat.
Maybe he can't Digivolve.
Of course he can!
Come on, Greymon, you can do it!
Believe in your power and you can
Digivolve!
Way to go, Greymon!
Nova Blast!
He certainly doesn't have any Digimanners.
At least they excuse me.
Am I imagining it or is he moving a lot
slower than usual?
He consumed way too much so his reflexes
are sluggish.
You're right, Izzy.
Ow!
Not again.
Get up and fight!
It's looking like this is going to be over
sooner than I thought.
You silly rabbits stop carrying on like a
trained seal.
Get the fireworks ready so I can celebrate
my victory!
Yes, sir!
We need help!
Watching fishes!
Where did those fish come from?
How could they just come out of there like
that?
I don't know, but if it's not broken,
don't fix it!
It's really elementary, Joe.
There's probably just a dimensional vortex
rift in the water.
Ditto!
Oh.
Thank you, fish!
Now, what are we going to do to get out of
here?
We should dig a hole and tunnel our way
out.
Good idea.
There's a black cable here, too.
This rock is in the way.
My tag.
It's... It's reacting again.
What if this rock is the crest we've been
looking for?
If this really is the crest that goes with
my tag, then maybe...
It is my crest!
Yes!
Look, a tunnel!
We can get out through here!
How do you like that?
Not only did those little darlings escape,
but they found another crest, too.
This is unforgivable!
Greymon, you could win if you'd only
digivolve!
Greymon!
Ty, don't!
Don't stop me!
This is my chance to make him digivolve to
the next level!
Please mind your own business,
Sora!
But Ty, without a reaction from the crest,
there's no way for him to digivolve!
I can make him do it!
Watch!
What do you think he's gonna do?
The other condition for digivolving is
their partner must be in danger.
He wouldn't!
Hurry up and finish him off!
Use your Nova Blast!
Stop!
You!
Okay, fire breath!
Come and get me!
What do we have here?
A dope who thinks he's a superstar?
You got it!
Now start singing your final number!
Mm-hmm!
Ah!
Be-o-mon, you've got to help Ty!
You go too, Gob-o-mon!
Got it!
U-mon!
Digivolve to...
Greymon, I believe in you!
You can do it, Greymon!
Digivolve!
What do you think that is?
Oh, my!
Is that what I think it is?
What do you call that thing?
Skull Greymon!
The sight of him makes other Digimon
tremble!
He is a fully digivolved
Digimon whose explosive
power causes him to
constantly search for battle!
This could be very bad!
There's been some mistake and he's
digivolved into a horrible monster!
This is Greymon's digivolved form?
No!
Listen to me, Skull Greymon!
If you're really the Digivolve form of
Greymon, then you can't hurt me!
Ty, get out of there!
Leave it to me!
Tentermon Digivolve to...
Gabu Terrimon!
Digimon?
Oh, no!
Oh, no, my poor network!
They're destroying everything that I
worked so hard to create!
Oh!
Golden Bluster!
ElectroShocker!
I savagely attacked three of my fellow
Digimons.
It wasn't your fault.
She's right.
We completely understand.
I'm really sorry I didn't live up to your
expectations of me, Tai.
It's not your fault.
I know who's to blame.
I know.
It's all my fault.
I'm really, really sorry.
I didn't mean to put it all on you,
Tai.
It's okay.
It's my fault.
Right, Sora?
Yeah.
I mean... I didn't know what I was doing,
but I kept pushing people around anyway.
I felt like because I had the
crest, I had to be in charge
and fight on my own without
any help from the rest of you.
I'm sorry, everybody.
Please forgive me.
You were finally able to Digivolve,
but it was a huge mistake.
I wonder if our Digimon will ever be able
to Digivolve the right way.
One thing's for sure, I learned my lesson.
Okay, so I'll be asking that for more.
Oh, I had to go.
Oh, I'm sorry.
We got to go.
Oh, my God.