Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Change into Digital Champions to save the
digital world!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Digimon is your champions!
Digital Monsters, Digimon are the
champions!
That's home.
Planet Earth.
But I'm not sure that's where I am right
now.
Okay, let me back up a little.
It all began when the climate went
completely out of control.
The rainforest dried
out, and other places got
totally flooded with
oceans like chocolate sauce.
And get this.
Cities which were normally blazing hot in
the summer got super cold.
At the time, I didn't know any of this was
going on because I was at camp.
All of the other campers were,
you know, goofing off and hanging out.
Me?
I was enjoying the summer sun while,
uh, going over my multiplication tables.
That is, until it started to snow in the
middle of July.
Totally freaky.
And it gets weirder.
You won't believe what happened to me and
six other kids.
Oh, by the way, my name's Ty.
Huh?
This is Sora.
She's okay, for a girl.
Huh?
And Matt.
Matt's too cool.
Just look at that haircut.
And this little kid is Izzy.
He should have gone to computer camp.
Huh?
That's Mimi.
I'll bet you can guess her favorite color
on the first try.
TK is Matt's dopey little brother.
Oh, and this is Joe.
But don't ever scare him.
He'd probably wet his pants.
So there we all were at camp, when suddenly
this huge blizzard came out of nowhere.
Needless to say, the canoe races were
cancelled.
So let's have toboggan races instead.
I'm gonna build the biggest snowman.
Hey TK, be careful.
Slow down.
Brr.
It is freezing.
And I didn't bring a jacket.
Man, I was worried I'd catch a summer
cold.
But this is even worse.
Wow!
Why didn't I pack my fluffy pink snow
boots?
Still not working.
Bummer.
This storm's making a mess of my infrared
internet connection.
Look it!
Wow!
Hey, what's your name?
Izzy!
Come on out here!
You gotta see this!
Whoa!
It's beautiful!
Magical even!
Yeah.
Yeah?
What is it?
Maybe an aurora?
You mean aurora borealis, the northern
lights?
That's impossible.
You see that in Alaska.
We're way too far south.
Tell that to the snow.
I really think we ought to get back inside
before we all come down with pneumonia.
Miss this?
The sky is like short-circuiting.
Hey!
What's that?
Oh!
Do you think we need sunscreen?
Everyone, are you alright?
We're still here.
That was scary!
What?
What was it?
Meteors?
Oh!
Okay, so it's not meteors.
Huh?
What?
Are these?
My guess is some sort of miniature remote
digital apparatus.
No instructions?
Get the instructions!
Surf's up!
Woohoo!
Ty!
Yeah, I'm okay.
Last
time I ate camp food.
Hey!
Just what are you?
Have you had your rabies shots?
Everything's gonna be alright now,
Ty!
I've been waiting for you!
Waiting for me?
My name's Coralmon.
And we're partners!
Coralmon?
That means...talking head?
Hmm.
It means brave little warrior.
And don't forget it, Ty!
So what did you mean you've been waiting
for me?
And how did you know my name?
Ty?
Hmm?
Izzy, that you?
It's me.
And I've got this little pink thing
following me everywhere.
It is me, Multimon, at your service.
Anybody want lunch?
Another one?
What are they?
Oh, allow me to introduce myself.
My friends call me Multimon.
Everyone does, actually.
I believe those miniature remote digital
gadgets have taken on an actual life form.
I don't remember anything like this in the
camp brochure.
You think?
It's weird.
The vegetation is lush, but the soil
appears rather common.
Nothing is common in Digi World!
That's right, Ty!
You are in the Digi World!
And just where is the Digi World?
I don't care so much about where it is.
I will know what it is.
Guess I'll just take a look around for
myself.
The ocean?
What's that doing there?
Our campsite was nowhere near the ocean.
And I sure don't remember those mountains.
Hmm.
Something tells me a compass isn't gonna
help much.
Hey, Ty!
What do you see?
Nothing I recognize.
Huh?
Wait.
What's that?
Look at that!
It's some sort of giant red beetle.
And it's flying right at us!
I can't watch.
That is one seriously bad Digimon even
when he's in good mood.
That's just great.
Watch out!
No!
His name is Quagamon.
He's an insectoid Digimon.
Vicious and ruthless.
With teeth like knives and scissor hands
that can chop through anything!
Who needs a gardener?
Help!
Ty, you okay?
Well, I have had better days.
Little guy, you should pick on bugs your
own size.
What's your name?
Coromod?
That's me.
You're pretty brave, for a little guy.
I'm impressed.
It was nothing.
Here, quickly, everyone.
This way.
Come on.
Hurry up!
For having two long legs, you boys are
awfully slow.
Inside this tree!
Let's go!
What kind of tree is this?
It's a hiding tree, silly.
Quiet now!
Don't make a sound!
All clear!
No need to hide!
Sora!
You can come out now.
Oh, we were just planning the trap we were
gonna set for that big bug.
Huh?
I am enchanted to meet you, friends of
Sora!
Welcome!
I, Izzy, meet Yokomon.
My own personal something or other.
Looks kinda like a radish.
Must be another one of them.
Like the other.
Whatever they are.
Uh-oh.
They're popping up everywhere.
Hello!
I am Tokomon.
Hey, TK!
Over here!
Coming!
Come on, there you are!
TK!
Hey, Matt!
You too?
Yeah, I'm here too.
No, I meant that under your arm.
Oh, this guy?
Yeah, well... Hello,
you appear pleasant.
Tsunomon is my name and I am quite pleased
to meet you.
Help me!
This thing!
It won't leave me alone!
Hey, who are you calling a thing?
A no-stuffed animal.
The name is Pokemon.
What's wrong with you guys?
Don't you see this creature hanging off
me?
And those creatures standing right there!
There!
They're everywhere!
What are they?
We're...
Digimon!
Digital monsters!
Digital monsters?
Yes, Digimon!
We're not just digital monsters,
we're much more than that!
We're... kind of cute!
And... very loyal!
With beautiful hair!
Or maybe no hair at all!
We can be funny!
Ha!
And... adorable!
It's a pleasure to meet each of you!
My name's Ty and these are my friends from
camp!
I'd like you to meet Sora!
Nice place you got here, except the bugs!
And the self-proclaimed cool one over
there is mad!
No autographs, please!
And this is Joe!
I'd shake hands, if you had me!
Izzy here's our computer expert!
Do you have internet access?
And last but not least,
this little guy is, uh... TK!
Call me TK!
And I'm not as small as I look!
There now!
Is that everybody?
Hey, what happened to that girl with the
funny pink hat?
Now, now, her name is Mimi.
Well, perhaps she's off picking flowers.
Or going on a nature hike.
Or, uh... Come on!
Okay, so she's not picking flowers.
Mimi, where are you?
There she is!
Mimi, it's okay!
Mimi!
It's that big bug again!
Mimi, are you alright?
I think so.
Don't worry.
Tandamon's here to protect you.
It's okay now.
Oh, sorry!
Watch it!
Here he comes!
Run!
My mom is gonna want a complete and total
refund!
Here he comes again!
That does it!
No more running away!
What else can we do?
She's right!
There's no way we can fight that thing!
Not win, anyway.
Great!
Anybody bring a helicopter?
Be careful, Ty!
There's no way down.
We're going to have to find another way.
Another way where?
Yoko-mon!
Are you crazy?
Why'd you do it?
Sorry, it's just... I'm trying
to make a good impression.
Crazy guy.
Oh... Yoko-mon!
Tandamon, talk to me!
They must be programmed for courage.
Tukumon, what's wrong?
Hey, Tsunumon, wake up!
Bukumon?
Wake up!
Oh no!
Get back!
I
was hoping we'd seen the last of him!
Me too!
Guess he had other plans, huh?
I knew I should've brought my bug spread
out!
Okay, get ready to run!
No, we fight!
Huh?
That's right!
It's the only way!
Stand and fight!
Give it up, will ya?
No, Kuromon's right!
It's time that we showed what we're made
of!
No, don't!
They're right!
No way!
It's hopeless!
You're no match for him, Yoko-mon!
Let me go, let me go, let me go,
let me go, let me go!
Yes, we can get it, we can get it!
Let me go, let me go, let me go!
Tanymon, you too?
Uh-huh!
I'm sorry, Tai!
Let's go!
It's useless!
Yoko-mon!
Don't go-No, wait!
Don't do it, Zuma-mon!
Don't go!
Be careful!
Uh-huh!
Toromon, digivolve
to... Iko-mon!
Yoko-mon!
Digivolve to...
Trio-mon!
Multimon, digivolve
to... Tento-mon!
Tsunomon, digivolve
to... Kabo-mon!
Tocomon, digivolve
Look at them!
What's happened to the little guys?
They're... Bigger!
You asked for it!
Poison Ivy!
Lubbles!
Super Shocker!
Blue Blaster!
Marl Twister!
Rawr!
They made vaporware out of them.
Amazing!
Told you we could do it!
How about that Super Shocker?
Pretty wizard, huh?
Huh?
Watch out!
Guess we celebrated too soon!
So, just when we make some pretty cool
friends, we all take a plunge.
Never to see each other again?
I don't think so.
But find out for yourself next time on
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!