Ty and Oglemon finally returned to the
DigiWorld, but lots had happened.
Demidevilmon had tricked me into thinking
all the other kids didn't like me anymore,
and he made me and Toklemon get in a
fight.
I played with him instead, but I still
miss the others.
When Ty finally found me, I was so happy
that me and Toklemon made friends again,
which made Demidevilmon kind of scared.
He tried to make us eat these mushrooms
that would make me forget about Tokle,
but Oglemon stopped me just in time.
That's when Kalamon boom-bubbled!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Change into Digital Champions to save the
Digital World.
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Where are we, Matt?
Don't tell me we're lost again.
Okay, I won't.
But just take a look at that ridge up
there.
Where?
Hey, other Digimon.
I say we follow them wherever they're
going and hope they're not lost, too.
Huh, now that's weird.
A restaurant in the middle of nowhere?
The perfect location for hungry Digimon.
The usual waiter, a large snow cone.
Same here.
And rotten fruit.
Okay, okay, I got it.
A number four and two specials.
Meet Vegemon, the maniacal manager of a
rundown cafe.
He puts a new spin on the term slave
driver.
Busboy, go get some new customers!
Whoa!
What?
You?
Gomamon, are you okay?
Gabumon, and Matt!
Is Joe ever gonna be happy to see you two?
Hey, Matt.
Hey, Joe.
Where you been and what are you doing
here?
Well, you see, I, um... You left, and
then Mimi and Izzy, they both disappeared.
Then TK and I were left alone.
I know.
Well, it started when we all went our
separate ways to look for Tai.
I wasn't lost.
I definitely knew
where I wasn't, but I just
didn't know exactly
where I was, I think.
You're lost, aren't you?
Ah!
Why did you sneak up on me like that?
Who are you?
Just a friend.
I thought you'd like to know I saw some
other humans just like you nearby.
You say you saw my friends?
Which way?
This way!
But we gotta hurry before we lose him!
I was sure he was leading us the wrong
way, but who was I to question him?
It's not like I knew my way around.
Eventually, we ended up at this
restaurant, which the time was good,
because we were starving.
Boy, I wish my mom cooked that good.
Delicious!
And now the bill!
Oh, of course.
This should be enough.
What are you, some kind of comedian pal?
Huh?
There you go, Vegemon!
Dollar bills?
What did you expect?
Oh, well, I was, um, um, all I have are
digit dollars.
Some play money?
Is all you have?
So, what I'm hearing is...
You actually thought I let you eat without
me!
And now he's making you cook the food to
pay him back.
When I'm not doing dishes or scrubbing
toilets.
Hey!
What's going on here?
I'm not getting richer with you
chit-chatting!
What?
You want me to stay pretty pleased?
They shot that Joe!
Okay, alright, quit yelling or you'll make
me spill all over my pants.
Huh!
About time!
Who are these jokers?
We're friends of Joe and Gomamon.
Well, whoop-dee-doo and good for you!
Ah!
Disgusting!
I can't give that to my customers!
Um, but, but I... Now you'll work an
extra day for the ingredients you wasted!
Another day?
One more day?
On top of how long, Joe?
Well, first... You see, it was only
supposed to be for three days.
But I... I kept on making
mistakes and it got longer.
Now I'm up to over six weeks.
And he still owes me for all the wasted
food!
Not to mention the broken dishes!
That's all the commotion in here!
The customers are complaining!
We didn't know it yet, but
Digitamomon was an evil
Digimon, fully evolved and
protected by his Digi-Eggshell.
Excuse me, are you the restaurant owner?
My friend's been working like crazy to pay
off one lousy meal.
Can't he go now?
Are you kidding me?
This guy's not going anywhere.
Of course, if you stay and work with
him to pay off the debt... Who, me?
If you want help, then just go away!
You're no use to me!
I feel ill.
I'm allergic to kitchen work.
What are you saying?
Oh, just never mind.
Listen, I've got to go and find TK.
But after I do, we'll come back here and
help you work off your debt, okay?
Really?
You will?
That's what friends do, Joe.
When things are tough, they help each
other out.
I'll always remember this, Matt.
Digitamonon, I... I didn't know you were
coming.
Hmm.
Hey, Digit, you have another jab for me to
do.
The new boy!
You mustn't let him leave here.
Where are you going?
You're not finished.
I checked the schedule.
Schedule?
The work schedule.
Now get inside and start cooking or you're
fired!
I quit.
How's that?
You can't quit!
I see you stay!
Hey, what's the big deal, Egghead?
I'm coming right back.
Besides, you already got a slave working
in your kitchen.
Oh, I see!
So you don't care what happens to your
friend while you're gone.
Selfish, aren't we?
What are you talking about?
I'm just saying, while
you're away, there's no
telling what might happen
to your poor little friend.
So many accidents can happen in the
kitchen, you know.
Is that a threat?
Easy, Matt.
He's already cracked.
Hmm...
This water's hot.
If I had some rubber gloves, my fingers
wouldn't get all wrinkled.
Hmm... So hey, just, what
are you making over there?
Is there some reason you're not talking to
me?
I mean, I know you think I can be
irritating sometimes, but what gives?
Matt?
So many accidents can happen in the
kitchen.
So many accidents!
I can't leave him.
Did you hear me?
Earth to Matt!
Come in, Matt!
Although he does talk a lot.
Weren't you gonna go get TK?
If you want to leave, it's
okay... I decided not to go!
Hey, wow.
I'm sorry if I said something that made
you mad.
Huh?
Man, I can't believe what a jerk I'm
being.
Joe's just trying to be nice, and I bite
off his head.
Hey, I'm sorry.
Uh-huh?
I didn't mean to yell at you, okay?
I guess I was just thinking about
something else.
Oh, yeah.
Anyways, I'm a really good cook.
Everything will go a
lot faster if we work
together, and we'll be
out of here in no time.
All right.
I guess that sounds like a plan.
I make a mean PB and J, you know.
Then I'm an expert at boiling water.
All right, then.
We can do it.
Hang on, TK.
I gotta solve this first.
Clumsy!
That'll cost you three more days!
Not again!
That's another week!
Hey!
Wrong, wrong, wrong!
That'll cost you ten more days!
Boy, oh boy.
I don't understand why I'm so
accident-prone.
Okay, so maybe balancing plates on a
platter isn't one of my natural skills,
but now it seems worse than ever.
Sorry, Matt.
Look at me.
I'm falling apart.
And why am I talking to myself?
Even worse, why am I listening and talking
back?
I've got to do something to snap out of
this.
It's okay.
Don't worry about it.
Uh-oh.
Half of what I cook ends up on the floor
and the other half is on his clothes.
This job is giving me a killer headache.
Tell me this is all just a bad dream.
Everything's going perfectly.
Those two will be slaving in that kitchen
for life!
Hmm, looks like a likely spot for another
little accident.
Bring me some potatoes, will you,
Joe?
All right, coming right up.
Those potatoes falling will cost them
another month of work!
Think it'll work?
Quiet, Beaumont.
Here goes.
Nothing happened.
But I'll... Looks like my dirty
tricks will have to be even dirtier.
That's a beautiful sound.
Huh?
Where'd you come from?
I was just passing by when I heard the
sound of your music.
You're very good.
I'm a bad Digimon.
We have good hearing and it sounds as if
you're worried about something.
Huh?
How could you tell?
A musical instrument often reflects the
feelings of the person who's playing it.
Your music sounds sad.
So I figure that you're sad about
something.
I wonder if you're hurting yourself to
help out a friend.
And how would you know?
Well, it's obvious what's happening at the
restaurant.
I see what your friend is up to.
What are you talking about?
I think he's making all those mistakes on
purpose.
He can't be.
Just so you won't leave him there alone.
Not him.
Joe just wouldn't do that to me.
Hmm.
You're a nice guy.
But remember, nice guys wind up washing
dishes for the rest of their lives!
Joe?
Can't be.
Or could it?
Oh, I can't do that.
Listen, I promise you I'll come right
back.
You just have to let me go and get my
little brother.
Oh, I can't do that.
Please!
It's really important.
No!
Now get cooking before the customers start
complaining.
Whoa!
Not more plates!
That's another week for the both of you!
What are you talking about?
I can't stay here another week.
I've got places to go.
You'll stay alright.
And no tips!
Joe, why are you doing this?
Huh?
You think I'm doing this on purpose?
You think I'm juggling plates while I wash
them?
Something tripped me!
Quit making up excuses!
I'm not!
You've got to believe me, Matt.
What's that sound?
My digivice is going off again.
Then our friends are nearby.
It did the same thing when we found TK.
Maybe we'll find my brother!
And maybe some food!
Goomamon!
Gobblemon!
TK!
And Ty!
If you're here, then my brother must be
here too!
And Joe's here too, right pal?
Yeah.
He's here.
But... What's wrong?
Joe can tell you about it.
Joe?
Ty!
I'm so glad to see you guys.
But don't break anything.
Sure.
But what are you doing here?
Hey Joe!
It's great to see you!
But where's Matt?
Oh.
Um... Matt's around back.
Matt!
So?
What are you doing here?
Hey Matt!
TK!
I thought I'd never see you again!
Hey kid!
Are you okay?
I'm great now that we're together again!
So where's Ty?
Hey Matt!
Alright!
There you are!
So, seems like something weird's going on
around here.
Yeah!
You could say we got ourselves into some
hot water.
Oh!
A cooking joke!
I'm really sorry I didn't come back and
keep my promise to get you, TK.
That's alright!
I'm sure you would have if you could have,
Matt!
Anyhow, you're here and that's what
counts.
No, what counts is that we get out of this
weirdo place and quick!
What?
Run away?
Of course run away!
I don't see any guards around here.
I don't want to!
Huh?
Well, why not?
I'll leave when I'm ready.
Anyway, I am not going anywhere with Joe.
Huh?
He doesn't want to work together.
He only cares about himself.
Huh?
How dare you say that, Matt?
We're all friends here!
Right!
What friends?
Oh, you mean this guy who
deliberately wrecks everything
to keep me here cooking
rice until I'm an old geezer?
Hey!
Back off!
And what about you, big shot?
The one who got us all separated?
Matt, stop yelling!
Aren't you glad all your friends met?
Be quiet, TK!
Huh?
Just be quiet and come with me.
Well, well, well.
Huh?
You weren't planning on running away now,
were you?
That would make me very angry.
Yes, that would be a very bad idea.
Hey!
Isn't that... Demikin!
Demi Demi Mon!
It's the evil Digimon we met before!
You lied!
You lied to me to get me to come here.
And you're the one that's wrecking
everything!
So we're gonna teach you a good lesson!
Peppa Breath Point!
Boom!
Bubble Pop!
Hey!
Hey, watch it!
That's hot!
After him, guys!
How dishonest!
Trying to leave without paying me!
You're a thief!
We've worked here long enough to pay for a
trip to Hawaii!
Hawaii's not on schedule!
But if you insist, I'll send you to the
moon!
What?
You wanna leave?
You'll have to beat me first!
Oh!
Digimon!
Gabumon!
Digivol!
Doom!
Garumon!
Digimon!
Doom Blaster!
His shell!
His shell is closed, so the blast has no
effect!
Very perceptive of you!
Garumon!
Ha-ha!
Call off, you beast!
Help me!
How nice!
Your little brother decided to hang
around!
That's going too far!
I've had it!
Digimon!
No!
Ikakuma!
Digimon!
No!
Hey, back off for a ball on the kids'
lunch beat!
Got it!
Stop that!
Ah!
Joe!
He's gone!
Matt!
You were right!
You always said that we would all have to
work together to get out of this mess!
Now, it looks like my turn!
Matt!
We gotta help him!
Go on, Ikakuma!
Blast him now!
Tell your friend I'm a very short-tempered
Benjamin!
Do it, Joe!
No!
You've gotta attack while I keep him busy!
Attack!
I'm fine!
Oh, man!
After I accused him and yelled at him,
he still risked himself for TK.
Joe!
No!
I see you two don't know in the quick!
I'll destroy you both with one shot!
Nightmare syndrome!
No, this is bad!
They're too strong!
We can't just give up!
We've gotta beat them!
But I can't beat them alone!
I need Ty, TK, Sora, Izzy, Mimi,
and Joe!
Together we're strong!
And we can beat anything!
Garurumon!
Where's Garurumon?!
Move!
Ultimate.
G-mon, no monsters, but G-mon are the
champions.
Where's Gabumon?
Ultimate form of Gabumon is a really
fierce warrior with claws, strong kicks,
and jumps.
He's extreme, but Egghead and his little
bat buddy leave him no choice.
Coming up, one scrambled egg.
You and your little doggy don't frighten
me.
Nightmare syndrome!
Impassable!
That was just the beginning, you little
poacher!
Fegemon, hey, Fegemon, hey!
Ultimate form of race, silver boy,
sweet girl, sweet girl, sweet girl,
sweet girl!
They beat Digitommon!
Ay, ay, ay, time for me to fly!
Well, he's gone.
Vegemon, you better let go of him!
Unless you wanna be silent!
Wow, that was so cool, Matt!
I gotta hand it to you, Joe.
That was really brave.
All I did was get grabbed.
By a giant vegetable.
A cranky one.
Uh, Joe?
Huh?
I'm really proud of how you handled this
situation.
At my old school, they voted me most
likely to chicken out.
I guess we showed them.
I also need to apologize.
Oh?
Why, Matt?
Because I... I never should have doubted
you, Joe.
My Otis-mon!
One of the humans got the crest of
friendship to glow in called Weir-Gururu-mon!
What?!
I tried, but... Perhaps your
brain is too small for this job.
You rotten kitten, you rotten Digimon!
You'll pay for this!
So everything is linked.
If we don't fix things here, then our
world will be in trouble, too.
It's going off again!
It seems like every time this happens,
we find one of our friends.
So there must be someone around here.
But which direction?
Well, mine's pointing out there.
Mine says they're off this way.
I guess if we want to find them,
we're just gonna have to split up again.
Yeah, I think you're right.
TK, you hang with me.
Cool.
And Joe will come with me.
Just so nobody gets lost, let's meet at
the foot of that mountain, okay?
Sounds like a plan.
Matt, do you really think we'll meet
again?
Yeah, sure we will.
I guarantee it.
Farewell!
Bye-bye!
Auf Wiedersehen!
Wait!
Don't go yet!
I have to tie my shoe.
Aw, you're ruining our big dramatic exit!
I've got it.
Bye-bye!
Bye.