We were still in the desert
trying to avoid Edamon
and his dark network
when a big ship pulled up.
We got on board and everything was fine,
at least we thought so.
As it turned out, the ship was just a trap
set up by Cockatrymon.
He used his petrifier and turned some of
us to stone.
Fortunately, nothing beats a good
Digivolve.
We sent Cockatrymon flying and a
well-placed cactus took care of the ship.
The next quest turned out to be for Mimi.
And it was then that she realized how
important she was to our adventure.
Digimon, Digital Monsters, Digimon are the
champions!
Change into Digital Champions too!
Save the Digital World!
Digimon, Digital Monsters, Digimon are the
champions!
Digimon, Digital Monsters,
Digimon are the champions!
Digimon, Digital Monsters, Digimon are the
champions!
Digimon, Digital Monsters,
Digimon... Yeah, maybe for a scorpion.
It's beautiful, isn't it, Joe?
And every crest we've found so far has
been different.
Yeah, but we need to learn how to use
them.
Or else our Digimon could digivolve all
messed up, right?
Yeah, but none of that really matters
until we find all the crests.
Hmm, I think you're probably right about
that one, Matt.
Maybe the crest power comes from having
them all.
Hmm, what are they doing back there?
Hey, we gotta move on.
If we're gonna take some down time,
we need to find some shade.
Aw, thanks, Ty.
We were right in the
middle of a serious digit
conversation about
the crest and everything.
And then you made me forget what I was
saying.
You'll be in charge of finding the shade.
We'll catch up.
Whoa!
What happened?
Something grabbed them from underneath.
Oh!
It's Guagamo!
Whoa!
Is that the same one?
Really?
Huh?
It's Guagamo all right.
There's no mistaking that ugly face.
But he's sure bigger than he was the last
time.
Whoa!
Top of red.
We have a big problem.
This guy's much stronger than he used to
be.
Oh, no!
Now!
Digivolve!
Agumon, digivolve to Greymon!
All right.
Rethinking our training program here.
Oh, man.
I hope Agumon doesn't freak out.
What if something's wrong with me?
What if I can't become Greymon?
Agumon, stay away from his choppers!
Oh, move, Agumon!
Move!
Do something!
Get back!
I got you!
Nice one!
Pixie Bomb Seek and Destroy!
Check it out.
Are you two okay?
Agumon, do a tie.
Are you okay?
What just happened to us?
A powder puff with wings!
Just don't use it on your face.
And where's Quagumon?
Oh, man.
Maybe that's him.
Ha!
I am no enemy.
Nope, nope.
If anything, you are your own enemies.
Oh, I've heard of you.
You're the famous Pixiemon, right?
You are?
Pixiemon is famous in
the digital world for his
skills and training, but
few have ever met him.
His secret home is the training ground for
all the great Digimon fighters.
And I've heard all about you too,
but so far I am not impressed.
Huh!
You seven are supposed to be the
Digi-destined.
Ha!
You'd better be more careful or you'll end
up Digi-dinners.
Yep, yep.
Without my spears and
my magic, Quagumon
would be eating you
with a side of Digi-fries.
That's gross.
Thanks a lot.
And that's not all.
You Digimon there!
You're supposed to protect the children,
but half the time they're protecting you!
I want to see some guts!
I want to see some courage!
This guy reminds me of a gym teacher I
once had.
He's right.
We just don't have any guts.
Hmm.
Don't we get points for enthusiasm?
But the news isn't all bad.
Yep, yep.
From now on you're all going to train with
me!
But why?
Let's not go overboard, Pixiemon!
Especially you two guys!
What?!
You heard me!
You two need lots of help and I have a
special extreme training program just for you!
Did I hear him right?
Sounds kinda extreme.
Yep!
Follow me!
I have a question.
Do we trust a ping pong ball with wings?
But he did save Agumon and me.
Why would he do that if he was no good?
Precisely.
He didn't have a black gear anywhere on
him.
I checked.
What do you say, Biomon?
After all, you seem to know a lot about
him.
Well, it's an honor to be chosen for
training by Pixiemon.
Sounds like a lot of work to me.
He's right though.
We could use some help.
How can you say that?
Just cause we've nearly been eaten a
hundred times.
Well, there are worse options.
I mean, do we have a choice?
All in favor say aye.
Aye!
Would you all just hurry up?
Are we there yet?
Just a little further!
That's about the seventh time he's said
that.
I think he's lost.
So what do we do?
Ask a cactus for directions?
Ice cream.
Cold rupees.
Shut up!
Oh!
We have arrived!
What are you talking about?
There isn't anything here.
Pixie portal!
It's a hole in the desert.
Am I the only one who thinks this looks
like trouble?
Actually, it's just my front door.
Come on in now quickly before it closes.
Yep, yep.
Cool, a jungle inside a desert.
I bet you got lots of friends who want to
play with you.
You should have seen it when I first got
it.
Huh?
Heads up!
Behind us, guys!
Huh?
What?
Oh no, it's Edelon and his trailer.
Oh boy, this is bad.
And right outside the front door he is,
too.
Huh?
Oh, don't worry about it.
He isn't able to see through the barrier.
He sees nothing but desert.
The stupid screen is still broken.
What's taking so long?
We've almost got it fixed at your mind.
No need for a conniption fit.
Yeah, I'll show you conniption,
you insolent little worms.
Fix it right away.
I have a show to get on.
All right, everybody.
Home we are.
My house is just up these steps.
Whoa.
We have to walk a fair?
But I didn't bring my stair-climbing
sneakers.
Yeah, and I just remembered I'm afraid of
heights.
Purely from a logical standpoint,
it doesn't look very safe.
Is this part of our training?
Exactly!
Hey, no sweat.
I'll just fly up there, and
before you know it, I'll
be chilling by the pool
while you guys are still...
And no, by the way,
did I mention there will
be no flying by anyone
during all my training?
Oh?
Haven't you rookies learned that the easy
way is sometimes a trap?
Now let's move out!
Aw!
I guess Pixiemon never heard of elevators.
Don't tell me you're all tired.
Don't give up yet!
You see, you've almost arrived!
That's his place?
That's it, and there's plenty of food for
all!
Yum, yum, yum!
Well, thank you.
Is it as handsome as I am?
You said something about food?
Ah, yes.
But first, you must earn it.
I should've known there'd be a catch.
I
want you all to scrub the floors!
All the floors!
Serious!
Not serious!
Take forever!
But not you, Agumon and Tai!
Come now!
I have a special chore for you!
Great, we probably have to paint the
place.
Well, let's do it.
The last time I scrubbed a floor was...
never!
It's a simple task, Mimi.
Even you'll catch on.
Is this really training,
or is this just Pixiemon's
maid's day off and he
doesn't like to vacuum?
Togumon, let's have a cleaning race!
Ready, set, go!
Broom!
All right, you two.
This is the place.
Yep, yep.
Come on into the cave.
Wow, it's pitch black in here.
What kind of a chore can
we do in here when we won't
be able to see our hands
in front of our faces?
This is your training!
You must find your way back!
What delicious food!
Mine all mine!
Huh?
Shh!
Something's wrong.
Tai and Agamon never came back.
So what do you think happened?
Whoa!
You see that?
Prodigious!
When they glow, it means the crests are
nearby.
Are you sure this is a good idea,
Matt?
I mean, maybe we should bring
Tenamon and Goblin... Let him sleep.
The crests must be inside the barrier so
we're safe.
Come on, Izzy!
This way!
Hmm... Hmm?
Tai!
Tai, wake up!
Hey, wait.
Where are we?
I don't know.
We were in a cave, but I don't
remember any boat and I sure... Hey!
Hello!
Don't you know not to stand up in a boat?
Here, grab this.
Huh?
Do you see that light?
Don't look at the light.
Pull me in.
Hey!
Don't rock the boat, Hala!
Now look what you did.
We're both in the water.
What I did?
You were the one standing up in the boat.
I was just trying to pull...
Well, if you'd been watching
what you were doing instead
of looking at some stupid
light in the distance...
If you hadn't pulled on the oar,
we wouldn't be swimming like tuna...
I do not swim like a tuna fish!
We'd be back in the boat for the truck!
And where do you get off blaming...
Huh?
What is it?
What's going on?
Rise and shine, everybody!
Everybody up!
Come on, people!
Peekamon, do you know where Izzy went?
He's not in his bed.
Huh?
And I can't find Matt.
What?
Hey, did you send my brother somewhere?
Your brother and his pal left to look for
crests about midnight.
Oh, I don't believe it.
Why would Izzy leave me behind?
Isn't it strange?
First it's Agumon and Ty leaving.
Now it's Matt and Izzy gone.
Ever since we met Pixiemon, people started
disappearing.
Maybe next Joe will turn up missing.
Come on, you guys.
It's not funny.
Stop fooling around.
What if it's Pixiemon making everyone
disappear?
Come on, Joe.
Chill.
We can trust Pixiemon, can't we?
I mean, you wouldn't do anything really
cool, would you?
Like not feed us?
Attention!
Training will now begin!
Why do you want to find a crest,
Izzy?
I guess it's mostly just because of
Kabuterimon.
I would like to see what stage he will
digivolve into after that one.
Isn't that the reason why you're looking
for a crest?
No.
I want to use the crest to digivolve me.
Oh?
Not into a Digimon, but to make me
stronger and smarter.
Maybe learn something new about myself,
you know, to reach my next level.
The barrier of this land!
Don't tell me we came all this way for
nothing.
Wait!
Look at that glow!
We made it!
The crest!
The crest have got to be right there
inside the well.
Let's go!
Yeah, but it's outside the wall.
I know, but we're so close!
I hope my hand doesn't melt!
Hey!
It's okay, Matt!
We can go through it!
Yeah!
See anything?
The light's bright down here.
Hey!
We should try holding our tags up towards
the wall!
Good call!
Mmm!
Wow!
Izzy!
Man, this is happening!
We both found our crests!
Edgimon!
We have contacted Sector G3, sir!
What?
Well, that's the sector we just passed
through!
Turn us around!
Turn us around, you little whippersnapper!
What are you waiting for?
G3's Tyranimon's territory!
Send him at once!
I love a roadie with a good appetite!
Tyranimon!
A huge Digimon with fire breath strong
enough to cook a couple of boys like you!
No, G3's Tyranimon!
No, Garberman!
Making funny faces will not defeat your
enemies!
You must always... Huh?
My barrier's been broken!
Oh, Izzy's there!
He might be in trouble!
And Matt!
We've got to help him!
Didn't I see this guy in one of my
nightmares?!
I wish you'd be more careful what you
dream.
Matt!
Izzy!
Oh, thank goodness you're safe!
April!
Well, well, well, isn't that nice?
Everybody's all together now.
You know I can't resist an audience,
so I guess it's showtime.
I hear this song I call bye-bye,
Digimon, bye-bye.
My power's been drained.
It zapped them!
So now they can't digivolve!
It's no use.
The more we fight it, the farther away we
drift.
I remember this bridge.
What is it?
Who's that?
Me.
But I... What?
That's you?
You die!
Agumon, what are you doing?
Your friends are in trouble!
You've got to come back before it's too
late!
Die!
Can you hear me?
I'm never gonna learn how to ride my bike.
Don't give up!
You can't call it quits now just because
of one or two mistakes you made.
Man, I've made plenty and I ought to know.
You just have to get up and try again.
Uh-huh!
Okay, I'll try.
We can hold you up!
From behind!
See?
You're doing it!
You're doing great!
Hey, I'm doing it all by myself.
I'm riding!
Wait, Agumon, I get it.
It's all about overcoming your fear.
I was so afraid of you digivolving back
into Skull Greymon again that I lost it.
You must be a mind reader.
That same fear stopped me from digivolving
to Greymon.
But if we really believe in ourselves,
it'll be just like riding a bike.
Greymon, my friend, I'm coming back to
you.
We're on our way back!
Right!
Together!
Oh!
They're in real trouble!
Can't wait for Tai any longer.
He needs this lesson, but I've got to
attack!
Everyone stand back!
Agumon, digivolve!
Digimon, digital monsters, Digimon are the
champions!
Agumon!
Digivolve!
Hey, he digivolved!
Yay!
Nova Browse!
Pulling the cables out!
Black
cables all shattering into pieces!
Got
it kind of close, but they did it!
Yep, yep!
Those run kids beat me again!
Oh, I've got to find something easier to
beat like some cardboard boxes or something!
Thank you, Pixiemon.
We've learned a lot from you.
Yeah, like how to scrub floors and starve
half to death.
Joe!
That's just Joe's stomach talking.
Far from over your training is.
Remember, life itself is a training
session.
Learn all you can.
Right!
They truly are the Digi-Dustin.
Yep, yep.
No doubt have I, for
though they are sometimes
foolish, I have seen
the love in their hearts.
With a little luck, they just may succeed
and save our digital world.