We finally found Mimi living
like a princess in a castle
with a bunch of froggy-looking
guys called Gekkomon.
They had the idea that
Mimi singing could wake
up their lord and master
from a kind of coma.
But Mimi loved the royal treatment,
so she just strung them along.
She made up lots of excuses why she
couldn't get through her song,
and when we told her to stop fooling
around, she went and threw us in prison.
Nice, huh?
She finally came to her senses and sang
her song.
The big guy woke up, but in a nasty mood.
Thanks to MetalGreymon, we get out in one
piece.
Digital Monsters, Digimon are the
champions!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters, Digimon are the
champions!
Digimon!
Because of Demi-Devimon's tricks,
we all became separated.
Once we caught wind of that blowhard,
we were able to find each other.
Except for Zora.
Okay, we're here.
I'm tired.
Come on, Mimi, get off your throne.
I wouldn't exactly call this a throne.
Yeah, well, I wouldn't call you a
princess.
Guys, over here!
Hey, it's Matt!
It's been so long since I've seen you.
Mike, you've shrunk.
Don't rub it in!
Where's Zora?
We thought you might know.
We haven't seen her.
That's weird.
It's not like her to disappear like that.
Well, actually, I think I saw Zora.
Huh?
So where did you see her?
At the Gigimon's castle, but I might have
been...dreaming.
That a girl.
I knew you'd come back to yourself.
I think you're right.
It must have been a dream.
Actually, I forgot that when I was just
about to eat one of those mushrooms of
forgetfulness, when I was Agumon, I heard
a voice that sounded a lot like Zora's.
That's real weird.
But then, if Zora is
actually close to where
we are, why doesn't
she come out and tell us?
Well, maybe Zora just doesn't want to.
Even worse, maybe she just can't.
All I know is we've got to find her quick.
It's almost like we're playing tag with
her.
Come on, the signal point's this way.
Because of your stupidity, all of my evil
plans have failed.
Oh, boy.
My Otismont.
How'd I ever get stuck working for this
guy?
Talk about a bad temper.
And he's got all those bats.
I hate bats.
Give my mistakes, Master.
My Otismont.
I beg you.
Courage.
Hope.
Friendship.
The children's crests are beginning to
glow, one by one.
Everyone makes mistakes.
Remember, Disco?
Besides, sir, not all the children's
crests have begun to glow yet.
That girl has the crest of love,
and it's still not glowing thanks to me.
Anyway, according to
my schedule, she'll be
meeting up with the
other children very soon.
And when she does, Master
My Otismont, when they
are all together, that's
when I'll get them.
You think you can?
If you fail me again, my bats will have a
new chew toy.
You!
I hate bats.
Zora!
Where are you?
Oh, why don't we find a spot to rest for
the night?
Or better yet, for the next couple of
weeks?
My feet are killing me, not to mention
every other part of my body.
I can't go another inch!
Hold it.
I'm getting a reading on my digivice.
Really?
Oh!
Well, what is it?
What's that fuzzy?
I wonder if it's Zora.
What's that sound?
Flymon's here!
Brown stickers!
Maybe this Digimon analyzer the Jedi gave
me could help us out.
Here he is, Flymon.
Classified as an insect Digimon,
a virus type.
And I think we already know what his
attack is.
And it's not very pleasant.
And here he comes now!
Careful, Tie!
Whoa!
Look out, man!
Horomon Digivolve to...
Agumon!
Tune-o-man, digi-ball to...
Kabu-man!
Agu-man!
Pepperbreath!
New blaster!
It's just not working, they need more
help!
Munching fish in!
Blazing ivy!
Bounce fingers!
It's Perdramon!
If Perdramon's here, then so is Sora!
No!
Sora!
Wait up, Ty!
You're coming!
I'm going with you!
T.K., wait up!
Sora, it's you!
So why were you running away?
Enough running, tell us what's going on!
Sora?
Sora, does this mean that you don't like
us anymore?
No... Of course not!
Then what's wrong?
Sora, why don't you tell them?
Okay.
It happened the night that Biomon and I
left camp to try and find Ty.
Shh!
Someone's here!
Huh?
Oh!
I saw a strange Digimon.
He looked like a bowling
ball with wings, and
he was talking to
something in a giant bubble.
So could you hear what he was saying?
Yeah, I heard him talking about our
crests.
What about them?
He was saying that each of our crests has
its own special meaning.
For example, Ty, yours is the crest of
courage.
The crest of courage?
Oh!
Gather your courage!
That's right!
And then the crests started to glow!
And the crest you have, Matt, is the crest
of friendship.
Friendship.
And mine?
Yours is special, TK.
It's the crest of hope.
Alright!
I hope we can get back home!
Izzy's crest is the crest of knowledge.
Joe's is the crest of reliability.
Thanks for being there, Joe.
And Mimi's is the crest of sincerity.
And finally mine?
Mine is the crest of love.
Wow!
The crest of love?
That's just perfect for you, Sora!
No, it's not!
You're wrong!
Don't even say that, Ty!
It's not like me at all!
But Sora, it is like you.
You're always thinking of everyone else.
No way!
I don't care what happens to everyone
else!
The truth is, you don't know the first
thing about me!
So back off!
I'm sorry, Ty.
Sora, what's the matter?
It's just that my crest... it won't glow!
Huh?
It's because I don't have any love.
You love us, don't you, Sora?
I don't get it.
Why is it that girls always have to get so
emotional when it comes to love?
Leave her alone, Ty.
I was just joking around.
The Digimon thought I was funny too.
Is your name by any chance Demi-Devimon?
It sure is!
And you're one of those kids that did your
destiny!
Tell me something.
Did you hear about the crests?
Yes, in fact I did.
Oh yeah!
You're that kid Sora!
The crest of love!
And why are you laughing about that?
You just think you're so hot!
But guess what?
You'll never be able to make the crest
glow!
Never!
Oh!
That's it?
I thought it was something
serious like they were
gonna stop making those
stuffed beanbag animals.
Besides, Demi-Devimon is a liar!
It's true.
It started back when I was on a girls'
soccer team.
My family owned a flower shop.
It was my mom's whole life.
Please mom, I gotta go to the soccer
match!
The girls are counting on me!
Don't talk so loud, dear.
The flowers are very sensitive.
But this match is to win the title!
Sora, you can't go with your knee injured
like that.
But mom, my leg's fine.
I'm sorry, you can't go.
Sit down, we need to talk.
I want you to stop playing soccer and come
to work at the flower shop after school.
Do what?
I won't stop playing to work with smelly
old flowers!
I can't believe a daughter of mine would
act this way.
My decision is final.
Why can't you understand me?
I walked around for hours.
I found myself at the soccer field.
The game had just finished.
What happened?
We lost the game six to three.
My teammates were
so depressed that they
didn't even notice me
when they walked by me.
I felt like I had let them all down.
Like it was all my fault.
My mom said I had to be part of the family
business.
No questions.
That's how she is.
It's like it's the only thing that's
important to her.
She doesn't understand.
That's why I know he wasn't lying when he
said I grew up not knowing what love is.
Wow!
Sora, stop it!
Let go!
Even if what you said
is true, you shouldn't
believe a word from
that loser Demi-Devi-mon.
He's just a creep that's trying to hurt
you.
Wait, wait!
Don't cry, Sora!
Matt, help me out.
I don't know what to do with her when she
starts blubbering.
Just let her go, Ty.
She'll be okay.
Boy, Matt's like a real grown-up.
How if only he would cut his hair.
Sora, I forgot to thank you.
Huh?
You told us not to eat the mushrooms,
didn't you?
I want to thank you for saving us.
Right, TK.
We thought Demi-Devi-mon
was up to no good, so we kept
out of sight and made sure
you guys stayed out of trouble.
We were even there when you guys were
working in the restaurant, Matt.
I had no idea.
You didn't have to hide from us.
We were all worried.
Sora just needed to be alone for a little
while.
But she really didn't want to be separated
from you guys.
Please understand.
Hmm... Sora, I like you.
Huh?
So please, don't go away again.
I don't like being away from you.
When you're around, I don't miss my mom as
much.
TK...
I'm so, so sorry.
Hey!
Hey, what took you guys so long?
Well, we would have been here sooner,
but Joe fell in the river.
Hey Mimi, you're the
one who was hungry and
tired and had to sit
down every five minutes.
Finally, they're all together.
I must tell my Otis-mon.
Let's go.
My Otis-mon will be so proud of my work,
maybe I'll get a promotion.
Demidart.
Sora, watch out!
No, Biomon!
Please wake up!
Biomon!
Sora, I will protect you.
Oh, no.
Sora, what's wrong?
Demi-Demimon!
Ah!
Hey, what is that?
Digi-Destined!
Your journey ends here.
That's it!
That's the thing Demi-Devi-mon was talking
to!
He's not a thing, he's Lord Myotismon!
Myotismon?
It's Lord Myotismon!
These Digi-destined are making me feel a
little batty.
Grizzly-wee!
Come on, guys, let's go!
Pepperbred!
Blue Blaster!
Come on, Digi-Ball!
Pentamon!
Super Shocker!
Ball bubble!
There's
no!
Me-me!
Calmon, Digi-Ball too!
Togomon!
Let me try to get my point across!
Needle Stray!
Domomon, Digi-Ball too!
Ikakuma!
Harpoon Torpedo!
Wow, way to go!
You can't defeat me that easily!
Crimson Lightning!
Kai,
he's just too strong for us!
Now what?
I've gotta do something to help them!
Huh?
I'm the only one left to fight Myotismon!
It's no use!
You can't do anything in your condition!
Please understand, Sora!
I have to go!
No, Rioman!
You can't!
You'll get hurt!
I won't let you!
My decision is final!
Sora, why can't you understand?
Huh?
Why can't you understand?
I always thought my mom
was thinking about her flower
shop, but she was really
worried about me getting hurt!
We are on Digibob 2!
Erdramon!
Meteor Wing!
Crimson Lightning!
Erdramon!
Digimon!
Garudamon!
What?
Where is that glow coming from?
Sora, I can feel your love.
It's making me strong.
My crest... it glows.
Garudamon is the ultimate form of
Birdramon.
She commands the sky and protects the
Earth.
Her attack is a flaming bird called
Wingblade.
Ah, why is it now the crest of love glows
just as I was about to claim victory?
I'll protect you, Sora!
Hey, Digimon!
Answer friends to the board!
Wingblade!
Grisly Wing!
I did not anticipate such strength.
Come on, everyone.
Climb on!
Next time you won't escape!
All you had to do was stop worrying about
it, Sora, and you got your crest to work!
When Biomon was in
danger of getting hurt, I
realized that I was
acting just like my mom.
You know what I realized?
My mom loved me all along.
And it was your love that helped me ditch
evolve, Sora!
I'm glad.
You see, you aren't capable of love after
all!
I felt something.
I guess it was your love shining through.
I felt something, too.
It made me feel uncomfortable.
Love shouldn't make you feel like that.
That's right, TK.
I know why you felt uncomfortable,
Joe.
Why?
These were in your pocket.
Oh, I guess it wasn't love.
Sora joined up with us again, and we were
closer than ever.
We finally thought things were going our
way.
And then...
I know that laugh!
You foolish digi-destin!
The seven of you are no match for my
powers!
Prepare for your ultimate destruction!
You bring your pals walk!
Take care!