Wizardmon, a longtime friend of Gatomon,
was able to make her remember that she was
to be the Digimon of the Eighth Child, who
turned out to be my little sister, Kari.
Gatomon had been waiting in the Digi-World
for a long time, and when Kari didn't show
up, Myotismon took her under his grizzly
wing and convinced her that she was evil.
Our new friends then
tried to get the true crest
from Myotismon's lair,
but he surprised them.
Good news is, he didn't know that Kari was
the Eighth Child.
Bad news is, he's using Gatomon to find
out who is.
Digimon, digital monsters, Digimon are the
champions!
Change into digital champions to save the
digital world!
Digimon, digital monsters, Digimon are the
champions!
Due to the continuing heavy fog, we'll
be experiencing some delays up ahead.
Please bear with us.
Ha!
It's almost done.
Soon now, not in fire or ice, but in fog,
this world will be mine!
Yuck!
This soil's polluted!
Tastes like gasoline and old candy
wrappers.
I've got this bottled water.
Try it.
It's fresh and pure as a winter morning in
the Swiss Alps.
At least that's what it says on the
bottle.
Okay, pour it on my roots.
Mmm!
Yummy!
Yodley-poo!
Hush!
Hmm?
Mimi?
Is that you?
Mimi, what are you doing out here?
Oh!
Hi, Dad!
You should be inside.
Well, you see, I was just waiting for you!
Huh?
So, Dad, why are you so late, anyway?
It's this fog.
It's got everything tied up in knots.
Say, what's that you got under your hat
there?
Oh!
It's just, uh, uh... Ooh!
Burr, it's getting cold out here.
We better hurry up and get home or Mom
will be worried.
Hi, honey!
Hello!
Sorry.
I could have pretended you were my doll or
a stuffed animal, I suppose.
But I have a reputation for good taste to
maintain.
I'm in bad taste?
Is that what you're saying?
Oh, Palmon, I didn't mean it that way.
Really?
I made this dish up myself.
Well, I call it shrimp fried rice with
whipped cream and strawberries.
Well...
You've really outdone yourself this time,
honey.
You mean it?
Oh, I'm so glad you like it.
I mean it.
Really?
Really.
I can't believe I got a C.
There goes med school and my dad wanted me
to call right away and tell him my grades.
A C?
Forget about my oldest mom.
This is a real disaster.
You're right.
Clearly this grade is the result of all
the stress from the monster attacks.
Well, if you can't get into medical
school, I'd try politics.
Oh, no!
Give me a break.
Come on.
Huh?
Aw, man.
Right when it was about to get to the best
part.
Hey, what's going on, Charlie?
You're awake.
I was just coming to get you.
The whole system's gone down.
Transmitters, satellite feed, the whole
shebang.
What?
If it's a systems glitch, it's like the
Godzilla of all systems glitches.
But we can't even check it out because
communications are down too.
It's like the end of the world or
something.
No one will escape.
No one.
Not even the eighth child.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Due to a systems failure, all trains will
be delayed indefinitely.
We apologize for the inconvenience.
The payphones don't work either.
What's going on?
Everything's falling apart.
It could be worse.
We could be stuck on the train.
Everything started going wonky ever since
that fog came in.
Even my cell phone isn't working.
Of course, it wasn't working before,
but still.
Hey, where are you going?
To earn my pay.
To investigate this thing.
That's what I do, after all.
We'll come with you.
Believe in yourself.
Say it.
I believe in me.
Good.
Hey, Ty.
Do you think Gato Mom's okay?
Sure she is, Kari.
First thing tomorrow, we'll go find her.
Don't worry.
I think we'd better go to bed.
We'll need our rest to fight my Otis Mom.
Don't want to fall asleep on the job,
do ya?
Okay.
You scared, Kari?
Not really.
Atta girl.
Leave everything to me.
I'm dying my clothes pink again.
Okay.
Looks like Dad's working late again.
Something weird's going on.
We're just getting our child down.
The fog's disrupting our entire area.
Why isn't any other part of town seeing
fog?
It's like some alien powers controlling
the fog bank with magic or something.
Magic?
Stop trying to scare me.
Keep quiet.
What's that?
Shh!
Keep it down.
You both saw it?
Mm-hmm.
Good.
At least I know I'm not the only one going
crazy.
What's the connection?
Somehow the fog's tied in with these
monsters we keep seeing.
Let the humans scream.
It doesn't bother us, Gizamon.
We travel in packs creating terror,
whether on land or under water.
Everyone, get in the car!
An impenetrable fog has sealed off the
main district of the city.
Incoming reports also
verify that all communication
systems appear to have
been rendered useless.
I'm coming, Matt.
TK!
I have to go!
You don't understand.
Whatever happens, they'll need me there.
Mm-mm.
Aw, Mom.
Matt is there.
And so is Dad.
We can't just leave them.
Oh.
All right, then.
We'll go together.
Get your coat, son.
Yeah.
Wake up, son.
Get up and get dressed.
Uh... What is it?
Dad, what happened to you?
I'll tell you later.
Just get up and get dressed, okay?
Joe, where are you going?
Down to the pier.
Maybe we can get in by boat.
An announcement will be made when service
has been restored.
We apologize for any inconvenience.
What in the world is that thing?
I'm Phantoman.
You don't want to be near
me or my frightening little
friends when I start to
swing my... shadow side.
My Otifman requests your presence and he
won't take no for an answer.
Are you really going to soccer practice
today?
Ty will be there and I really need to talk
to him about our plan of attack.
Besides, I could use the practice.
Mom!
I'm going to soccer.
Mom?
Well, I'll see you in a little bit.
Oh great.
The phone's still out.
Oh, your poor father.
I hope he's not stuck in the subway.
We're not watching that video again.
The TV's still out, sweetie.
I wonder who'd be dropping by unannounced.
Coming!
Hello?
All right, we're all safe now.
But honey, what are they?
It's a long story, Mom!
Oh my God!
Spiral Twister!
You just talked!
I saw you!
I thought you were a stuffed animal!
Well, life's full of surprises.
Where's the soccer field?
It's down at the school!
Why do you ask?
All you need to know is, Sora's in
trouble.
I've got to find her.
We'll start by separating the children
from their parents.
Ah, how they'll scream and weep delicious.
I guess you're not as powerful here in the
real world as you thought you'd be.
Power isn't anything
I'd concern myself with if
I were you, especially
since you don't have any.
You little traitor.
Now will you tell me what happened,
Dad?
I hardly know myself.
But I want you to stay here.
Out of sight.
Where are you going?
The station.
To try to find some way to communicate
with the outside world.
Smoke signals.
Anything.
You'll be safe here.
Stay with Gabumon.
How do you know about me?
But Dad, how?
Never mind how.
Just be safe.
You know, I think he likes me.
Agumon!
Digivolve!
To...
Graymon!
Oh no!
Another monster!
Don't worry.
This monster's on our side.
Get my mom, Graymon!
Hurry!
Shadow side!
Well, Graymon, it looks like your time is
up.
Get the rest of the crowd.
No!
Nova Blast!
Sorry, Ty.
I'm losing it.
We'll get your mom later.
Right now, we've got to get out of here.
Mommy!
Oh, we'll be there!
Ty!
We'll follow them and find out where
they've taken her.
But will it work?
We'll see.
Sora!
It's you!
Oh no, Mimi.
They got you too.
Psst!
I can digivob anytime!
Just say the word!
There's too many people, and too many of
them.
Let's see how this plays out.
You'll be our trump card for later.
Got it!
I can't stand it!
I can't stand not knowing!
Calm down, dear.
How can I calm down?
For all we know, that monster's devoured
the children by now!
Don't worry.
He's one of ours.
Huh?
There's a lot more where he came from.
We've got some powerful friends.
Besides, we've got truth and justice and
all that good stuff on our side.
Well, if you can't beat him, join him!
Now let's go inside and find Sora!
Right!
Wait, this may be a strange question,
but did Sora ever say, Did she tell you,
Does Sora hate me?
What?
Oh boy, do you have it wrong!
Then I realized I was worried about you
just the way my mother worries about me.
And now I know for sure.
My mom loved me all along.
And it was your love that helped me
digivolve, Sora!
I'm glad.
Sora...
How could it be worse?
You could work for
minimum wage in a foam
rubber suit with kids
kicking you all the time!
Right, guys?
Right!
What is it, Mom?
I just can't stay in this place one second
longer!
Well, you've been wanting to get away.
Look at this as a vacation.
Who asked you to talk?
I'm sorry, children.
I didn't mean to yell.
It's just that I'm not used to being held
captive by creatures from another world.
Don't worry, lady.
You'll get used to it.
But I don't want to get used to it!
I want to go home and sleep in my own bed!
I want to live life to the fullest!
I want to clean lint out of my dryer!
I want to pick up after my doggy!
I want to know what's happening on my soap
operas!
I'm so glad I got that off my chest!
Enough of this!
We need a plan!
Yeah, Jeremiah.
Why don't you help
us instead of listening
to those Mind Over
Matter tapes all the time?
What'd you say?
The only way to weaken Bakuman is with
Mind Over Matter!
Huh?
Mind over what?
It's an old Roman technique.
You repeat a phrase over and over again
and it helps you focus your mind!
That's it!
We need some of you to attack
the Bakuman creating a diversion
while the rest of us come up
with a Mind Over Matter chant!
What's that mean?
Just do what she says, alright?
Half of you come with me!
Let's get em!
Women and children, follow me!
Bakuman, lose your powers!
We made it!
We're safe at last!
Oh, smoke too soon!
It's Dark Tyranimon!
He was actually a nice guy
once until he was taken over
by an evil computer virus
and his personality did a 180!
Huh?
Where are you going?
You couldn't be in safer hands!
Come on, did you evolve too?
Togomon!
Back to the stone age with you!
Dad!
Honeybunch, are you okay?
I guess I made a fool of myself,
huh?
Don't be ridiculous!
That was the bravest thing I ever saw!
Really?
You mean it?
I mean it!
Oh, honey!
Oh, Mom!
Dad!
I hate to ruin this love fest, but maybe
we should run for cover or something!
No!
Togomon!
It's no use!
Save yourself!
I got it under control, no problem!
This is the end!
It's over!
Yeah!
My Ohisman will rule the world!
Ah!
Oh!
This is terrible!
Now my family's going to suffer and so are
my friends!
There's got to be something I can do!
Huh?
Digimon!
Where'd she come from?
Flower cannon!
Whoa!
Who are you?
It's just little old me!
Or should I say little old us?
I'm Palmon and Togomon too!
This is just my fully digivolved form!
You can call me Lillimon!
Am I?
In bad taste?
No way!
I'm sorry I ever said the...
No biggie!
You have to be quicker than that!
Be careful!
Your wish to save your family and friends
brought me into existence!
Mimi, you're a very special girl, even
though your wardrobe sometimes clashes!
What do you mean?
Later!
Right now I have a dinosaur to tame!
My flower wreath counteracted
the evil computer virus,
so he oughta be as gentle
as a lamb from now on!
Nice to run him on!
That boy!
Please bear with us!
I should have known!
What made me think the boats would be
running when nothing else is?
It could be worse!
We could be stuck in some crazy...
Please stop saying it could be worse!
I have news for you, pal!
It is worse!
The whole world is stuck in turmoil and
we're waiting for a ride into town!
We might as well just give up right now!
Well, I wouldn't go that far.
After all, it could be worse!
Huh?
Maybe if I can just get to that satellite
dish.
You okay, Agumon?
I felt better.
Ty!
Huh?
Up here!
Matt!
Is that you?
Hey, we gotta talk!
You feel any better?
A lot better!
Thanks, Kari!
What?
You're kidding me!
No, it's true.
Kari's the eighth child.
Enough!
Get off!
That new-age drichobabble won't help you
where you're going, my pretty little miss.
Seize her!
Take it away!
What?
Oh,
it's just a bird.
A large bird, I grant you.
A large, angry bird!
Sarah!
Oh, Mom.
I'm so... There's
no time now, honey.
You've got to get out of here.
Hurry!
But what about you?
Get moving!
I'll be fine!
No, Mother!
We'll see about that.
Back to the digital world with you!
You are such a bad sport!
You, meddlesome little flower child!
It's time I plucked your petals!
Crimson Lightning!
Will Lilymon withstand
Myotismon's Crimson
Lightning, or will Mimi
lose her best friend?
Next time on Digimon Digital Monsters.