Pixiemon was unable to
fight off all of the Dark Masters,
but we were grateful to
him and his noble defeat.
Sometime later, we were on our way to what
we thought was a beach picnic,
but it turned out to be a track set up by
Scorpiomon.
With most of the group unconscious,
it was up to us to rescue them.
Xudomon and Lillimon allowed
us to get the gang out of the
hut just as Metal Seedramon
was blasting it into rubble.
We escaped into the ocean on Xudomon's
back.
At least, we thought we got away.
Xudomon and Lillimon's back.
Ding on Digital Monsters Change into
Digital Champions To Save the Digital
World Digimon, Digital Monsters,
Digimon are the kindergarten.
Digimon, Digital Monsters, Digimon are the
chumpkins.
Digimon, out your captain
of monsters, Digimon.
A river of power!
You're finished, you upstart
Digi-destined.
In a word, you're sucked!
Huh?
Who is that?
It's Waymon!
I
never thought I'd want to be fish food,
but we'll be safe in here.
Technically, it's
a...
You escaped this time, but you've escaped
for the last time!
Why did Waymon stick his spout in my
business and save the Digi-destined?
What are you doing here, Divermon?
We just came up for a little air!
Those Divermon, if it wasn't for their
striking fish attack, they'd be useless to me.
No matter.
Wherever those kids try to hide,
I'll find them.
I rule this ocean with
an iron hand, an iron
tail, and an iron
everything for that matter.
I'll catch them even with Waymon on their
side.
Well, don't just sit there treading water.
I told you, go find those kids!
Aye, aye, sir!
Thanks for saving us, Waymon!
Aw, don't mention it.
No, seriously, don't mention it.
I don't want it to get around.
Hey, guys!
We still have a problem.
How are we gonna be able to defeat the
Dark Masters?
I wonder how they took over the digital
world in the first place.
Do you remember, Waymon?
Of course I remember, Waymon.
Big fella.
Snappy dresser.
Oh, you mean the Dark Masters?
I don't know all the details, but soon
after the digital world began to warp,
Metal Seedramon began to take over the
ocean.
Darn!
Ow!
Oh, uh, sorry, Waymon.
Ty, don't get upset.
We'll fix things.
You're right.
We'll do it.
We've done it before, haven't we?
Yeah!
That's the attitude.
I'll find a safe place for you
outside of Metal Seedramon's
reach, even if I have to swim
to the far corners of the ocean.
By the way, did I mention I charge by the
mile?
No!
Can'ts land on their feet, but we still
need to eat.
It's Gatoman's wish for some fresh flying
fish, cause I'm a kitty.
A kitty kitty.
Whoa!
Oh!
That's great, Gatoman, but the rest of us
have to eat too.
Stand aside and watch how a pro does it.
Hmmm... Point ivy!
They're served!
Why'd you stop playing, Matt?
Oh, that song is just too depressing.
It always gives me the blues.
Besides, I can't stop thinking about the
Dark Masters.
They're different than any Digimon we've
ever faced before.
Well, I've analyzed the situation, and I
believe we can defeat them with WarGreymon.
Huh?
He's a Draymon Destroyer.
Draymon Destroyer?
Try speaking English.
Well, you see, the weapons on WarGreymon's
arms are the key.
They're especially effective
against Draymon-type
Digimon, hence the
phrase Draymon Destroyer.
With these devices, we might be able to
defeat the Dark Masters.
Izzy, you're a genius!
Draymon Destroyer, huh?
Agumon, you're gonna eat those Draymon
alive!
That's not what I had in mind.
Hey, Vicious!
Learned anything new in school?
We learned Divermon are in the area.
Hey, guys!
We got trouble!
I caught a whopper.
Look!
Wait, what are Divermon?
Oh, those are Meadowseedramon's henchmen.
It seems the fish have seen them about 200
miles behind us.
Huh?
What are we gonna do?
Well, we can't stay here.
They'll find us too easily.
I'm gonna dive.
Quick!
Everyone get inside me!
And don't mind the smell.
I had fish for lunch.
Ew!
Red Leader to Blue Leader.
Areas 13 through 18 are clear!
Gold Leader to Blue Leader.
Areas 23 and 24 are clear, too!
Listen, Bill, Sid, how many times do I
have to tell you guys?
There are just three of us!
You can call me Jim!
What are you guys?
Knock it off!
Sorry!
Do you smell something?
There's a set of digi-destined in the
current.
Either that, or there's a bad patch of
seaweed around here.
Ew!
This is my moment to shine!
Does my hair look alright?
Yeah!
You digi-destined fools!
You can swim, but you can't hide!
I was
taking catnapping and it woke me up.
I'll explain later.
Oh, come on!
You think I'm too brainless to understand?
Yes, but I'll tell you anyway.
Check it out!
What is it?
What did you do, Izzy?
What a cool screensaver.
It's not a screensaver.
What is it then?
I connected to Waymon's
hard drive and rerouted
all his sensory
information to my computer.
Rerouted?
In other words, what
you're seeing on the screen
is exactly what Waymon
is looking at right now.
Cool!
Like a submarine!
Oh boy!
I've always wanted to go in a submarine!
I think she's been out of the sea a little
too long.
Yeah, I hate square dances.
What's wrong, Kari?
It's my ears!
They're starting to hurt!
Nini, stop!
Be quiet!
Oh!
Hey, you know, my ears hurt a little too.
Me too!
Sorry, I dove a little too fast.
I'll fix the pressure now.
Hold on.
Oh!
Oh, that's better!
Well, I guess that's one way to equalize
the gas pressure.
By the way, you're excused.
What's that sound?
Huh?
It's getting louder!
Everyone, be quiet!
Sounds like Divermon!
Huh?
Sounds like they passed us.
We're not out of danger yet.
You'll have to be quiet a little longer.
Over there!
Hey, it's Waymon!
Oh, no!
They found us!
Red Leader, this is...
I mean, this is Phil.
I found Waymon!
He's in Area 51 on the ocean floor!
Great!
Keep an eye on it!
I'll tell the boss, and he can tell Metal
Seedramon!
Good news!
We found Waymon!
Hey!
What do we do now?
Oh, master of the ocean!
Attack!
Striking face!
Watch out!
The Divermon are attacking!
Hang on, everyone!
I've got an idea!
Where did all those bubbles come from?
Key!
I couldn't see where I was aiming!
Uh-oh!
You're squeezing me too hard!
Matt, you're squeezing me too hard!
Sorry, I guess we're all a little scared.
Ugh!
I hate this!
We're stuck in here and can't bite!
According to the audio sensors,
there are three more.
Behind us!
What is it, Waymon?
It's the enemy!
Don't let them get away!
Oh, they're gaining on us!
That's it!
I'm tired of running!
Come on, Waymon, let's go up to the
surface and fight!
Right!
Well... Let me try
one more thing.
Hopefully it'll work.
What do you mean, hopefully it'll work?
That's what the captain of the Titanic
said!
Striking fish!
And what if it doesn't work?
What's plan B?
I still think we should turn and fight.
I hope you know what you're doing,
Waymon.
What's he trying to do?
Waymon must be crazy trying to escape into
such a narrow space.
Stay with him!
No matter what!
You and the big whale!
Pull over!
It's no use!
We've got you tracked!
Oh no!
Don't catch us!
No!
A break!
That's gotta hurt!
Prodigious!
They can't take the water pressure!
That was Waymon's plan all along!
Waymon is built to handle pressure!
Unlike some of us!
Well, forgive me for not being a whale!
Boy, that was close!
I didn't know you had this kind of hidden
attack!
This is great!
But what are we gonna do now?
Yeah, we can't stay at the bottom of the
ocean forever!
I've got it!
Kari, come over here for a moment!
That was great!
That was good!
We've got it!
I've got it!
It was great!
You've got it!
Thanks for the help!
Sure.
The whistle was sort of like sonar.
We used the reverberations of the sound to
find a tunnel.
And there's one up ahead that should lead
us to land.
Cool.
Isn't that great, Waymon?
What?
I said, isn't that great?
I can't hear you.
Someone was whistling in my ear.
But there's a tunnel up ahead.
It should lead us to land.
Those fools think I don't know where
they're headed.
They're easier to figure out than a
two-piece jigsaw puzzle.
Enjoy playing submarine while you can.
Wow!
Pretty!
Aha!
A tunnel?
Yay!
We're safe!
I've got to get changed!
Huh?
Hug!
Yay!
Not again!
How can those fish heads be back?
They're not.
Be careful, everyone!
It's Metal Seedramon!
Yaaah!
Yaaaah!
Yaaaaah!
Is everybody okay?
Where… where are we?
The sun's so bright!
Smell that.
Fresh air.
I feel I've been underwater so long,
I might never take a bath again.
You mind telling me what's so funny?
It's Metal Seedramon!
How can it be?
It was only a matter of time before you
came up for air.
Now you're going down with the ship!
Everyone, hold on!
Should I?
Agumon gets their attention.
Let's cross over to the shore and prepare
ourselves for battle.
Aye, aye.
Uh, Goldmumon and I will stay here and
bring up the rear.
Joe, don't be such a coward.
Agumon!
Here I go!
Agumon, more Digimon!
Ha!
Digimon!
exotic araadrum.
Oh, poor promo!
Oh, Mom!
Ikakumon, thanks for everything,
but you can leave the rest to us.
What?
No tip?
Hurry and get out of here.
You're an easy target.
You're just too big.
Are you calling me fat?
I'm just Big Bone.
Striking fish!
I'm Blue Torpedo!
Ikakumon, quick!
Digiball!
Digiball 2!
Is everybody okay?
Round
of you, WarGreymon!
Say goodbye!
Is this really the end for WarGreymon?
Will the DigiDestined ever defeat the Dark
Masters?
Find out on the next Digimon Digital
Monsters.