My Otismon cut off all axes in and out of
town in order to find the Eighth Child.
I was being held captive along with a lot
of other people by the Bokemon.
To distract them, I
repeated the same chant that
Joe had used to make the
Bokemon lose their power.
That worked until Phantomon got wise and
destroyed my recording.
Then Dark Tyranomon showed up.
Little Pelmon turned over
a new leaf by digivolving
all the way to the
ultimate level, Lillimon.
Thankfully, she was able to return them to
a tame state.
And then, just to make things even worse,
My Otismon arrived.
Digimon!
Do you expect to beat me with geraniums?
Nightmare Claw!
No!
Get out of here, Sora, now!
But what about you, Mom?
Just go!
Oh...
Meteor win!
Christ, what are you waiting for?
Get away, you!
You think?
Poor Agumon, you're always getting beat
up.
What's that feeling?
You're getting good at this.
No way!
Way?
It's true.
I saw the whole thing.
That Creepazoid!
He's cut off the whole entire district.
Mm-hmm.
It's that crazy fog bank of his.
This is insane!
Holding thousands of people prisoner?
Just so he can find the eighth child!
And there's no telling what he'll do if he
doesn't find her.
Ah!
This is all my fault, isn't it?
Huh?
It's all happening because he's looking
for me, right?
Um... That's why Mom and Dad and
everybody are... Now, don't say that.
It's not your fault.
It's just the way things are.
It's called destiny.
Don't you worry.
I'm gonna bring Mom and Dad back home safe
and sound.
And your little buddy got him on,
too.
Hey, Matt!
Do me a favor and look after her till I
get back.
Uh, sure.
No problem.
Kari, I need you to be a big strong girl
for me while I'm away.
Okay.
Please be careful.
Hey!
Aren't I always?
Okay, it's 7.30.
Give me two hours.
If we don't make it back by then,
you guys get out of here.
Let's go, Agumon!
Okay!
Be careful, man!
See you soon!
Everything's gonna be all right!
I hope so.
Look!
Email from Jedi.
Greetings.
Salutations from cyberspace.
Oh, get to the point.
But this is no time for pleasantries.
You're in a tight spot, eh?
The first thing to do is put up a digital
barrier.
A digital what?
You're probably wondering what that is.
Well, download the program and I'll
explain.
If you can put it up in time, the digital
barrier will protect you.
Oh, the Bakuman are getting closer every
second.
Can't you go any faster, Izzy?
I'm trying!
I told Dad I need a quicker modem.
What's all the commotion?
Uh, we're sorry, but because
of fog conditions, no ferries
will be running to the
district until further notice.
What will we do in the meantime?
Please bear with us.
We're doing everything we can.
We just have to wait for the fog to lift.
I'm getting a bad feeling from this crowd.
I think maybe we should be going,
TK.
Hey, what do you suggest I do?
My family's in there!
My two!
Ah!
Please, stay calm!
You stay calm!
Yeah!
In cases of emergency, you might try
renting a private boat down at the harbor.
That's all I can suggest for now.
Mommy!
TK, where are you?
Ah!
Me!
Come on, come on!
It is time to go, Izzy.
We've got to get out of here.
No, believe it or not, we'll be safer
here.
What are you talking about, Izzy?
Those creatures will be at our door any
minute.
Trust me, I know what I'm doing.
Just give me another couple of minutes
here.
No!
Ah!
You are coming...
Wait, Mom, let me go!
Mom, you don't understand!
No, you don't understand.
This isn't the time.
Now will you please leave that computer
alone and come on?
Huh?
Dear, maybe he knows what he's doing.
Let's trust the boy.
All right?
The kids seem to know more about it than
we do.
You're right.
Go for it, son.
Hmm.
Trick-o-treat!
Done!
Digital barrier coming on now!
Ah!
That's funny.
I could've sworn.
Huh.
There's no one here.
Let's get moving!
It worked!
The digital barrier is in place!
Ah!
Oops!
Well, now that you know I can talk,
my name's Tensimon.
Pleased to make your acquaintance.
Oh, yeah!
Hmm.
Well, what are you gonna do with us?
Now what's going to happen?
Well, if I told you now it would just
simply ruin the surprise that's coming up!
In the meantime, why doesn't everybody
take a little nap?
It's not him.
Next.
It's not her.
Okay, next.
Beware, Gatomar.
Huh?
If you lie to me, I will simply destroy
them all!
Slow down!
I thought we were gonna be goners.
Joe!
Hey, TK.
I thought you'd be in town with the
others.
No, I was across the harbor when the power
went out.
So, we're both stuck out here while
everyone else is in there.
Yeah, who knows what Myotismon's planning
to do inside that evil blanket of fog.
Not so good.
All right, enough talk.
It's time for action.
We've gotta get there.
I know.
What'll we use to get across?
This is what?
The answer's right here.
Ta-da!
Gommamon!
Huh, rich head.
Are you ready to give it a try?
Sure, if you are.
TK!
Enderman!
Gommamon!
Digibrow to...
Pikakuma!
It's another one.
TK!
Uh-oh.
TK, what is that thing?
Get down from there.
Oh, it's okay, Mom.
By the way, this is a friend of mine.
His name's Joe.
It's very nice to meet you, ma'am.
I was in TK's woodworking class at summer
camp.
He nearly cut off one of my fingers.
But that's a whole different story.
I won't go into it right now.
Please stop.
I don't understand.
Don't worry.
The sauce slipped, but I missed him by a
mile.
He wasn't hurt.
That's not what I'm talking about.
So long, Mom.
I'll be back with Matt and Dad by
dinnertime!
Oh, no.
I've lost all of them now.
So, Izzy, if you're still
listening to me, that
means the digital
barrier must have worked.
Like a charm.
The fog barrier surrounding the entire
district is not a natural phenomenon.
It's my auto's mom's doing.
Well, duh.
Yeah, but what do we do about it?
You're probably wondering when I'm going
to tell you what you can do about it.
The source of the fog is here.
Attack its source, and you should be able
to bring down the barrier.
That's a TV station.
Let's get moving.
Aye, aye.
They might come back.
The safest thing you guys can do is to
stay right where you are.
In here, the digital barrier will protect
you.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
So long.
Wait!
You've grown so much, Izzy, and it's
obvious you can take care of yourself,
but you will always be my little boy.
So please, son, be careful.
I will.
Don't worry about me, Mom.
I'll make sure he's safe.
Never a moment's rest.
It's always seize her or grab him or go
terrorize that old lady.
I'm one poop spook.
Yeah!
Okay, stop talking!
Where are you keeping everyone,
you little creep?
Hey, Ty!
Zora!
So you're alright?
Hey, come back!
The convention center!
My Otis mom's holding the prisoner there!
Everyone in the whole district?
Yeah, including Mimi.
He's got your parents as well.
Huh?
I've about had it with this guy.
Okay, Zora, you go hook up with Matt.
He's in the warehouse by Aqua City.
Hm.
I'm on my way.
Let's go!
Aqua City, Bertrand!
Step on it!
The blood thickens.
The satellite dish won't respond!
Rats!
Come on, there's gotta be some way of
communicating with the outside world.
Whoa!
I had no idea TV stations were so big!
If I'm going to destroy it, I should
Digivolve.
Hold on for a minute.
For all we know, there might still be some
people inside.
We better check it out.
Hang in there, Mimi.
I'll get all of you out.
I promised Kari.
Wizardmon, huh?
Is that your Digimon's name?
No, no.
Mine is Gatomon.
Wizardmon is like her best friend,
but he's gone now.
He got captured by the bad Digimon.
It must be awful losing your best friend.
My mommy got captured by them too.
But not my daddy!
Do you think maybe my daddy got away?
He's alright, don't you think?
And mommy will be too, cause Tai's gonna
rescue her, right?
Uh, sure he will, Kari.
But let's remember, Tai's just one kid and
he's fighting hundreds.
I want mommy to come back!
Nice work.
Have some compassion.
Can't you see she's worried about her
family?
You're worried about yours, aren't you?
We're almost there.
Once we get past the bridge, we'll be
through the barrier.
Right!
Is your tummy rumbling or did I hear
something?
Huh?
Like what?
Wait, what's up there by the bridge?
I knew this was too easy.
That's Mega Seedramon.
The regular old Seedramon was bad enough.
But compared to this fully Digivol
version, it was just an angry guppy.
You'll
probably get blamed for this.
And they're giant!
T-Kai!
Oh!
Joe!
Just hang on tight to that and you'll be
alright.
I wouldn't want your mom to worry about
you.
You're just a kid.
I'm responsible for you.
Joe?
Joe!
Come
on!
Digivolve too!
He's the fully Digivolve version of
Ikakuman.
I was wondering when he'd finally show up.
Hey, Digimon!
Joe!
Huh?
He's cutting an opening in the fog bank.
I'm not Digimon!
I don't think so!
That's my Digimon!
Falcon's hammer!
It's
a head full, Pseudomon!
Okay, keep your eyes peeled.
Now, if I were a fog barrier generator,
where would I be?
Get back!
Back up!
We'll go the other way!
Not that way either!
They've got us surrounded!
Keep quiet.
Pretty boring, huh?
You said it!
Who are you?
I can't see anything in here.
I just hope we don't end up going in the
totally wrong direction.
Take me!
What?
To Garamon!
Please!
Huh?
Who's there?
I'm who's it?
Must find Garamon important.
Not so fast there!
Aren't you one of Myotismon's henchmen?
He looks beat up pretty bad.
Gotta give Garamon this.
Look, he's got somebody's crest.
Yes.
It belongs to...
the eighth child.
Call the eighth child!
Hmm.
Your brother should've been back by now.
Where is he?
Hey, is anyone there?
Sora, what's up?
Matt!
Thank goodness!
Myotismon's rounded up the whole district.
He's holding everybody at the convention
center.
So what do we do now?
I have a suggestion.
Huh?
You see, I've never
understood why the master is
wasting all this time
searching for the eighth child.
When it would be so much easier just to
destroy you all!
Say hello to Tuskmon and watch out.
Avoiding his razor sharp horns is no easy
tusk.
Sorry.
And here's the second member of our tag
team.
Naimon, a deadly praying mantis bigimon.
Which is so appropriate because you're all
about to become his prey.
Watch out!
Garumon, digiball, twin...
Garumon!
Don't worry, we can take these guys!
Twin sickos!
Kinda chokes you up, doesn't it?
Stop it!
No!
That's...
It's me you want.
I'm the eighth child.
If you'll just stop
hurting my friends, I'll
come with you quietly,
wherever you want.
What a refreshingly helpful attitude.
It's a deal.
Kari!
Oh no, Matt!
What are we going to do?
I don't know!
Ty is gonna be so mad at me!
Will the Digi-Destined find Kari before
it's too late?
Find out on the next Digimon Digital
Monsters.