Leomon and Ogremon decided to stop fighting
each other and face Metal Edemon together.
Meanwhile, the rest of the gang had their
own problems with Puppetmon.
But thanks to a brief
appearance by Matt and
Metal Garurumon, he
finally got his strings cut.
Risking all the same meme, Saber Leomon
threw himself in front of a vicious blast.
I did Juval to Zootomon and
used my Vulcan's hammer
to put a serious dent in
Metal Edemon's armor.
We thought Leomon would return to a
Digi-Egg, but Primary Village was poisoned
by evil, and it'll stay that way until all
of the Dark Masters are defeated.
DIGIMON!
DIGI-ON!
DIGI-MON!
DIG
This road has to be going somewhere,
right?
Don't count on it!
Nothing is certain in the Digi-world!
Do you have a furball, Kari?
No, silly.
I'm okay.
One thing is certain, only a cactus could
love this place.
She has to stay out of
the sun, and we've got
to find a way to get
her fever down, soon.
Don't worry, I won't leave you.
Yeah... How come you didn't
say something before now, Kari?
If we'd known sooner, we could have rested
until you felt better.
You mad?
I didn't want to slow everyone down.
Oh, I'm not mad.
I wasn't paying attention.
We probably shouldn't have even brought
her along.
Huh?
What are you talking about?
We had to bring her.
We need her if we want to save the
Digi-world.
She's one of the Digi-destined.
Have you forgotten that?
Not at all, but her being sick?
We should have left her someplace safe.
We should have split up so someone could
take care of her while the others looked.
Split up?
Ty, this isn't like you.
I'm just a little... worried about her.
It's all a part of what I do to be a good
leader, Izzy.
Uh, yeah, but... Izzy, I found it!
Uh... Huh?
We're saved!
Look right up ahead!
You wanted civilization?
Well, it doesn't get more civilized than
this!
Whoa!
Is that America?
Do you think they have a bathroom?
Well, that's New York City!
But that isn't!
That's Rome!
We studied it in geography, and up there,
that's the Arc de Triomphe in Paris!
They're all smooshed together!
It's like that theme park in Florida!
Except that this place is deserted.
Look, there's not a sign of life anywhere!
Uh... Hey, Izzy!
Kari's getting worse!
Let's find some place to land!
Oh, yeah, right!
Uh...
This looks like a nice quiet spot.
These cupboards are empty!
There's not even a speck of food!
Hey!
This one you're looking for?
Oh, right!
Way to go!
What is it, Agumon?
Did you find some aspirin?
Yeah, this ought to do the trick!
It's empty!
Just like everything else!
This place is weird!
Ty, humans aren't supposed to be this
color, are they?
Mm-mm.
Well?
I'm afraid to leave in case something
happens.
But she needs medicine.
She's stable, I think.
All we can do now is hope her fever breaks
soon.
It will!
Least I know I'm leaving her in good hands
with you!
Don't worry.
Just be careful.
Listen, Ty!
I wanna come with you!
I won't get in the way!
Honest!
No way!
You're my last line of defense!
What if the Dark Masters come,
huh?
I need you here to look after the others!
You can count on me!
Don't worry!
I'm on the job!
Yeah!
Leave it to us!
I knew I could count on you guys!
This place is deserted, but I still get
the feeling we're being followed.
Isn't that strange?
Izzy, what do you think you're doing?
Aha!
This is the digital age, Ty.
There are a lot simpler ways of finding
things now.
Good!
I was beginning to get a crab in my wings!
I knew it!
There's an online map of the city!
Izzy, you're a genius!
Nice going!
Okay, now I'll search for hospitals and
pharmacies.
Jackpot, take your pick!
This one's the closest.
Let's go!
Hey, wait for me!
I gotta unplug myself!
They have logged all up!
Yes!
My Lord Machinedraman, sir!
They've accessed maps and things for
hospitals and pharmacies!
Hi-o!
And you're waiting for what?
Show me those locations.
Right away, sir!
There are, uh... One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven!
Twelve of them!
Let me put this in words you can
understand.
Send units to all twelve locations and
blow them up!
Oh, I get it now!
Blow them up!
Yes, sir!
Consider it already done, my Lord.
The little fools have swallowed the bait.
Now it is time to sprint to the trap.
Finally!
It was getting a little stuffy!
No wonder this hospital's so clean.
There's no sick people.
Hello?
Do you have any idea what you've done?
Hey, over here!
I found the pharmacy!
There's a lot of medicine, all right.
But how do we know what to use for Kari's
fever?
Strange as it sounds, I wish Joe were
here.
He might know what these are.
His father's a doctor.
That's a doctor's kid for you.
There's never one around when you need
him.
Huh?
Hold on!
I can patch into the hospital's computer!
As he shoots, he scores!
Fever reduction.
Children.
Sir!
There they are, sir!
Ha-ha!
The network is being accessed from inside
Target Four, Master Sir!
Then wouldn't it be a
good idea to have all forces
converge on their target
and prepare to attack?
Well, a brilliant idea, my lord,
sir!
After you, Megatramon!
Oh, no!
After you!
Hey, Izzy!
You sure that's the right stuff?
It's the safest children's aspirin!
Good job!
Then let's get back!
Fire!
Ah!
Hey, let's beat it!
Lucky we're in a hospital, cause it looks
like we might need one!
What are they?
Nekanorimon!
Evil robots with one job!
Blasting Digimon!
I suggest we get out of here, and fast!
Target in range!
Bane!
Twin Beings!
Ahhhh!
Tankmon!
An armor-plated bully with a sneeze like a
cannon!
If you think the other guys are bad, these
creeps have more firepower than a volcano!
I thought we lost them!
How did they find us so quickly?
Really?
One of them must have been following us
and saw us come in here.
Big, Kari needs us to get back pronto.
Target in range.
Twin beam.
Hyper cannon!
Look out!
Duck!
Come on!
What
are they getting tired of that sound?
Where are they going to call it quits and
go home?
We don't have time for this.
I'm going to go down there and take care
of them.
No, wait!
Huh?
Those rolling arsenals are just waiting
for us.
We show ourselves and they'll go
ballistic.
So, we just hide here all day,
is that it?
Those machines are the only
things moving out there, so a
map of the city's traffic flow
will show us where they are.
Then it's just a question of plotting the
best course to avoid them.
Yeah, just might work.
Of course it'll work.
You see?
There.
I've pinpointed every one of them.
Good job, Izzy.
Excuse me, your metal men.
They are accessing
the network again, but
the access point is
relocated to Sector B-17.
Then relay those coordinates to all forces
and attack.
Now it's about time!
Inconceivable!
Incon what?
What now?
The machines!
Every one of them rotated in sync and now
they're heading our way!
Huh?
Of course!
They're zeroing in on my computer
connection!
Incoming!
What?
Ah!
Digimon!
Digivol wolf monsters!
Digimon now they're leurs jego hocks!
Digimon!
The monsters, the monsters are the
champions.
Krakumal!
Digiball!
Raymon!
Digimon?
Nobububub!
Get out of here!
The plot sickens.
I had such high hopes that these little
ones would put on them all.
Entertaining show.
But this... really, it's too tiresome!
Can we just get this over with and get
onto something a little less tedious?
There's no escape from Machine Drummond!
He's designed for total annihilation.
It's only a matter of time now before he
catches them.
And then the game is over.
Ah, it's not fair that that overgrown can
opener gets all the fun.
When I was so looking forward to playing
with them myself.
Farewell!
Farewell, Little ones!
Whoa!
Digimon!
Dig Liberal Monster!
Digimon Gnarla!
擊 cards!
Digimon!
Free sh醒
Digimon, into Ultimates.
Digimon, you're hostile.
I'm not the champions.
Metal dream!
Digimon, hang on!
Good news.
Nave escaped again, my lord, sir.
And yet you're still here.
It's all my fault.
I was giving away our location every time
I logged on with my computer.
How could I have not thought of that
before?
Quick question!
Now we're stuck here!
Meanwhile, Kari's getting sicker and
sicker!
Because of you!
Stop it, Ty!
What's come over you?
Huh?
I'm sorry, Izzy.
Hey, Ty, this isn't your normal behavior.
It's Kari.
She almost died once before because of me.
Huh?
It happened when she was four or five,
just a little kid.
She stayed home from kindergarten one day
because she was sick.
I mean, I knew she
was sick, but all I could
think about on the way
home was playing soccer.
Hey, I'm home.
I wanted to go out and play, but I didn't
want to leave her by herself.
So I took her outside with me.
She seemed okay.
Really, she did.
I didn't want to do this.
Now watch me.
Just like that.
No, that's not right.
Huh?
Kari?
Kari!
What could you have been thinking?
You knew she was sick!
She ended up with pneumonia or something.
She almost didn't make it.
But what really kills
me is what she said
when they brought her
home from the hospital.
The first words out of her mouth.
Ty, I'm sorry I can't kick the ball very
good.
You'll probably never want to play with me
again.
That's her.
That's Kari.
She never thinks about herself.
It doesn't matter if she feels bad or
she's bummed out about other stuff.
She's always worried about the other kids.
She wouldn't be sick.
She'd be just fine if she never came to
this stupid place.
But she came because she knew that we
needed her help.
She never thought about what she wanted.
She never does.
Because she cares.
She's a kid.
I'm her big brother.
I'm supposed to look after her and protect
her and think of what's best for her.
That's what I'm supposed to do!
Oh, Ty.
Okay, it would be ridiculous to try to
break through them.
But maybe we can use their own
surveillance techniques against them.
You're not going online again,
are you?
Yes, but this time I know what I'm doing.
I've got a program that'll throw them off
our trail.
I'm going to mask our access point.
It's a little trick a computer programmer
taught me once.
There they are again!
Oh!
Um, boss!
There are now dozens of access points all
over the map!
Does this mean what I think it does,
my lord sir?
That you have the brains of our tin can?
What are those?
Those are the enemy Digimon.
They're not moving.
That's because the program worked and they
don't have a clue where to look for us.
Pro-digis!
Well, what are we waiting for?
Let's get going!
I'm bored with this game of cat and mouse.
Initiate plan, eliminate.
Uh, eliminate?
How about eliminate?
Are you actually questioning me?
Initiate plan, eliminate.
Now!
No sir!
Yes sir!
Attention!
Initiate plan, eliminate!
I'm glad you agree.
Fire at will.
Can I blow something up?
I don't know.
Can you?
Now we're in for it.
Dark side attack!
And
what a waste of ammo.
They're way off.
I don't think they're shooting at us.
Huh?
No, it can't be!
Involved flying fiend with devastating
destructive powers.
Those missiles of his can level a city
block in the blink of an eye.
The other one's Gigadramon.
If anything, he's more powerful than his
buddy.
Believe me, if these
guys were shooting at us,
we wouldn't still be
here talking about it.
Looks like my plan may have backfired on
us.
How do you figure that?
It appears they've decided searching for
us is too much trouble.
So instead, they're just gonna level the
whole city and everybody in it.
You've gotta be kidding.
That's it for Sexus A and B.
What a mess!
Megadramon and Gigadramon have begun
operations in sectors C and D.
Children sneaky...
Soon there will be no place left to hide
and this game will abruptly end.
Kari!
Safe and sound.
Everything's okay.
We're back, Kari!
The building's gone!
No!
No way!
It can't be!
Kari!
Me!
Here comes one more!
Oh no, look out!
Angemon!
But that means...
Hey, what's up?
You look tired!
TK!
Biomon!
And the others!
Kari, you're okay!
Actually, you look better than okay.
When we saw them bombing buildings,
we thought we'd better get out.
And all the way, I took care of them like
you said.
I never doubted you.
Ah!
Machine Dramon!
You can't rely on scrap metal if you want
the job done right.
Take cover, everybody!
That's right.
Scurry away.
Ask any Redcatcher.
The chase is part of the fun.
Gigacannon!
Something
like a little old-sailed destruction to
end a hard day's work.
Goodbye, DigiDestined!
Hurry!
Has Machinedramon succeeded in destroying
the DigiDestined?
Don't miss the next Digimon Digital
Monsters!