Metal Seedramon had
followed us from the underwater
channels and was now in
a fierce battle with our Digis.
In the midst of all of
it, he released his river
of power and hit Waymon
with a devastating blast.
Poor Graymon had no
other choice but to use his
Terra Force to finally put
an end to Metal Seedramon.
Sadly, our friend Waymon was reconfigured
as well.
As the ocean started
to disappear, we took it
as a sign that things
might get back to normal.
The odds of that happening anytime soon?
Not good.
Digimon are the champions!
Matt, where are you?
I'm worried.
What do you think could have happened to
him, Ty?
Matt's a big boy.
He could take care of himself.
Well, wait a minute.
What if he was kidnapped by Puppet Mod?
Yeah, he might have been.
Or something worse.
No, it wasn't anything like that.
Huh?
What?
How do you know?
Come on, let's go.
Huh?
What, he just walked away?
And you didn't even try to stop him?
Well, no.
Was I supposed to?
I mean, I thought he was just gonna go use
the bushes.
Or something.
Huh.
This is weird.
I mean, it's one thing if he was
kidnapped.
But why would he just disappear on us like
this?
I'll say.
He's been gone way too long for just a
potty break.
Wait a minute.
Is it just me, or has Matt been kind of
strange lately?
He has been acting a little hustler.
Remember when Gabumon had that digivolving
problem?
Yeah, I bet there's a connection.
Huh?
Kari, what is it?
I thought I heard a voice out there.
A voice?
Was it Matt?
I don't hear anything.
Come on, Kari, don't you start losing it
too.
He couldn't be very far away, you know.
Maybe we should look for him.
Yeah, I suppose.
Okay guys, let's go.
Come
on.
It wasn't Matt's voice I heard.
Whose was it?
Matt, come on.
I'm all for exercise, but I'm really not
built for long distances.
Matt, where are we going?
Just away.
I need some space.
Oh, the poor little kid needs a little
space.
Someplace far away from his nice little
friends and closer than me.
I agree completely.
I'm not waiting.
I'll put him out of his misery.
Those Digi-Dustin kids really bug me.
Wait a minute, Puppetmon.
I have a better idea.
You can take care of those
other Digi-Dustin children
if you want to, but as for
this one, leave him to me.
I'll have him climbing up a tree before
I'm through with him.
You ever felt like a fifth wheel,
Gabumon?
That's what I feel like.
All this time, I thought I had like a
purpose, you know?
To look out for my little brother.
I thought TK wouldn't be able to survive
without me watching over him.
But suddenly, it's like he's growing up.
He doesn't need me anymore.
And it's not just him.
It's everybody, man.
I mean, when I think of Tai
and Mimi and Sora and the
others, this place has
changed them for the better.
They're stronger now.
It's almost like they've digivolved or
something.
But you see, the problem is, I haven't.
I'm still stuck in the same place.
I haven't changed a bit.
You may not see it, Matt, but you've
changed a lot.
Oh, please, Gabumon, give me a break.
I'm the same jerk I always was.
Hey, come on.
It'll never happen.
Not this way.
I finally got it figured out.
If I'm ever gonna change, I have to do it
on my own.
On my own.
The others can't help me.
Well, well, well.
Look what we've got here.
Greetings, nature lovers.
What?
You mean you've never seen a talking tree?
Not many.
Be careful.
That's Cherrymon, Lord of the Forest.
And the best reason for the existence of
termites.
Stop right there or I'll turn you into
toothpick.
You really shouldn't be that rude.
Calm down.
My fighting days are over.
I only want to talk with you.
In fact, you might even say I've turned
over a new leaf.
It's no use.
I'm getting nothing.
For some reason, the digivices aren't
working in this forest.
You know, I'm not so sure we should be
trying to find him.
Everyone needs to be alone sometimes.
I should know.
I'm not gonna let him break up this team.
We're gonna find him whether he wants us
to or not.
We're always walking around searching for
someone.
I've never done so much walking in my
life.
Yeah, it's disgusting.
My calves are starting to look like a
bodybuilder's.
Like a what?
Oh, Mimi.
Yoo-hoo!
Huh?
Puppet Mod?
Hi, everybody.
Hey, TK.
Did you miss me?
No, not at all.
And I'm not gonna play with you anymore,
either.
No?
Well, fine.
You're not a lot of fun, anyway.
Front and center, everybody.
Yes, sir!
Thank you.
Oh, Garbage Mod!
They're as tough as they are mean.
And they don't smell very good,
either.
Junk Tuckers ready!
Aim, fire!
I won't budge!
Let's let them do the running for it!
Boing, boing!
Huh?
Mimi, come on!
Yeah, good idea!
I must be nuts!
I touched that stuff!
No offense, but even if I felt like
talking, it wouldn't be to a tree.
See you around.
Hey, what's the idea?
Young man, didn't anyone ever tell you you
should listen to your elders?
Or was it Redwood you should listen to?
I can never quite get those two straight.
But anyway, I digress.
So, you're still stuck in the same place.
Still the same old jerk you always were.
Surprised, huh?
I know all about it.
Must be tough being in such a rut.
You've been spying on me, huh?
Listen to me, kid.
I don't need to spy
because there's nothing that
happens in this forest
that I don't know about.
Huh.
Alright then, if you're so smart,
what am I supposed to do?
Tell me that!
Ah, simple as that, eh?
Kids, you want all the answers just handed
to you on a mahogany platter.
But you never want to
do the hard work of looking
deep within yourself where
all the answers truly lie.
Let's go!
Don't you listen to that talking firewood,
Matt!
Come on!
That's right, go on!
But you'll never learn how to change!
You'll always be what you are right now!
I want to change!
Yes, of course, but are you really ready?
After all, change isn't always a pleasant
thing.
You might find out a few things that you
wish you hadn't.
I'm ready.
More than ready.
Enough talking, big guy!
If you've got some answers, let's see him!
He fell for it like an overripe fig.
Alright, kid, I'll help you out.
First off, you're gonna have to defeat
your rival.
My rival?
There!
In that lake, you will see
the face of the one who is
preventing you from becoming
as strong as you could be.
Where are you going?
I know it sounds pretty bogus,
but might as well look.
Listen, Matt.
You don't really believe him, do you?
Ty?
Come on!
What kind of trick is this?
Don't you know that wherever you go,
there will always be garbage?
Okay, ready guys?
Make a mess!
Way to go!
That trash is thrashed!
We're going home!
Sike!
Look behind you!
It's trash!
Look out!
Here's mud in your eyes!
No!
Jolt Chaker!
Nightmare!
Twice as nice!
Oh!
Trash that petunia!
That chick is heavier than she works!
Flour, ten!
All right!
Finish him off!
Digimon!
Digimon monsters, Digimon are the jump
guns!
Digimon rolls!
Digimon rolls too!
Metal Draymon!
Digimon!
Digimon monsters, Digimon are the jump
guns!
Digimon!
Monster friends too!
Boys and girls!
Digimon!
Yeah!
Behold!
The face of your rival!
So you're saying... I
have to fight Tai, is that it?
Nice try, Foliage Face!
You had me going there!
But you'll have to do better than that!
I had nothing to do with it!
The lake of truth reflects only what is in
a person's heart, hence the name!
You gotta be kidding!
Sorry kid, it's never wrong.
That right?
Well I've got news for you, it's off this
time!
Way off!
Well you can argue
with me all you want, but
you're really only
arguing with yourself.
It's about time you face the truth!
The one you call Tai is your leader,
everything he says you do, everywhere he
goes you follow, and yet in
your heart you resent it because
you know you're just as
qualified to be the boss as he is!
Stop it!
Who do you think you are?
Huh?
Who died and left you in charge of the
world?
Huh?
What do you mean?
I've just about had it!
Do not be ashamed of your resentment,
do not hide it, embrace it!
For in your anger lies your strength!
Only when you recognize that will you at
last be free to grow, to change!
So face your rival and prove you are his
equal, or better, by defeating him!
Don't listen!
He's just trying to cause trouble!
He's playing games with your mind!
It's all part of some kind of trap!
Tai is your friend!
Huh?
He's my friend, yeah!
He may not always act
like it, but... He's right!
Tai's my friend!
You don't fight your friends!
Friends?
Ha!
Now that's a good one!
You don't even believe that such a thing
really exists!
Huh?
Not in your heart of hearts, anyway!
Hit the nail on the head, didn't I?
What's he mean?
Friendship.
Loyalty.
Comrades.
Fine sounding words.
But that's all they are.
Words.
Delusions.
And you're wise enough to see that now.
You'll know that ultimately, the only
person you can depend on is yourself.
Isn't that right, Matt?
He's wrong!
Isn't he?
I don't know.
I... I don't know.
You don't?
Alright then!
That's enough moping around for now!
Look kids, stop staring at your shoes!
The choice in front of you is simple!
Whoa, if you'll truly
want a change to reach
your full potential,
you must defeat Tai!
It's either that or be
content to live your
life following in the
shadows of him forever.
What a choice!
What do I do?
Oh, what do I do?
Oh, that's a laugh.
Wouldn't you know that my crest had to be
the crest of friendship?
Matt!
There's one thing he's right about.
Whatever you're going to do, do it!
But do what?
You've got to hear what
your own conscience
is telling you and not
listen to anybody else.
Not Tai or Cherrymon or me.
You've got to have faith in yourself,
Matt!
What if I make the wrong decision?
I know that whatever it is, it'll be the
right one.
Because I have faith in you.
And whichever path you take, I'll be there
with you.
You mean that?
You do have a friend.
Never forget that.
I'll always be there, Matt, no matter
what.
Ah, Bulmon...
Digivolve 2!
Ready!
Lead the way!
Right.
Ha ha!
Yeah, I think that went rather well.
Still, I'm surprised by the strength of
the bond between them.
It took every trick I had to undermine it.
If Puppetmon isn't careful, this game
could still be lost.
I meant what I said, Matt.
Cherrymon was wrong.
Friendship, loyalty, they're more than
just words.
They're real.
And they matter.
I'm going to prove it to you.
Splattering me with their gunk.
Those fucking brains will pay for this.
There you are.
The plan went perfectly, just as I
thought.
Plan?
What plan?
You should have seen it.
I played that trusting sap like a violin.
He's going to do our dirty work for us,
Puppetmon.
Well, sounds like a plan.
Any second now, we'll hear
the sounds of WarGreymon
and MetalGaruramon
locked in mortal combat.
You're serious?
Oh, yeah.
With any luck, they'll destroy each other.
With the two strongest Digimon out of the
way, the rest will fall like rotten fruit.
Mortal combat?
This I've got to see.
Let's go.
What are we waiting for?
Wait a minute.
We've got to be careful.
The Digidestined are strong.
Stronger than I suspected.
And to underestimate them could be
disastrous.
What?
Are you saying I might lose?
I'm only saying that I think you should
take them seriously.
There's something about them.
Something?
Hmm.
You mean like something I might be
missing?
Well, not totally.
I have everything I need to take care of
you.
Puppet, come on!
Out of the horror!
Huh?
Man, that kind of negative attitude really
brings me down.
Okay, okay!
I know what I'm meeting you with!
I surrender!
Just kidding!
Crash day!
Everybody in the can!
If you're lucky, you'll
get re- My smooth claw!
Matt, you're back!
Better late than never!
Where you been, buddy?
Thanks for saving our next, but did you
have to cut it that close?
What's he doing?
Hey, what is this?
What do you think?
It's a challenge!
You might want to digivolve and fast!
What have you been eating out there in the
forest?
You want to fight me?
This is insane!
Matt, what's going on?
Is this some kind of joke?
Matt, I don't know what he's doing,
but call him off now!
No, Ty.
I won't.
What did you say?
You won't?
I'm warning you!
Hurry up and digivolve into WarGreymon
because I won't miss next time!
I think he really means it!
Well, time's running out, Argumon!
Ty, stop him!
I wish I could, but there's only one
person who can stop him!
Will Matt succeed in destroying the
DigiDestined from within?
Find out next time on Digimon Digital
Monsters!