We finally found TK, and just in time,
too.
Later, Devamon channeled his power and
became enormous.
No matter how many times they tried,
our Digimon couldn't stop him.
That's when the incredible happened.
Patamon finally digivolved
into Angemon, and
using all of his energy,
defeated Devamon.
With all of his strength gone, Angemon
returned to the youngest stage, a Digi-Egg.
With Devamon gone, File Island began to
rebuild itself.
I'm just glad we're all back together
again.
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Change into Digital Champions 2!
Save the digital world!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Digimon!
After the Digimon defeated Devamon,
we thought the worst was over.
And then, a mysterious being appeared
before us.
So, you children are the Digi-destined.
You must be strong to have defeated
Devimon.
Who are you?
Are you a friend of Devimon's?
Fear not, for I am a friend to all,
and yet I am a friend to none.
I can't believe it.
There are actually other humans besides us
in this world.
I am human, and yet I am not human.
This is confusing.
No, my name is Jani.
I couldn't send you this transmission
during your battle with Devimon,
but now the lines are clear and only ten
cents a minute.
Well, who are you?
And just where are you?
I am speaking to you
far away from Fire Island,
across the ocean on
the continent of Surba.
Talk about a long-distance call.
How long have you been here?
Since before the beginning until after the
end.
Are you the one who got us stuck here in
the digital world?
It was not I.
Then who was it?
It was... I don't know.
But Mr. Jani, sir, do you know what we need
to do so we can all get back home again?
No, I don't.
Boy, you're a regular fountain of
information, aren't you?
I'm sorry I can't help you, but you can be
of help to me.
How?
Please come to Surba and defeat our
enemies.
As the Digidists and I have faith in all
of you.
That's crazy when we don't know your exact
location.
Good point.
I forgot you're from out of town.
Let me create a map for you on your
computer.
Huh?
What?
What if your enemies are humongazoid?
Do you think we can beat anything tougher
than Debamon?
Not presently, but
if your Digimon can
digivolve once more,
you might be able to do it.
So we can digivolve even more?
But you'll need something special to do
it.
If you have the tags and crests, your Digimon
will be able to digivolve even further.
Please tell us where we can find these
tags and crests.
When the crests are
scattered about, you can
locate them all throughout
the continent of Surba.
And the tags were secretly sealed away
somewhere by Debamon.
Oh no, Debamon, oh no!
You must come!
What's going on?
Hey!
Come, quickly!
I'll be waiting!
I'm savored!
He's gone!
What was that?
Jedi's transmission ended rather abruptly.
Well, at least he was able to send the map
through before he got cut off.
I hope he's alright.
What's our next move going to be?
Huh.
I've got a foolproof plan.
First we'll eat something, and after that
I'm open to suggestions.
That was delicious!
I was so hungry!
Now that my stomach is full, I'm ready for
lunch!
TK?
Oh, I was just wishing
my Digi-Egg would
hurry up and hatch
already so I could grow up!
Don't sweat it, little bro.
When your Digimon hatches, it'll be the
coolest one yet!
Exactly!
Okay, everyone.
Now that we've stuffed our faces,
what are we gonna do next?
You know what's next.
We have to go to Server to save Jedi from
his enemies.
Well, according to my
calculations of longitude and
latitude, I'd say Server is
quite some distance from here.
I can't even swim across the bathtub,
let alone an ocean!
I'll never make it!
Why do we have to go, anyway?
What I mean is, Devamon's gone from the
island.
The Black Gears have disappeared,
too!
We've been once around the island, so
we pretty much know where everything is.
We wouldn't have to worry about food or
water.
What are you saying?
Why should we believe what this weirdo
Jedi guy says?
What I mean is, how do we even know that
this place Server really exists?
What are you thinking?
If we hang around here, guys, we'll never
get back home!
I don't know, guys.
Devamon almost got us.
Maybe we shouldn't go.
At least we know what we're up against
over here.
And even if we wanted to go, what mode of
transportation could we utilize?
We don't even know what the fashions are
like on Server.
Mm-hmm.
Maybe we should stay here a while longer
and think this through.
What's with you, man?
Let's go!
Huh?
TK?
We don't know what kind of danger will be
waiting for us, but let's see!
I'm sure Angemon would say the same thing
if he were still around.
So I'm going!
We'll go, too!
If we have the tags and crests,
we'll be able to digivolve again, right?
Once we transform into our new shapes,
we'll be able to protect you for sure!
Utamon!
Sora, so what do you say?
Our chances for success are extremely
high!
Come on, Mimi!
I'll bet you we'll be the prettiest
flowers on all of Server!
Don't worry about me!
I'll swim to Server!
Come on!
Let's do it!
Let's go!
Count me in!
K, I'll go!
I'm convinced!
Well, I'm not staying by myself!
I'll go, too!
All right, it's unanimous!
That's great!
It's decided!
We're going to Server!
Yay!
Peppa Bread!
Blue Blaster!
At our current rate, it'll take us forever
to build a raft!
Don't worry about it, Izzy.
It's not like we're in any kind of hurry.
Huh?
Leomon!
So I heard you are all going to Server.
How did you know?
Oh, you know us monsters.
We all love to gossip.
I thought I'd see if you needed some help
with anything.
You mean you'll really help us?
I've got some friends who want to help as
well.
Mmm!
Elok Mon!
Mojomon and Sitarumon, too!
Yeah!
Hi!
What's up?
Mojomon!
Fist of the Beast King!
Wow, Leomon!
So
dynamically designed.
I think I'm getting seasick already.
Get a grip, Joe.
It'll have to do.
Believe me, that raft is strong enough to
get you across the ocean.
Thanks, Leomon.
We never could have done it without your
help.
Oh!
What is it?
Hi!
Get your egg!
You hatched!
Boyo!
Boyo Mon!
How cute!
That's great!
Yay!
He did it!
Boyo Mon is a jellyfish-type Digimon of
few words.
But, if his friends are in trouble,
he is ready for action!
This is goodbye.
And good luck!
Thanks!
Goodbye!
So we sailed away from File Island,
where we had some really cool adventures.
When we had to survive on our own,
we grew up very fast.
Except Joe.
He just threw up very fast.
But he came around, too.
We don't know what's
waiting for us on the other
side of the ocean, but
we'll face it as a team!
I can't see anything.
I wonder how much longer this trip will
take.
Chill out, Joe.
We just left.
The salt air is killing my sinuses, and
we've only got enough food for two weeks.
If we run out of food, we'll catch some
fish.
Well, the one good thing is, this is
beautiful weather for sailing.
So good!
I didn't calculate these waves being so
rough.
Hey, hey!
Boyomon!
What?
Oh!
Oh, Boyomon, be careful!
Look!
Tidal Wave!
That had to be 12 feet tall!
18.3 to be exact!
Was that another boat that caused that
wave?
There's no boat that can do that!
An island!
Waymon is a giant Digimon who lives in the
deep oceans of the digital world.
Its jet arrows are unbelievable!
It was massive!
A Waymon can sometimes be fierce, but
I've never seen one act this aggressive!
I hope we don't give him a sore throat!
Technically, it's not the throat, it's the
esophagus that leads to the stomach!
He thinks we're fast food!
Oh, he really did eat us!
Sooner or later, this has to lead to an
exit!
It does, but you don't want to go there!
This is damaging my hair all the way to
the roots!
Here's my roots?
You're a plant!
What is that gross gooey junk?
Maybe they're anybody's!
They're attacking us because they think
we're germs or something!
Finally, we've stopped!
Is everyone okay?
Where are we?
Anatomically speaking, this would be the
stomach.
The stomach?
Isn't that where food goes after it's
chewed up?
Yeah!
Gastric juice!
What?!
It's the acid in the stomach that
dissolves the food!
We're melting!
Don't let it get on you!
We better get out of here before we give
him a major ulcer!
Ty, look up there!
It's a black gear!
That's why Waymon was acting so
aggressive!
Joe, do something to help!
Why me?
Someone can climb on these!
Poison Ivy!
Right!
I'll do it!
Okay, I destroyed it!
Are you okay?
Yeah... Somehow
we got out of there!
Yeah... Waymon, talk to me!
You're okay!
Again!
Sorry about that!
I must have had a tummy ache or something!
It's okay!
We all know it wasn't your fault!
That's right!
It was the black gear inside you!
Those black gears are rude!
I'll bet that's the last one!
I bet you're wrong!
Thanks, kids!
I owe you one!
Don't mention it, Waymon!
It was our pleasure!
By the way, do you know how far it is to
serve her?
Yes, it would take me five days!
Make that three and a half without
traffic!
Great!
Our raft's broken!
Are you going to serve her?
Yeah, we were trying to!
I'll take you there myself!
It's not every day your lunch saves your
life!
Really?
Yay!
All right!
There!
This is great!
This sure is a whole lot faster and
smoother than that raft!
Which means I won't get seasick!
Now if we only knew
where we could find those
tags and those crests that
Devamon hid somewhere!
Did you say Devamon?
Yeah, do you know him?
Well, I don't know anything about tags or
crests.
But a while ago, Devamon hid something
deep at the bottom of the ocean.
Can you tell us where?
It's on the way to server.
You can all ride inside me and I'll take
you there.
But no tickling!
I'm so out of shape, I have to rest here
for a while.
I gotta drop a couple of thousand pounds.
Thanks, Waymon!
What's that?
A convenience store.
Huh?
What is it?
Jumajumaj!
Jumajumaj lives deep inside the earth
drilling tunnels.
He uses his iron drill spin and crusher
bone to wipe out his enemies.
Oh!
A black gear!
I knew that couldn't have been the last
black gear.
It is Lord Devamon's will that no one
shall pass!
Ty, leave this to us Digimon.
You try to find the tags.
I got it!
Ty, you think that drill scares us?
Think again!
Digimon!
Now's our chance!
Come
on, you've got him down!
Get him!
Heartful torpedo!
I think it's time I join the battle!
Digimon!
Digimon Digiball 2!
Yeah!
Crusher Bull!
Kabuterimon, aim for the black gear!
Electro Shocker!
Yeah!
Can't stay in this store!
What's in the box?
Please forgive me for attacking you.
Pardon me, do you know where the tags are?
The tags should be in the convenience
store, next to the jerky.
The tags!
Just like the ones Jedi showed us during
his transmission.
How pretty!
Remember what Jedi told us, you guys.
The crests are scattered throughout the
continent of Server.
And if we get both the tags and the crests,
we'll all be able to digivolve once again.
Then we'll just have to go out there and
find the crests!
The F But it's characteristics that you
really had to go out there.
But it was a little bit odd.
It's a little bit wait.
We'll see the back of it and that's the
last one.
It's a輕ersis!