Mimi and I made our way to Primary
Village, where we found Electmon,
who also resolved to join our ragtag
group.
Knowing Mimi would now be safe,
I made the same decision as Matt,
to go find out what kind
of person I am, and make
sure I can be counted
on when the time arrives.
Meanwhile, Ty and his crew
made it to the top of Spiral
Mountain, where they came
face to face with Lady Debumon.
Sora and TK set out to
find the rest of us for the final
confrontation, while Ty and Izzy
stayed behind to keep Piedmon busy.
Do you think he'd mind rescheduling our
destruction?
Guess not.
Change into digital champions to save the
digital world!
Digimon, digital monsters, Digimon are the
champions!
Digimon are the champions!
We've looked everywhere, Gomomon,
but we still can't find Matt.
Maybe your harmonica playing is keeping
him in hiding.
Hmm, everybody's a critic.
Hey, Joe, look over there!
What is it?
It's Matt's boat!
He must be close by!
But we have no idea of when he left it,
or if he was using it at all!
Come on, we better keep looking!
Don't be such a downer!
This is our first clue in a long time, and
I want to see a little get-up in Golemon!
I guess I'm still pessimistic,
because when we
found Matt's harmonica,
it let us know where.
But you're right, he could be nearby.
Now that's a spirit.
Joe, you've become a real man lately!
Oh, I get it now.
So you're saying that I wasn't a real man
before, huh?
Are you mad enough not to laugh when I
tickle you?
Mega Claw!
I think we won!
Thank you for the sparring match,
WarGreymon.
Now I'm ready for the main event.
Oh no!
Once upon a time, there were these
digi-destined.
And then Paidmon destroyed them all.
The end.
No offense to your
storytelling skills, but I'd
like it better if your
ending were different.
It will be!
We can't win unless we're all together!
Where are they?
The digi-vice isn't responding at all!
I hope we find them soon!
I'm getting airsick!
We'll never find them all!
The digital world is too big!
They could be anywhere!
Hey, Sora!
What?
We'll be able to find Matt and the others,
right?
Should I tell him the truth?
Well, Sora?
The only thing I can say, TK, is...
Are you alright?
You're not crying, are you?
Just something in my eye.
Don't worry.
We'll find them, TK.
Hmm...
We'll find the others because we have to.
Unless we fight as a team, we'll never
defeat Paidmon.
We can't let him destroy the digital
world!
Tear up more!
He's tough.
We should all fight.
Everyone stay where you are!
But Ty, why not?
The Digimon are still too tired from our
fight with Lady Devimon.
We have to wait until we're at full
strength when Matt and the others rejoin us.
I hope it's soon.
Matt?
Yeah, Paidmon?
Maybe we've been traveling in this
direction a little too long.
This cave is starting to give me the
creeps.
Let's hurry up and get out of here.
I'm still not sure what
you mean by trying to find
yourself, but I'd appreciate
it if you didn't look in here.
Sure.
Whatever.
See everybody?
I told you I'd be back.
I can take care of myself just fine.
I've been living a lie.
You're not a real blonde?
I kept saying TK needed me, but really,
I was the one who needed him.
What do you mean?
I used to think that my one purpose in
life was to protect my little brother.
But then... You're the man!
Nice going, TK!
Great job, buddy!
We were so worried about you.
Boy, for a little kid, that was a pretty
big escape.
He didn't need me to protect him anymore.
And Ty was much better at acting like a
big brother than I ever was.
But you don't have to act.
You are TK's brother.
Ty isn't.
That's just the point.
I don't act like a brother at all.
And even though it made
me feel good to think that I was
the only one there for him,
in reality, all the kids were.
Let's talk about this outside.
There's something strange about this
place.
That's why Ty made me so mad.
I thought he was trying to take TK away
from me.
Ty might be real bossy and hard-headed
sometimes.
But he never treated TK like a child.
Which is how I've always treated him.
But I'm the one who's childish.
Matt, stop putting yourself down.
Sure, you have some teenage angst,
but you've been a great brother to TK.
I used to think Ty never thought about
anyone but himself.
But that actually describes me a lot
better.
Oh, Matt.
Oh, Matt!
I think you'd better take a look at this!
Whatever.
I'm no good.
I can never go back to being their friend.
You have to!
Don't you understand that
if the eight of you don't get
back together, the digital
world will be destroyed forever?
They don't need me, and besides,
seven is a luckier number than eight.
Hey Matt, snap out of it!
Just go away.
I want to be alone.
Come to your senses!
Matt, listen!
Ow!
What are you doing?
Are you crazy?
Don't you understand, Matt?
You've got to quit comparing yourself to
Ty.
You're not him.
It's like ice cream.
He's vanilla, and you're Rocky Road.
But only one of you is TK's real brother,
and it's not him.
No matter how much he
impresses TK, Ty will never be
able to break the bond
that you two brothers share.
Come on!
And besides, don't you think it would
break my heart if you weren't here?
After all, I didn't wait
my entire life for you
to arrive, just so you
can wallow in self-pity.
Huh?
Gabumon.
But Matt, if you really want to be left
alone, then I'll respect your wishes and
disappear, but only if that's what you
really want me to do.
No.
I don't really want to be left alone.
Sorry.
I never meant to hurt you.
Hmm.
I've never let anyone get close to me
before.
Not since my family split up.
Ever since then, I've been alone.
I figured if my family didn't
want me, then I would just
keep to myself and never
tell anyone what I was feeling.
And I swore I would never let anyone see
me cry.
But really, all I wanted to do was cry.
And cry.
I hate being alone.
I'm here for you, Matt.
I used to be lonely too.
I wandered around the digital world
without any friends at all.
And then after I met you, I knew I'd never
be lonely again.
I know what you mean.
Me too.
After all, you're the main reason I came
to the digital world in the first place.
And here I am, lost in this dark, strange
cave, and you're still right by my side.
That's the sign of a true friend.
Oh, shucks.
I guess I have friends.
And that includes TK and my mom and dad.
Now I realize I was never really alone.
People like me.
They really, really like me.
Matt, look!
What is it?
It's been around you this whole time.
You mean you haven't noticed it until now?
Not at all.
It was weird.
The more you talked about being alone,
the bigger that thing got.
It's pitch black.
That's exactly the feeling I had in my
heart just a minute ago.
I know what it is.
Please tell me.
It's... It's the darkness that I've been
carrying around with me this whole time.
The darkness that's been buried in my
heart.
Oh, Gabumon.
Now it's ready to swallow me up whole.
Like Jonah and the whale?
I have a feeling that
if I didn't recognize it
just now, it would have
taken over my whole life.
But I'm not gonna let that happen.
Hmm?
It can't hurt me because I'm not alone
anymore.
That's the spirit.
I wanna thank you, Gabumon.
Don't mention it.
That's what friends are for.
Besides, I should be thanking you.
You're the best friend a Digimon ever had.
Let's make a promise
that we'll always be
there for each other
no matter what happens.
Gabumon and Matt, friends for life.
What do you say?
Do we have a deal?
A handshake makes it official.
Will a pawshake do?
And I promise not to complain anymore
either.
Don't start that again.
If you're upset about something,
you should get it off your chest.
Alright, if you insist, I'll still
complain once in a while, but only to you.
Huh?
Correct me if I'm wrong
on this one, Matt, but
weren't we just in a big
dark cave a minute ago?
That's right, and we were completely lost.
Hey!
Matt!
Over here!
It's Joe!
Who's the man now?
I told you I'd find him!
I never doubted you for a single minute,
Joe.
What's going on?
I said to myself, Joe,
I said, just follow your
own path and sooner or
later you'll run into Matt.
I'm just glad it happened before I
retired.
I see.
Oh, that's right.
I forgot.
Here.
It's your harmonica, isn't it?
Hm.
Thanks, Joe.
Mm-hmm.
Trimpsons!
Wargrimmon's exhausted!
I can't watch anymore!
Stay tough!
Please, Izzy, let me help Wargrimmon!
No!
Wargrimmon needs help!
Come on, Matt!
Where are you?
Look down there!
That's Matt's boat!
But where's...
I hope he's not hurt somewhere.
We'll never find him.
What are we going to do?
TK's right.
Maybe we should go back and help the
others fight.
No.
Ty asked me to find the others and that's
what I'm going to do.
I won't let him down.
Zora, watch out!
There's some hot thing coming out of the
ground!
Huh?
Zora!
TK!
Matt!
It sure does!
Oh, Matt, where have you been?
I was so worried about you.
Sorry, TK.
I needed time to get my head straight,
but I won't leave you again.
I promise you.
Gee, Matt, you'll look different.
Did you cut your hair or something?
No, I just haven't been using as much gel.
Where is everybody?
Some black thing pulled Sora down into
that hole!
Huh?
What?
Is she alright?
Hey, Matt, does this remind you of
anything?
Yeah.
It looks just like that cave we were
trapped in before.
The same black thing must have gotten
Sora.
You've seen it?
Come on, guys!
We've got to help her!
I don't have a good feeling about this.
It's scary!
Whatever you do, don't be afraid.
Okay, guys?
I've realized that it's your fear that
feeds the darkness.
That's easy for you to say!
Whoa!
Oh!
Are you alright, Joe?
Yeah.
Fortunately, I landed on the one part of
my body that has a built-in airbag.
Very funny.
Where's Sora?
We need a clue!
Listen, I think I hear something coming
from over there!
Huh?
I'd call that a clue.
Sora, talk to me!
Please tell me what's wrong!
That's Beaumont's voice!
Which means Sora can't be far behind!
Sora!
Over here!
Sora, what's the matter with you?
Get up!
She's stuck!
Let me help!
On three!
One, two, three!
Once, it took four of us to get my
grandmother off the toilet like that!
Hey, listen!
Sora's saying something!
Huh?
I have to find Mimi, and Joe, and Matt!
I have to help Ty, or the world will be
destroyed!
There's no place like home!
She won't talk to me anymore!
All she does is keep mumbling the same
thing over and over again!
Sora!
Matt and I are right here!
Look at me!
Focus!
Joe, you're really here!
I can't believe it!
And Matt's with you, too!
Just relax.
Everything's gonna be okay now.
I'm afraid not.
I haven't been trying hard enough.
I have to get to Ty right away and help
him fight.
Because if I don't, the world will be
completely destroyed!
Sora, come on!
You can't be responsible for saving the
world!
You have to realize how strong your
negative feelings are!
They produce a powerful, destructive
energy!
Sora, it's the darkness in your heart that
has created the cave in the first place!
Don't you get it?
Really, Matt?
Is that true?
Is that why you told TK not to be scared?
Sora, listen to me.
There's only one way to make this cave
disappear!
You've got to reach deep into your heart!
And erase all the negative feelings!
I don't know if I can!
What should I do?
You'll have to find the answer to that
question on your own.
Sora, this isn't the kind of thing you do
just because you have to.
If you're going to do it, then it has to
be because you want to.
You mean that I don't have to do it if I
don't want to?
Right!
It'll only work if you want to do it!
I'm confused.
How will I know what the right thing to do
is?
When this whole thing
started, do you think we
had any idea what the
right thing to do was?
Of course not!
But that didn't stop us, did it?
Maybe we're here for a reason!
Maybe we're the only ones who can do it!
We're the only ones who can make a
difference!
It's working, Matt!
I think we're finally getting through to
her!
We're the only ones!
That's why we're here!
I get it now!
You were right, Matt!
How did you know?
I kind of went through the same thing
myself.
Welcome back!
Sora!
I'm so happy that you're the old Sora and
not the new Sora!
The cave's gone!
When the darkness from Sora's heart
disappeared, so did the cave!
I feel so relieved!
Boy, wait till Tai hears about this!
Let's find him!
Tai's waiting for us right now!
Let's go!
Hey!
Trumpsword!
Get up, Tai!
Hey, Tai!
Izzy, stop!
You stay there!
Protect Kari!
Tai, look.
I know it's important for
me to stay here and protect
Kari, but in the meantime,
who's gonna protect you?
He tends to be a bit stubborn,
doesn't he?
Don't worry about me.
I'm fine.
I've got him right where I want him.
He's exhausted.
But I can help you.
I'm fine.
That's funny.
General Custer said the exact same thing
at Little Bighorn.
Thanks for the history lesson.
All right, then.
Just one thing.
How come every time I ask, you never let
me join in the fight?
Clone Train!
WarGreymon's been hit!
No!
WarGreymon!
Get up!
Right.
Now who should be next?
WarGreymon!
I'm coming!
Once upon a time, they were digi-destined.
Now they're just sitting ducks waiting for
me to take target to practice.
Ty!
Matt!
You made it!
I can't believe you're here!
Yeah.
I made it, Ty.
Hang in there, buddy.
I never doubted you for a second,
Matt.
I know it didn't always seem that way.
Thank you, Ty, for believing in me.
I'm just sorry I was so late.
Ty, you have to know how much our
friendship has always meant to me.
And I swear nothing will ever come between
us again.
WarGreymon!
Now what?
Matt, your Crest of
Friendship gave me
strength and brought
WarGreymon back to normal.
Thank you, Guru Ruman.
Now I can fight again.
Come on, guys.
Get out of there!
Ty, are you okay?
I think so.
My first thought was to destroy you all
together in one nice little package.
But now I believe I'd
rather do it individually
so as to prolong your
suffering a little longer.
You sure talk a lot for a clown.
Trum Sword!
Grrrr!
Now he'll see what we're made of!
They were able to break Piedmon's attack!
All right!
Well, could it actually be the case that I
finally found an adversary worth fighting?
Will WarGreymon and MetalGururumon have
enough strength to defeat Piedmon,
the last of the Dark Masters?
Find out on the next Digimon Digital
Monsters.
We'll be right back.