Coromon and I didn't know how, but we were
transported back to my real-life hometown.
Not only was everything exactly the same
as it was when I left for camp,
it was even the same day I arrived in
DigiWorld.
Other things were weird, too.
My little sister, Kari, somehow knew all
about Coromon.
For some reason, evil Digimon were trying
to cross over into the real world.
We received a transmission from Izzy
warning us not to return to DigiWorld,
but we knew we had to go back.
We had to save both worlds!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Change into Digital Champions to save the
digital world!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
This is right where we left them.
Where could they have gone?
Huh?
Well, looks like somebody's around, because
I'm getting a reading from their digivice.
Hmm.
Okay, I've got a lock.
North-northwest, just a couple of clicks.
Very impressive, Ty.
You really sound like you know what you're
doing.
I just watch a lot of TV.
Just what is a click?
I don't know exactly, but we're getting
closer.
I hope so.
I'm hungry.
Look at this place.
Where are we?
I don't know, but it's the most beautiful
place I've ever seen.
Come on.
The signal's getting stronger.
Who is it?
It's Tokomon.
Tokomon!
Hey, what happened, little guy?
Are you all right?
Not exactly.
You look like Ty.
You're alive.
Yeah, the last time I checked.
I'll bet a black-eared Digimon got you
right.
No, if it was something simple like that,
I wouldn't feel so bad.
Where is everybody?
Where's TK?
I don't know.
He's probably out for this new friend.
New friend?
What new friend?
I think you better ask TK.
I would, but he's not here, and you are.
Now start at the beginning, Tokomon,
and tell me exactly what happened.
Well, you were gone an awful long time.
We were?
How long?
We looked high and low for you.
I did most of the low part.
Finally!
It's no use.
We're practically lost ourselves.
Oh, personally, I've been lost ever since
I got here.
What about Jedi?
Maybe he can help us find them.
Yeah, and where do we find Jedi?
I think one wild goose chase is enough.
This is the most depressing camp out ever.
Won't TK be upset?
Maybe, but he'll be safer here.
Shh!
We're going off to find Tai on our own.
Don't wake anyone.
We'll see you later, Tokomon.
Oh, okay.
That's how it started.
First Sora left.
Then we all went in search of Sora.
Then someone said maybe we'd cover more
ground if we split up.
So Izzy and Tintamon went up one way.
And Joe and Gomamon went up another.
And pretty soon, only Matt, TK,
Gabumon, and me were left.
Why did everybody go away?
When you're lost, you're supposed to stay
together.
We just had different ideas of what was
the best thing to do, TK.
We've looked everywhere, TK.
If they were anywhere in this area,
we would have found them.
We could have missed something.
We've got to keep searching.
Come on, Matt.
If we hurry, we could still catch up
with some... Hey, it's hopeless, all right?
We've already done everything we could.
Oh, come on.
Don't cry.
I didn't mean it.
Don't worry.
Wherever Agumon and Tai are, I'm sure
they're perfectly all right.
Really, Matt?
Any minute now, they'll be coming back,
right?
And they'll bring a bunch of presents with
them.
Oh, wow.
You think so?
I hope you're right.
I sure miss my friends.
I knew Matt was just kidding TK about the
presents.
But that didn't matter, because
just then... Oh, look, Matt!
Is it real?
Everybody's gonna love this place.
But Matt didn't seem too excited.
It was like there was something on his
mind that he couldn't stop thinking about.
Look at this!
No lines!
Actually, there are no people here at all.
Maybe they forgot to tell us that they're
closed.
So, TK, you sure you'll be all right?
I'll be fine.
Don't worry about me.
That's my big little bro.
But you'll be back pretty soon,
right?
Right.
I'm just gonna look around a little.
Really check this place out.
I'll be back in maybe a couple of hours at
the most.
Tokomon, you're responsible for looking
after him, okay?
Sure!
Don't worry.
We'll be waiting right here.
Great!
And remember, it's an amusement park,
so, like, amuse yourself.
See you soon!
Okay, bye!
Hours went by and still no Matt.
He'll come back, TK.
I wonder what's keeping them.
You've gotta eat something.
Should've come back by now.
We waited at the park for almost a week.
TK spent the whole time
staring out at the water,
except when he just
couldn't stay awake anymore.
He waited... and waited.
He's coming.
Any minute now, I'll see his boat out
there.
Don't cry again!
He's gone!
I just know it!
He's gone away like all the others!
He said he'd be back in a couple of hours!
Now don't give him hope!
Hey!
What's all the squawking about?
Demi Devamon's a name.
Mind if I drop in?
Demi Devamon?
I've heard about you.
Oh, great!
I'm flattered!
Don't be.
Nothing I heard was good.
Okay, okay.
I admit I used to be
a bit of a wise guy, but
that's only because I
was working for Edamon.
But now he's kaput thanks to you guys,
something for which I'm eternally grateful.
Personally, I never liked the guy.
You see, my brother out there is in a
boat.
Oh, is that what's got you down squirt
before you come to the right, Digimon?
What's his name, your brother?
His name is Matt.
Got it.
Let me see what I can do.
Back in the flash.
Well, maybe he has changed.
You think?
I couldn't believe that one of Edamon's
creepy henchmen was being helpful,
but sure enough, just a few minutes
later... Sorry to keep you waiting.
What about it?
Did you find my brother?
Did you find him?
Sure I did.
Is he on his way back?
Well, that's the bad news, kid.
What?
It kills me to have
to be the one to break
this to you, but your
bro ain't coming back.
In fact, he never wants to see you again.
Said he was tired of babysitting a
crybaby.
No way!
It can't be true, TK.
He called me... Crybaby,
yeah, that's what he said.
He called you some other stuff,
too, but I don't want to repeat it.
Anyway, he's gone...
No!
Don't take it so hard!
I'm lying to you, too!
Come on, Matt would never say stuff like
that.
Besides, we've been working on the crying
thing, and you're getting better.
You really are.
Don't believe that guy.
Hey, Flopsy!
You have to stop lying to TK.
Lies?
Whatever could you mean by that?
You take back all those lies, or you'll be
sorry.
My, my, those are pretty bold words coming
from a pink jubber with an overbite.
Besides, do you have any proof that I'm
lying about it, huh?
Well, no.
There you go.
You're just assuming the worst because of
my background.
That's not fair.
It's prejudice.
That's what it is.
Just because I'm
not a cuddly butterball
like you, then you think
I must be a bad guy.
That's so, I don't know, superficial.
Luckily, TK's more enlightened.
Tokamon, what are you doing?
What, TK?
I saw you take a shot at him.
Don't be too hard on him, TK.
I understand what the poor guy's feeling.
It's only naturally to be a little resentful
that you found yourself a new friend.
Hmph!
I don't know what's gotten into you,
but I think an apology's in order.
Well, don't hold your breath.
Do it!
I will not.
If you like that flying rat so much,
maybe I ought to leave.
If you won't apologize, you have to leave.
You really mean it?
Yeah, sure.
Go on.
I won't be coming back, you know.
You don't see me crying about it, and I
don't want these stupid gadgets either.
Come on, Demi-Devamon.
Let's go ride the roller coaster.
That suits me fine.
Goodbye.
You see, Ty, we go away for a couple of
days and everything falls apart.
Hmm.
First let's find out what TK's up to,
then we'll look for Matt and the others.
Take us to him, Tokomon.
You got it.
That's the place?
Yeah, TK's somewhere in there with that
flying phony.
We'll make those kids pay for what they
did to Lord Edamon.
Wait.
Those punk kids are not the pushoers they
look like.
Right.
What do we get out of it except a
headache?
Let's face it.
Edamon's washed up.
Why knock ourselves out for that creep?
Good question.
I never liked working for him anyway.
I say we take a lunch break.
So where can we get some grub around here?
Well, uh... If you like
mushrooms, I know just the place.
Woo-wee, ain't this a gas?
We're having some fun now, huh?
Ha-ha!
Hey TK, I bet I can spin farther than you!
Hmm... Tokomon's awful
small to be all on his own.
I hope he's okay.
Forget about him, will ya?
Come on, let's try the highway!
All right.
Okay, TK, really wrap this baby up!
Put the pedal to the metal and feel the
freedom of the open road!
Woo-hoo!
This is so much fun, it ought to be
illegal!
Okay, you gotta scream at the top of your
lungs!
Ready?
Whoa!
This kid's getting to be a real drag.
You're not still thinking about Tokomon,
are ya?
He made the decision to walk out on you!
Not much of a friend if you ask me!
I know, but I can't help wondering if he's
okay.
This is gonna be harder than I thought!
Hey, I just remember, there's something
I've gotta take care of!
I'll be right back!
You're leaving me too?
Just for a minute, trust me!
You just stay and have fun!
Huh?
Why's it going off?
Could be trouble, that's what it usually
means!
Never mind that now, look who I found!
TK!
Yoo-hoo!
Hey!
It's my friend!
Hey, little guy!
You're back!
Yeah, and are we glad to see you!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
I'm so happy!
Aw, Ty!
I was worried!
You were gone so long!
We thought something bad must've happened!
Well, I'm back again, and I'm all in one
piece!
Eww!
Tokomon, you came back too!
Uh-huh!
So you finally admit that you were wrong
and you're gonna apologize to him now?
I wasn't wrong and I won't apologize!
Tokomon, what's happened to you?
When'd you get to be such a brat?
Okay, you two, chill out!
Knock off this bickering
right now because we've
got too many other
problems to worry about!
We've gotta go try and find Matt and all
the others!
Not me!
Hmm?
Why should I?
They're not nice!
They left me behind!
First Sora, then Rest, then even my own
brother Matt!
Come on, TK!
It's not your fault they left!
They hate me!
They think I'm a crybaby!
Even Matt said I was!
Whoa, man!
I don't know what this new friend of yours
has been telling you!
But I happen to know for a fact that Matt
does not hate you!
Well, you might not be saying
such nice things about him if you
knew that I wanted to keep
searching for you, but he didn't!
It's true!
He's really jealous of you, Ty!
Haven't you ever noticed he
gets all upset when you and me
do stuff together and he
hates it when I talk about you?
Huh?
Do you think I could be your little
brother instead?
What?
Please!
Uh, I don't think it works that way.
Why not?
It just doesn't, that's all!
Uh, you don't like me either!
Hey!
What would Edamon say if he saw you two
lounging around like that?
Who?
Edamon what?
Who's that?
No idea!
Uh, who are you, come to think of it?
Who am I?
Guess I forgot!
Matt!
What do you know?
The famous mushrooms of forgetfulness!
I've always wondered if
these things really work and
judging from the two of you
clowns, they obviously do!
Feed the kid a few of these and he'll
forget all about that Tokomon!
So I'll be your big brother, but just
temporarily until we find Matt, okay?
Okay!
Look, it's Demi Devilmon!
That's him?
Not the most trustworthy looking guy I've
ever seen!
Welcome back Tokomon, how you been?
Okay, what did Matt really say to you?
Cool it buddy, just who are you anyway?
We're friends of TK's real friends!
Start talking and it better be the truth
this time!
It happened just like I told TK!
Matt said he was tired of the little guy
and didn't want to hang with him anymore!
I told Matt that
brothers really ought to
stick together, but he
wouldn't listen to me!
It's the truth, cross my heart!
If you've got one!
Hey!
Why would I lie?
Then you won't mind taking us to Matt so
we can ask him ourselves!
Not at all, but I gotta warn ya,
he's far away!
Let's get started then!
Fine, let's go!
But it's been a long day, wouldn't you
like something to eat first?
I am hungry!
Me too!
Well in that case... I picked these
myself, they're fresh and juicy!
Hey wait, don't just eat them raw,
let's do this right!
Voila!
Les mushrooms de la barbecue!
They'll be ready in just a minute!
Oops-a-daisy!
Gotta use the little Digimon's room!
Don't forget to wash your hands or claws
or whatever they are!
What do you know?
More mushrooms!
Okay TK, you're first!
Tell me if it's too hot!
Womp womp!
I wouldn't touch it!
Hang on, this one didn't get cooked on one
side!
No offense to Ty, but I prefer mine raw!
Don't eat it!
They're the mushrooms of forgetfulness!
They'll make all your memories disappear!
Who's there?
I know that voice, it's Sora!
If what she said about these
mushrooms is true, then that means... YAH!
Don't eat the mushrooms!
Yay!
Finally!
It's probably still a little hot,
huh?
Just blow on it!
There, now give it a try!
Smells yummy!
No, drop it!
Put it down!
Stop it!
Don't eat that mushroom!
It's all right, Agumon, there are plenty
of mushrooms to go around!
No!
Don't eat any of them!
They're poison!
Evil!
Bad stuff!
Hey!
Wait!
You don't see him eating them!
Try one!
Come on!
Open up!
He won't eat one!
He was trying to slip us some kind of
mushroom that makes you forget things!
You're bad!
Huh?
Is that true?
Were you trying to poison us?
Don't be silly!
You're lying just like you lied about
Matt!
It was a lie, wasn't it?
YAH!
You flying brat!
Tokumon, can you ever forgive me?
If you promise, we'll always be friends!
Of course!
Good work!
At least that's one problem taken care of!
Here, TK, I thought you might want this
back.
You betcha!
Check it out!
TK's crest is glowing!
It's not good!
Who gave you the idea that crest was
yours?
Hand it over, you little squirt!
I'm gonna teach this Mona lesson!
Get it!
Go after him!
Digimon!
Digimon are the champions!
Oh!
Way to go, Padamon!
Take him down!
Come here!
Padamon!
You know, you really should consider
running yourself out as a football!
Hang in there, Padamon!
We're on our way!
No!
Stay there!
Wait for us!
What are you doing?
Let him do what he's got to do.
I have a feeling he's going to be all
right.
What's this?
You're mine!
You were awesome, Padamon.
Now I feel even worse about the way I
treated you.
We promised we'd
always be friends and the
first rule of friendship
is forgive and forget.
Let's forget it ever happened,
okay?
Okay.
I'll pretend I had a bite of that funny
mushroom.
Me too!
Aw, that's kind of cool, isn't it?
Yeah!
And it wouldn't have happened if it hadn't
been for you, Agumon.
By the way, how did you find out about
those mushrooms anyway?
Uh, voice in my head!
You're kidding!
No!
I was close!
So close!
Uh-oh!
Now I'm in for it!
Forgive me, oh terrible one!
The Crest of Hope has regained its light!
I failed!
But I'll make it up to you!
I'll work overtime!
And on Sundays!
Okay, listen up.
Izzy was totally right when he said that
all the weird stuff going on here in the
Digiworld somehow affects our own world,
too!
I don't know how we're going to do it yet,
but it seems to me we've got to fix things
in this world before we can return to our
own world.
But if we're going to do that,
we've all got to work together as a team!
Every one of us is important!
Am I important, too?
Of course you are, TK!
You're a part of the team!
Now let's go find the others!
Yay!
I guess we learned it doesn't
take a mushroom of forgetfulness
to make us sometimes
forget who our real friends are.
Yeah, sorry, Catamon.
It's forgotten, remember?
That's right, I forgot!
Haha!