Matt and I were having
a disagreement when
suddenly an entity began
to speak through Kari.
It showed us images of the past when we
first saw the Digimon four years ago.
Next, we saw past images of
Prydemon attempting to steal
the Digi-Eggs of what were to
eventually become our Digimon.
A young Jedi rescued the eggs and took
them to the safety of Vile Island,
where we first found them.
After our history lesson, Kari returned to
normal, but Matt still wanted to leave.
Mimi and Joe also separated from the
group.
If this keeps up, there won't be anyone
left to save either world!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Change into Digital Champions to save the
Digital World!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Get away from me, you pile of Woodmon.
I know your tricks.
You pretend to be
trees and then absorb the
energy from unsuspecting
Digimon as they pass by.
This is your last warning.
All right, you ask for it.
How many Woodmon can an Ogremon chuck if
an Ogremon could chuck Woodmon?
Pummelwhats!
They should run fast for tree stumps.
This is good.
Joe, can I tell you something?
What?
I hope I wasn't too selfish for saying I
didn't want to fight anymore.
I don't think you were selfish.
In fact, I think you were pretty brave.
What you said was true.
Fighting just leads to more fighting and
then nothing ever gets resolved.
My brother Jim used to say the same thing
after he'd get beat up.
Joe?
What is it, Joe?
It's nothing.
Never mind.
Joe?
What?
Don't keep things bottled up inside.
It's not healthy.
Don't tell me about not being healthy.
I've been not healthy my whole life,
so I'm an expert.
And if I want to keep things bottled up,
I will.
Whoa, it looks like somebody needs a time
out in the corner.
I was just trying to lend a friendly ear.
I know you were, Gomomon.
Sorry, buddy.
What is that thing?
It looks like a meteorite.
Look out!
It's coming this way!
I can't get rid of you guys.
You're not trees, you're weeds.
It can't all in like this, not before I
beat Leomon.
Huh?
What in the world?
That thing is monstrous.
It's heading right for us!
What's happening?
Was that some sort of explosion?
An earthquake?
A meteor!
And I mean a whopper!
It just crashed in the forest!
Totally cool!
Let's go check it out!
I don't know, Ty.
It could be dangerous.
Yeah!
Let's head over to Puppetmon's mansion
instead!
We'll show you guys exactly where it is!
I suppose it's inevitable.
He's one of the Dark Masters and we'll
have to fight him sooner or later.
Yeah, it's time somebody cut his strings
instead of waiting around here.
Let's take the fight to him for a change.
If we don't hurry up, I'm afraid that both
our worlds will be destroyed!
Let's do it, Ty!
Hmm.
Wait a second, you guys.
Let's think this over.
Puppetmon is a Mega Digimon and we won't
be able to defeat him that easily.
Oh, in that case, let's give up and go
watch cartoons!
Let's fight!
The only fair thing to do is to take a
vote.
All those in favor of going to Puppetmon's
mansion, raise your hand and say aye!
Aye!
The ayes have it!
Ty, you didn't vote.
I wonder how Matt would vote.
Knowing him, he'd probably go the safe
route.
So Ty, what do you think?
And what about TK?
With Matt not here, it's my job to make
sure nothing happens to him.
What should we do, Ty?
Well, uh, we're waiting for an answer!
After all we've been through, he can't
really be thinking about going.
All right, we're going.
Just to take a look around.
But we don't necessarily have to start any
trouble.
Yes!
It's this way, guys!
Sora?
I'll go along with your decision,
but I'm still not sure it's safe.
I know it's dangerous, Sora, and we're not
looking for trouble.
But if anything happens,
Coromon and I will hold
off Puppetmon while you
take the others and escape.
I won't let anything happen to you.
You mean it?
Of course I do.
Okay, then.
Ladies and gentlemen, boys and girls, get
ready for the comeback tour of the year!
Baby, I'm back!
Yeah!
Look!
There it is!
The meteor landed up on that cliff!
I wonder where on earth it could have come
from?
Probably L.A.
Huh.
What?
I smell something.
Come over there!
Wait!
Hey!
Not so fast!
I might sweat!
And I keep tripping on my roots!
Huh?
I think someone's hurt.
Hang in there!
We're coming!
We've got to get these branches off of
him!
Get out of here before he wakes up!
It looks like he's hurt!
Good!
Then he won't be able to chase us!
Remember him from File Island?
He was meaner than a cat getting a bath!
Let's pretend like we never found him.
Hey!
Mimi!
What are you doing?
This cat looks bad!
You're the Digi Destin!
Well, I guess you don't have amnesia,
but try not to move anyway, okay?
Palmon, go look for some healing herbs, and
go, Amon, see if you can find some water!
Right!
Now, Joe, I want
you to... I know.
My father is a doctor, and he taught me a
lot.
I used to practice on my toys.
Toys?
I told you not to move!
Okay.
Ow!
That stuff burns!
Be careful!
Big baby, don't you want to get better?
It looks like his arm might be broken.
We're going to have to put it in a sling.
Ooh!
Toilet paper!
Do you have to do that now?
Really, Mimi?
I'm using this bandages.
Before we came back to the digital world,
I thought of things we might need.
And toilet paper was the first thing that
came to my mind.
There.
Just about finished here.
Well?
Feel soft.
It must be two-ply.
Lay off the Digivolving for a few days,
and you'll be as good as new.
Ow!
Joe, I never knew you were so resourceful.
Why are you digi-destined being so nice to
me?
Especially after the way I tried to
destroy you on Vile Island.
You could have left me here to rot,
but instead you saved me.
Why?
Well, we were taught that if someone's in
trouble, you always help them out.
That means even if they were trying to
pummel you into oblivion.
Gee, I never thought of it that way.
Thanks.
I owe you one.
Don't mention it.
Besides, that's what friends do.
They help each other out.
Bye.
Wait.
Don't leave now.
I've never had any friends.
Oh.
Well, you have them now.
I've never seen Obermann cry before.
Don't tell me you need more toilet paper
to blow your nose.
It's all right.
I'll just use my sleeve.
That's gotta hurt with all those spikes.
Huh?
Here's a riddle.
What has four strings and is made of what?
Togamon!
No.
A violin.
But that's a good guess.
I guess you guys aren't music lovers.
No, it's you we don't like.
Oh, yeah?
Do you like this?
I can also play a really mean saxophone.
I've got a digi-ball!
But...
Oh, no.
What if Togamon gets hurt during the
fight?
Go Momon, digi-volve!
Right!
Digimon!
Digital monsters, Digimon are the
truck-gills!
Digimon!
Digital monsters, Digimon are the
truck-gills!
The Kaku-mon!
Digimon!
Harpoon torpedo!
Arrgh!
Huh?
Digimon!
The truck-gills!
The Kaku-mon!
Digimon!
Dude!
Whoa!
Get Digi with it!
Metal Edamon's in the house!
A superstar like me deserves a little
applause, baby!
After all, it's been so long since we've
seen each other!
Oh, no!
It's Edamon!
I used to be Edamon, kid, but that was a
long time ago.
Oh!
Now?
I'm Metal Edamon!
Oh, thank you!
Oh, thank you very much!
We thought Edamon was tough!
Metal Edamon's a Mega Digimon!
After his banana slip attack, he'll have
to peel us off the floor!
Just what we need!
New and unimproved!
Let me tell you how I became me!
Now here's what inspired when an Edamon
expired!
Listen up, baby!
I'm sure you all remember the battle I had
with Metal Grandma!
I'll tell you, he's one tough dinosaur,
honey!
After that, I was swallowed up by a black
hole!
I think I gave it indigestion!
My digital information was scattered
throughout the universe!
I pulled myself together and chilled out
for a while in Digimon Limbo!
My information was chopped, mixed,
whipped, and pureed!
I felt like a four-speed blender,
honey!
But I refused to return to the digital
world until I was bigger, fatter,
and had a full head of beautiful metal
hair!
Now I'm back to get my revenge on you,
Digidistant!
I got the low-down dirty revengeful!
Now!
I'm talkin' big-time Digidistant!
Enough!
I just got started there, you oversized
footstool!
Who you callin' oversized?
Watch your step!
Banana slip!
Too much of a wax and build-up?
Uh-huh!
Puppet!
Palmer!
I'll use you as a toothpick!
Metal power!
You're pretty dirty!
I'm not dirty, I just got detailed at the
car wash yesterday!
Now's our chance to escape!
Na-na-na-na-na-na-na!
So that's Puppetmon's mansion,
huh?
There are two guards!
See who they are!
Analyze it!
One of them is Floramon!
She's a plant-type Digimon who digivolves
like a reptile!
Her attack is Reign of Pollen!
And the other
guard is... Daramon!
At first glance it looks
like a bird-type Digimon,
but it's actually got a plant
growing out of its back!
Prodigious!
So they're not ultimate Digimon,
right?
Right!
Nonetheless, we should be careful!
They could be quite dangerous!
Shall we go?
Wait!
Hmm?
There might be more guards inside!
I'll go inside and make sure the coast is
clear!
You guys wait here until I get back!
Ty, I think Padamon and I should go with
you!
After all, we're the only ones who know
where everything is inside there!
Right!
Sorry, it might be dangerous!
Come on, Ty!
Don't treat me like a little kid!
That's not it!
What if we go together?
As a team?
I vote with Kari!
There's nothing to be afraid of if we all
go together!
What do we do, Ty?
You decide!
All right, everyone!
We're going!
Follow me!
Oh!
Hey!
Cut it out!
Hey, quit it!
I hate tickling!
Come on!
We're gone!
It's your fault, you piece of rotted drip,
boy!
You recycle tin can!
Big dumb knothole!
Hey!
Where you going?
Home!
You're lousy at name calling!
Oh, yeah?
Well, I'm metal and you're wood!
Whatever you say bounces off of me and
splits you in half!
Who needs him, anyway?
I can find old DigiDestine myself!
After all, I am the ultimate metal
detector!
Let's go!
Digimon!
Digimon Captain!
Caramon Digimon 2!
Super Shocker!
Go get him!
Pepper Bread!
Woo!
Whoa!
If you wanted fried chicken, you could've
asked!
Sorry!
We thought you guys were out here
protecting Puppetmon's mansion!
Oh!
So you barbecue me!
We're not here protecting anything!
Then what are you guys doing?
Well, we're supposed to be Puppetmon's
playmates!
You know, someone to chase around and
attack when he gets bored.
But let me fill you in on a little secret.
Puppetmon is an obnoxious jerk and none of
us around this place can stand him!
Oh yeah, now I remember
Puppetmon doesn't have
any friends even
though he thinks he does!
Yeah, that's right!
Wow!
What could be worse than having a life
without a single friend?
A litter box lined with flypaper?
Ha!
So is Puppetmon inside the house right
now?
I think he's out being fumigated for
termites!
So what should we do, Ty?
Well now's a good chance to take a look
inside the mansion.
Terramon, will you show us around?
Sure, I used to be a tour guide at Digimon
Studios!
Oh, no video cameras, flash photography,
food or drink are allowed during the tour.
Great!
Let's go!
The main structure was built before the
digital revolution.
How hard could it be to find a bunch of
kids?
So, does it still hurt?
Actually, no, not really.
I need to know how I can ever thank you
all.
Oh, forget about it.
You don't need to thank us.
No, I have to.
It's an ancient tradition to repay all
acts of kindness.
It's part of my sacred moral code as an
ogre-mon.
Sacred moral code?
What are you?
A member of King Arthur's court or
something?
Oh, that's so romantic.
I'm sorry.
I'll try to be meaner next time.
Yeah, you'll ruin your reputation.
It's a jack-in-the-box with a serious
attitude!
You wouldn't happen to be leading us into
some sort of trap, would you, Dara-mon?
Why, of course not!
I would never try
anything as deceitful as
Puppet-mon, cross my
wings and hope to fly, honest!
I believe him, Ty.
How about you?
Hmm... Oh, boy!
It's a toy!
Oh, no!
Make sure you don't touch it!
Uh-oh!
What's happening?
Watch out!
Get down!
It was a heat-activated bomb!
That's why I said don't touch anything!
Sorry!
Ogre-mon, can I ask you a personal
question?
Yes, it's true.
I don't floss.
That's not what I was going to ask.
Why do you fight with Le-mon?
Do you hate him?
No, no, it's not a question of hate.
It's our destiny to fight each other.
He and I will be rivals for all eternity.
Well, if that's your only purpose in life,
what would happen if you actually won?
I never really thought about it before.
Maybe I'll take a vacation.
A cruise is always nice.
And after that?
What do you mean, after that?
Well, if the fight's over, you wouldn't
have a rival anymore.
Of course I would.
He and I are like two
old warriors, fighting
a war that had no
beginning and has no end.
Why, the only reason I exist at all is to
defeat Le-mon, and if he were gone,
well, I'm so confused.
You've got to have more of a purpose in
life than to just defeat Le-mon.
Leave me alone.
You can't possibly understand.
This rivalry is as old as time itself.
I don't care what happens.
I'll think about it after I've defeated
Le-mon.
You're getting way too excited.
I better take your blood pressure.
What's that?
It came from out here.
I found you!
Run!
Who should I play with next?
Puppet-mon's coming back.
Are you ready?
It would help if I had some idea of how
this worked.
You do it.
What?
That's against every principle I stand
for.
All right, what the heck, I'll do it.
But don't tell Puppet-mon.
It'll be our secret.
Shh.
Yeah, yeah.
We know.
Okay, I've got him in my sights.
Ready?
Aim.
Fire!
I can see him coming.
Take this, Puppet-mon!
It's the Digi-dustin!
You can't hide from me.
I'm the king of swing!
Oh!
Who is this new creature?
Could he be Ogre-mon's arch-rival?
And will Puppet-mon
escape Der-mon's cannon
blast to take his revenge
on the Digi-dustin?
Tune in for the next episode of Digimon
Digital Monsters.