So we wound up back at camp where this
whole adventure started.
We had to find the 8th Digi-Destined before
Myotismon could sink his fangs into him.
It wouldn't be easy, because we were still
miles away from the city.
We got there only to find Mammothmon
destroying everything.
Garudamon took care of that hairy
elephant.
That's when we remember that all of us saw
two Digimon fighting years ago.
Izzy figured that's why we
were the Digi-Destined, and
that the 8th child must have
seen the Digimon before, too.
Let's hope we find the kid before
Myotismon does.
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Change into Digital Champions to save the
Digital World!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Digimon!
Digital Monsters!
Digimon are the champions!
Digimon are the champions.
Digimon, digital monsters.
Digimon, digital...
So you're telling me Garudamon has
appeared in the real world?
Right.
And the seven children have returned to
the real world as well, Master.
And?
The eighth child has not been found yet?
Eh, no, malignant one.
Not quite yet, but any minute now.
Guaranteed.
We're, uh, widening the search pattern
even as we speak.
He's alive.
If the kid's anywhere to be found,
we'll find him.
We're looking everywhere.
Air, land, and sea.
We gotta cover no problem.
Meanwhile, we are not the only ones
looking for him, are we?
You don't.
Make sure that those children don't find
him first.
Got it, Master.
Can we get a snack before we go looking?
There's no time.
We've got to get to Odaiba and find that
eighth kid before somebody else does.
How will we get there?
Do you think there are any fast food
places along the way?
Would you knock it off about the food?
Anyway, we've only got enough money for
our subway tickets.
Subway?
Oh well, my parents won't let me ride the
subway by myself.
You're not by yourself.
Now come on.
Are subways like regular trains?
I mean, do they have snack cars?
Just drop it and stick together,
everybody.
It can get kind of confusing down here.
I just hope my Otis Mon has as much
trouble reading this map as I do.
Okay, what do we do now besides starve to
death?
I'm just figuring it out.
Okay, that'll work.
Now, the fastest route to
Odaiba is to take the number
12 train to Nagano and
transfer to the Maranucci Line.
Then transfer to the Ginza Line and get
off at Shinbashi.
Huh?
Sounds simple enough.
Now we just have to figure out the right
fare.
What's that, Ty?
What are you getting?
A ticket.
You can't ride the train without one.
What's a ticket?
What's a train?
Shh!
Come on, guys.
Not another word out of you from now on,
okay?
We don't want anybody seeing
you and then asking a bunch
of questions that we don't
want to explain the answer to.
Yeah, while we're here, you've got to
pretend to be toys or stuffed animals.
But remember to keep still and no
fidgeting.
Here's an idea.
I'll be one of those dolls you told me
about.
The kind where you squeeze them and they
go, wah, wah, wah, wah!
Be a doll that doesn't talk.
It's some kind of cave.
I don't like being underground.
Hey, put a lid on it.
Attention, attention.
Number 12 train now arriving at Platform
7.
What?
Where'd that voice come from?
You heard it?
Then it's not just inside my head.
Something's coming!
Look at those glowing eyes!
It's one of my Otispawn's goons!
Hey!
Watch out!
Ah!
We can't take you guys anywhere.
Hush!
Come on!
Here, take my seat.
Oh!
Thank you!
Wasn't that nice of a girl?
We've been on our feet all day,
haven't we?
Ah!
No!
No, no, honey!
Let go now!
That's the girl's toy!
Come on!
Honey!
Ow!
That's gotta hurt!
Oh, come on, honey!
Let go of the girl's toy before you break
it!
Honey!
I guess my toy didn't like when you pulled
on him.
You hear that?
That stuffed animal talked!
Ha!
It worked!
All that practice is paying off!
Fooled him, didn't we?
Hush!
Just keep quiet and play along!
Come on!
The baby pulled your hair because he likes
you, that's all!
Oh, really?
There's no reason to bite the poor thing's
head off!
Oh!
I'm very sorry I shouted!
See that, son?
She's just making it look like the doll is
talking.
It's called ventriloquism!
She's pretty good!
Whoa!
Actually, that was the doll talking!
I want one!
Huh?
Daddy, give me that toy!
I want that doll!
Huh?
If I don't get one right now, I'll start
screaming at the top of my bones!
Excuse me, young lady, can I ask where you
bought that doll?
I need one right away!
Uh, where I bought it?
It's not that hard a question,
is it?
Come on, you'll be doing me a big favor.
Where did you find it?
This stop is Nerima.
Please watch your step.
Again, this stop is Nerima.
Whoa!
The Nerima Department Store!
What?
Nerima?
Thanks a lot!
Come on, son!
Oh!
Thanks again!
Bye-bye!
Wow, that was a close one.
Pretty weird how nuts that kid went over
Yokomon.
If we don't find the eighth child,
we could go into the... Toy business?
How much longer?
Oh no, someone wake me when we get there!
Yeah, me too.
What's the name of the stop where we're
getting off again?
We get off in Nagano.
Okay.
Nagano.
This stop is Nagano.
Please watch your step.
Again, this stop is Nagano.
Hey!
Here's our stop!
Look!
We're supposed to be quiet!
Shinjuku, this stop.
The end of the line.
Last stop, Shinjuku.
Please exit.
Huh?
What?
How'd we miss our stop?
All of you slept right through it.
Padamont, you were awake?
Sure.
What's wrong with you?
Why didn't you wake us up?
How could I?
You told us not to make a sound.
Oh!
What now?
Go back to our stop?
No.
It's out of our way.
But I think we can change trains here and
be okay.
How much longer?
I'm getting awful hungry, Ty!
Yeah, I'm starving!
Famished!
It can wait.
Hey, I'm hungry too, you know.
I keep visualizing cheeseburgers!
And I don't even eat cheeseburgers!
It has been a long time since any of us
have eaten.
And our Digimon get weak when they're
hungry.
Okay.
This place is a zoo and not a restaurant
in sight.
The first one to see some place to eat,
give a shout, okay?
Huh?
Dad, can I get some ice cream?
Oh, uh, hey Izzy!
What is it?
You see something?
The other guys.
They're gone!
What?
I can't believe this!
They ditched us!
Oh!
Okay, okay, don't panic.
As long as we have this, we can always
find them.
Huh?
That's funny.
Why isn't it working?
You think something might have happened to
it when we came back to the real world?
All I know is this is one of those days
when everything goes wrong.
Come on!
Let's hurry.
Freeze it!
Apples!
Ow!
Ah!
Bad dog!
Huh?
Look!
They're eating without us!
I feel like a new woman!
Man!
Tastes great!
Yum-alicious!
Boy, I sure needed this!
You people are lucky!
Yum-yum!
You get to eat this stuff every day!
A little louder, why don't you?
There's a couple of people that aren't
staring yet.
Actually, nobody noticed yet, but Matt's
right!
You should...
Oh!
Uh-oh!
Joe, Izzy!
Well, it's about time!
Hey!
What are you guys waiting for?
Order something!
How?
When you guys have got all the money,
huh?
Whoops!
We went and spent it all!
See?
We were all so hungry, we ordered the
super-duper combos!
Great!
You spent it all?
That was all the money we had in the
world!
All the dumb, greedy, selfish little
things, it's unbelievable!
These guys are supposed to be my friends!
My friends!
Look at that!
Now the digivice is responding!
So, why wouldn't it be?
Well, it wasn't working at all when I
tried it in the station!
Really?
I guess in this world they only function
at a close distance.
That's great!
But meanwhile, what are we going to do
now?
We start walking!
They won't let us back on the train
without any money!
I'm sure not looking forward to walking
all that way!
Ha!
I know a way that won't cost us a penny!
Just leave everything to me!
Oh, great!
You're a genius!
Help!
Police!
My cat is stuck in a tree in Odaiba!
And I've gotta get there right away so I
can get her down!
Hey!
The police?
That's his brilliant idea?
If the police do stop, they'll lock him up
for disturbing the peace!
Hey!
I've got the right of way!
Looking good, Ty!
Good grief!
At this rate, we could be sitting here all
day!
And night!
Then you try to get us a ride!
Me?
No way!
How about you, Matt?
You think you're so smart!
Hm.
Whoa!
Well?
I'm waiting!
Not so easy, is it, Matt?
Well, at least my cat's not stuck in a
tree!
Taxi!
No taxi!
You kids want a cab?
Yeah!
You got any money?
No.
So?
It's my cousin!
Hi, Wade!
Need a lift?
Yeah!
Yay!
All right!
Her cousin?
What are the odds of that happening?
One in 4.2 million... Whatever!
I'm just glad we have a ride!
Excuse me, but what's a cousin?
Skip it.
Okay, here's the rules.
I'm gonna say this once, so listen.
Yeah?
Dig it!
You're only here cause Sora is my cousin.
You're like your luggage.
Yeah.
We're like your luggage.
And luggage doesn't make a sound.
You got me?
Or else it's liable to get itself thrown
out of the car, right?
Right.
Luggage doesn't make a sound.
You want some gum?
Sugarless?
Uh, sure.
How about you, Sora?
Thanks, Dwayne.
Uh-oh!
Hey, Sora.
I think your cousin's a major ramo.
He's sort of the black sheep of the family,
but he's giving us a lift, so be nice.
I will, but just make sure he takes us to
Odaiba.
Do you like it?
Mm-hmm.
How did I ever get into this?
Knocking myself out searching for some
pipsqueak kid.
I got half a mind to chuck this whole
lousy job.
But the master might not like that.
The radio's kinda loud!
The tunes are kinda what?
The radio?
Still loud?
Maybe just a little!
Now for a news update.
Officials have yet to find a clear
explanation for the devastating explosion
that rocked the
Heightened View Terrace
apartments in the Norema
District earlier today.
Power in the area is
still out, and the injured
are still being counted
after the bizarre incident.
While official sources have
offered no further information,
there are reports of
several eyewitness accounts.
However, these accounts have only served
to further mystify investigators.
The details of their accounts differ,
but several of these eyewitnesses agree
that an elephant and something described as
a giant firebird were seen in the vicinity.
A giant what?
Firebird?
You gotta love the crazies in this town.
A similar incident took
place at the Heightened
View Terrace
apartments four years ago.
It's unknown whether there is any
connection between the two.
What's the matter?
Stop the guard!
Whoa!
What is that?
Coromon, you couldn't wait?
Okay, who did it?
Huh?
Which one of you made a mess of my new
seat covers?
I'm sorry, I... Right here, I'm the one!
I'll clean it up, I'll even detail it for
you.
Don't try covering up for these losers!
Which one of them was it?
You, Mr. Peepers!
It was you, wasn't it?
Hey, let him go, he didn't...
Izzy, no!
Ah!
Izzy!
Nah, I'm coming, is he?
Digimon!
Digilo monsters, Digimon are the
champions!
Digimon!
Digilo monsters, Digimon are the
champions!
Muddy-man!
Digimon!
Tinko-man!
Ah, Izzy!
Thanks, Tato!
Ugh, you had to have that extra side of
chili fries, didn't you?
Hey, watch that!
You are... Yeah?
It's Ges-O-man!
It's what?
Ges-O-man!
Take a bit of everything nasty that lives
under water, stick them together,
and that's him!
Ah!
You get to run your own!
Good riddance, you're a lousy driver
anyway!
Digimon!
Digilo monsters, Digimon are the
champions!
Digimon!
Digilo monsters, Digimon are the
champions!
Go-O-man!
Digimon!
I think we'll just get out of the way!
Oh!
Coral Crosher!
Oracle Torpedo!
Holy cow!
What's going on?
They must be advertising something!
Advertising something?
Get out of here!
Maybe they're shooting a movie.
I don't see any cameras.
Oh well, maybe they're just rehearsing.
And so then you know what he said?
Oh, what's that?
What's going on over there?
Rough day at work, huh?
Uh, you know, same old set.
My money's on the big hairy one!
Bad!
Man, did you guys see that?
Zora?
Hey Zora!
Where'd all those kids go?
Well, so much for keeping a low profile.
At least we got away from lame Dwayne and
we're all in one piece.
Nice work, Ikakumon.
You nailed him!
Anyway, wouldn't
you rather travel in the
fresh air than under the
ground in that subway?
Oh yeah, this is great!
And best of all, it's free!
Here's good news!
Now that they've shown themselves,
we can finally take care of them!
Next up, home!
Yeah!
Good home!
Does anybody have something to eat?
Oh, Mimi, not that again.
I was just asking!